<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="story_names7">

        <item>Two Stubborn Women</item>
        <item>Mysterium</item>
        <item>The Dark Comes Closer </item>
        <item>Spider-Man Pyjamas </item>
        <item>Awakening </item>
        <item>Dead Even</item>
        <item>Ouija Wine Wednesdays</item>
        <item>113</item>
        <item>Wanna play Yacht?</item>
        <item>Play With Me</item>
        <item>Household Gods</item>
        <item>The Lottery</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="Author_Name7">
        <item>Piper Mae</item>
        <item>Maizie Bymers</item>
        <item>Emily Craner</item>
        <item>S.Fernando</item>
        <item>Arnesha Jackson</item>
        <item>Liby Nel</item>
        <item>Kelly Di Mario</item>
        <item>Alyssa Telgenhoff</item>
        <item>Madhatter Thawne</item>
        <item>Annette C</item>
        <item>Brian Stanton</item>
        <item>Shirley Jackson</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories7">

        <item>

The night is thick and heavy with clouds when I paint the front of The House yellow.
I paint quickly and quietly. I don’t want to wake my neighbor up.
The brush goes shhh shhh against the wall and even that is loud.

\n\nMy feet crunch on gravel as I finish up and slip into my home.

\n\nMy neighbor\’s cursing wakes me up in the morning.
I hear fuck! and shit! I split the blinds with two fingers.
The sun shines very bright and I squint to see my other neighbors file outside.
They see the yellow paint and shake their heads. One of them points at my home.
I come away from the window.
Knock knock.
I do not answer.
I make myself toast with a poached egg.
I eat it plain.
Butter has a strange, slimy texture and most jams are too sweet for my taste.

\n\nThey pound on the door.
The doorknob rattles in its socket before I hear silence on my front porch again.

\n\nMy neighbors assume I painted The House.
They are right, but it\’s still insulting that they point to me first.

\n\nUpon purchase, my new neighbor repainted The House beige before moving equally bland
furniture (and herself) inside.
I must fix it.
She does not understand that each house claims life as we do.
Their creaks are small sighs and groans,
their breath the wind that flutters curtains when their mouths are unlocked.
Each house is individual in personality.
They have different mannerisms,
likes and dislikes that can influence whoever its inhabitant might be at the time.
Often, though, its influence is overruled by tenants that bustle about, c
reating their own noises that muffle their homes.

\n\nI can hear them.
I hear anger when doors slam shut, peace when furniture is aligned and floors are swept clean.
Houses do not have control over their appearance,
so I help them. I listen and give them a color true to their individuality.

\n\nThe House in question, which you could say is my current \“client,\” is bubbly,
but prone to sickness and somewhat oblivious to the struggles of others.
It loves its inhabitants—most of the time—and wishes to give them a cozy embrace.
Most of all,
The House is very particular about its appearance and becomes incensed when the smallest thing is not quite right.
Right now, it is sulking.
The little yellow I gave it placated it, but soon it will demand more.

\n\nIn the afternoon I hear the grrr grrr of trucks and metallic clanking and deep voices shouting.
Big men in loose denim pants and ugly T-shirts paint The House back to beige.
My neighbor comes onto her lawn to survey the men, pointing out the spots that need extra paint.
The painters finish quickly,
taking my neighbor\’s cash and leaving extra paint cans and brushes and crinkled plastic tarps.

\n\nThe House strains against its new skin.
It pummels its beige bonds with angry fists and wails It\’s so ugly! The neighboring houses think it silly and childish,
but they are too old to remember what it was like to be a child.
I will The House to be patient.
Its paint is still wet.

\n\nThe sun burns hot, then abruptly cools in the evening.
Rain is predicted in the next few days, so the air hangs thick like soaked velvet.
I shift from chair to chair, unable to settle.
I need distraction, so a sandwich is readily made and quickly eaten.
I flip through books before putting them down. I stack the books.
I eat some mini-pretzels. I play a movie and turn the volume up loud.
All is drowned out by The House’s pouts and whines.

\n\nI doze fitfully and when I sleep,
I dream of an infant pouring a dripping yellow sky onto little people that drown in thick sunflower puddles.

\n\nThe night I return to soothe The House, a small red eye blinks from the corner of its porch.
A camera makes my job harder, but it is only one.
My neighbor is either lazy, or thinks that its presence is enough to deter me.
Either way, that is her mistake. I open my paint can and approach from an angle.
I grab a handful of viscous yellow and smear it over the lens.
The paint is cool and slippery, coating the lens completely while the excess puddles in the dirt below.
After that, it is a simple matter to paint as much yellow as I can in the time that I have.
I cannot fully free The House, but its grousing quiets and it settles more comfortably into its foundations.

\n\There is more cursing in the morning and more banging against my door.
This time, my neighbor screams through the door.
She says open up or I\’ll break the fucking door down.
My own home is a demure thing sheathed in light brown.
A broken door will cause it tremendous pain and that will not do.

\n\nMy neighbor\’s hair is unbrushed and sticks out like fur.
She wears a big t-shirt and no shoes.

\n\nI wish she was wearing shoes.
I think feet are so foreign.
I forget I have feet until I look down and wonder how something so strange could be attached to me.

\n\nI know it\’s you, she says.

\n\nI\’m quiet. I\’ll hear what she has to say.

\n\nMy neighbor turns red. Say something, she says.
You are the only person here who would paint my house yellow every fucking night.
I moved here and I heard stories about you.
You stare at all the houses and peek in the windows and you talk to yourself more than you talk to other people.

\n\nMy neighbor goes on and on.
She is quite incensed.
Spittle flies from her lips and she jerks her hands about to show just how angry she is.

\n\nShe says, You\’re free to do what you want, but Jesus Christ,
you have to know you look absolutely fucking crazy.
The house was one thing, the camera is just ridiculous.
I could put in a report for vandalism! I could call the police! What are you gonna do,
deny it? You stupid bitch, I should report you right—

\n\nI don\’t deny it, I say.

\n\nHer mouth gapes.
In addition to a hot temper, she also has strange rules about what is right and what is wrong.
The rules of her world apply to everyone.
She straightens my trash bins on trash day to match her own.
She quips often about the unique color of our shared fence, which is blue, though the blue is not on her side.

\n\nI\’m not bothered by it. My ambivalence (or apathy, in her mind) infuriates her.
It\’s amusing to see her realize that I won\’t fight her, not in this way.

\n\nShe opens and closes her mouth and turns more red.
Just stop painting my fucking house, she says.
And then she hacks a glob of spit onto my porch and leaves.

\n\nI see her painting over the yellow with rough strokes of beige paint.
Her work is streaky and thick globs drip down the woodwork.
It will harden and texture The House, which it will not like.
More cameras go up too,
one in the opposing corner of the front porch and and two more on the corner nearest to my home.

n\nAt night, I cover my face and approach not from my home, but through the backyards of neighboring houses.
I tell the houses hello and they breathe creaky whistles in return.
Many of the houses in this neighborhood are like my own: plain, ordinary, normal.
They do not require the same attention as The House.

\n\nI use paint again to cover the cameras.
My work is sloppier than previous nights and The House complains.
I tell it that its tenant has made my work more difficult and this is the best that I can do.
The House asks if it should do something to stop its tenant.
I say no, that goes too far.
I try to smooth out the streaky bits, apologize again, then come home.

\n\nMy hands shake as I wash out my paintbrush and dry my hands.
I suppose I\’m nervous about my neighbor\’s threat.
I don\’t fear the police or the possibility of arrest,
but rather I fear that if I am taken away, The House will not be cared for.
Who else can do what I do? Without me,
The House will push against its bland exterior and cry and cry.
Its caterwauling would also bother the other houses on the street, kind as they are.

\n\nAt night I dream again of a yellow paint sky,
but this time I am drowning and the viscous liquid is rising and
I cannot see through the lemon film that covers my eyes.
I am enveloped and smothered in an inward explosion of death.

\n\nI wake early.
I sip tea and let the hot mug burn my hands crimson while I peer through the window.
I stand there for an hour,
maybe longer, until my tea has gone cold and I find myself shifting from foot to foot.
I still when the door of The House opens and my neighbor steps out onto the porch.
She sees the damage to the cameras and the return of the yellow paint.
She stands there for a moment, then turns back inside.

\n\nI turn away from the window.
She has seen what I\’ve done, yes, but what is to come of it?
I go through the motions of my morning,
washing my face, changing into day clothes and making a bowl of cereal.
My ears hear The House\’s moans and its companions\’ whispers of encouragement, but no sirens.

\n\nClouds veil the sun as it dips and a gentle rain coats my neighborhood.
An earthy, slightly bitter scent emanates from the lawns and swathes of asphalt.
Petrichor: a phenomenon both clean and dirty, clinging and cleansing.
The houses love it. They inhale and exhale, inhale and exhale.

\n\nThe rain calms me.
I see no flashes of blue and red or the slap of heavy tires on wet asphalt.
I don\’t know why my neighbor failed to follow through on her threat.
Maybe she forgot.
Maybe she wants to keep me in suspense and prolong my anxiety.
Maybe, far-fetched as it is, she hopes to continue this little feud because she loves a good fight.
This will turn into a game, a competition between two stubborn women: one who refuses to admit fault,
and one who will never stop.
\n\nI will know tomorrow.
        </item>
        <item>

\"Come on guys please can we play the Mysterium,\" I pleaded to my 3 best friends Robert (Rob) Johnson, Ivy Ruth, and Rebecca Garden.

\n\n\"Sure,\" Rebecca said,
twirling in the seats in my basement meeting room which my dad usually uses for work but not today because it was a Saturday.

\n\n\"We always play this game,\" Rob groaned, which was true but still it\'s an awesome game.
\"Plus I\'m always stuck as a ghost.\"

\n\n\"Well not today my dad promised me that he would be a ghost.\"

\n\n\"Sure, Rubs,\" Ivy said, sitting down next to Rebecca.

\n\n\"Fine. But you promise me I wont be a ghost,\" Rob said sitting down across from Ivy.

\n\n\"I swear,\" I replied sitting next to him.
My dad hurried down the stairs still in his sweatpants and sweater which was very different then the usual
stiff black suit and tie he wore to meetings about his books that he wrote and the book store he owned.

\n\n\"Who\'s ready for Mysterium,\" He said, taking it off of a shelf on the wall.
We sorted out characters. Me: Alma, Ivy: Jessalyn, Rebecca: Madame Wang, Rob: Alphonse, Dad: Ghost.

\n\n\"Let\'s start,\'\' my dad said.
After 50 hours (15 min) of setting, we finally began but soon there was a rattle shock in the room.
Then everything fell into darkness.

\n\n\"What happened? Ruby, Rob, Rebecca are you okay,\" A voice but that of Ivy\'s.
It was like the voice of a (I\'m completely guessing) 1920\'s American woman.

\n\n\"I\'m fine,\" I replied but my voice was like what a Spanish woman would have sounded like in the 1920\'s as well.
I looked around and we were in the front of a tall mansion.

\n\n\"Me too,\" A heavy French accent called out.

\n\n\"And me,\" I said in a Chinese accent.
I turned around looking at the other people circling me.
They were my friends but they were also the characters we had picked in the game.

\n\n\"Wait one minute I\'m Alma. Rob your Alphonse.
Rebecca your Wang and Ivy your Jessalyn.\"

\n\n\"Which means we are in the game,\" Rebecca said. \"And this is the manor\."

\n\n\"And your dad is just a ghost most likely trying to give us visions now so do you all remember who to get them.\"
No we all said in unison but then we saw a button on our arms and when you saw a button you always got to press.
I waited a while but I only felt an odd wait in my pocket.
I pulled out a Pendulum and a card just like the ones in the game/rule book.

\"Alma Salvador\"

Specialty: Pendulum Divination,\" Wow I thought reading that I get visions through this (I held the pendant).
I held it up and closed my eyes. That\'s when I saw what was almost like a camera moving closer    to the door.

\"Let\'s go inside,\" I said, walking towards the door and opening it causing a LOUD creaking noise.
I stepped followed by the others.
That\'s when I saw 5 suspects sitting at the dining room table.
One looked like a chef and the one next to him was a hunter.
There was at the head of the table a con man magician and to his right was a maid and a woman with a basket full of baked goods.
I watched them but knew they could see we were here.
I looked up and saw there were 3 sets of staircases.
The second floor had a bunch of rooms and on the last level there were weapons laid out on different podiums.

We then heard a whisper stretch throughout the dim room, \"Madame Wang.\"
She looked terrified but then closed her eyes and pulled out a book and found what visions she needed.\"

\"Mine are only two and they\'re identical to some cards.
Mine is a house with buttons on it and rope strung across and also a mouse with a bird outfit on.\"
I knew which one it was immediately so I told her.

\"I think it\'s the maid with her buttons and tailoring just like on the mouse,\" She nodded and said, The maid.
That\'s when the maid disappeared into a card on her chair for Rebecca to pick up. None of the other suspects noticed.
Rebecca went up the staircase.

\"Jessalyn Smith,\" My dad said.
Ivy took out tarot cards and pulled 2 from the deck.
One was of a girl and a lion on a boat pointing towards the ocean.
The second was off a man running away from something on a red carpet with guard dogs barking at him.

\"This is easy,\" Ivy said, \"The hunter.\"
He vanished leaving the card for her to take.
She went up the stairs slightly tripping on heels which made me and Rebecca giggle.

\"Alphonse de Belcour,\" The ghost whispered. He closed his eyes and did his numerology.
He told me what his 2 cards were.
One was  a cave with axes and gleaming red eyes looking out of it and the second was the same rat dressed as a bird standing on cheese.

\"Easy this is Magician,\" He said, but nothing happened.
I rubbed my temples.

\"No, it\'s obviously the chef.
Didn\'t tell you tell me was on top of cheese,\" I shook my head and took out the Pendulum and watched it swirl and got my two cards.
One had pastries falling from the sky so I didn\'t even pay attention to the second one.

\"The baker,\" I called and she was gone so I took the card and went up the stairs.

\"Madame Wang,\" The house echoed.
She took out her book which I could now see was a ghost mystery book.
There were 5 rooms just like the 5 people.
One was a dungeon with a mysterious cave blocked by a book stand.
The second was a bedroom with a stone lion hanging on it with an open window and drapes hanging off the top frame of the bed.
The one next to it was also a bedroom but this one was pink and open with toys thrown around instead of a dark ominous nighttime room.
There was light everywhere and a purple rug on the floor.
The next room reminded me of a tropical forest but there was a weird tombstone in the middle with the same lion.
There was also some kind of dome enclosing it like a greenhouse.
The last one was an abandoned home patio looking out on a dead forest with a chair and table on the patio.

\"The next visions show me a man on an odd bicycle flying in the air.
The second was a bunch of books stacked to look like a triangle,\" She said looking at the 5 rooms.
\"I\'m going with the child\'s room.\" It vanished, leaving only the card behind.
She went up the last set of stairs.

\"Jessalyn Smith,\" The ghost whispered.
She stepped forward and pulled her two cards.
Here\'s where a red chair in the middle of a room and a red bed surrounded by ether stuffing our clouds.

\"Easy, bedroom,\" She said and it was gone and she left me to go with Rebecca.

\nAfter a few minutes I was with rob again, \"Alma Salvador.\"
I took out the pendulum and got the visions.
One off a little spiked creature wearing a skull like mask the other an apple
punctured by needles dripping black stuff down the pestle it was on.

\"Green house,\" I called but nothing happened.
No, it was the dungeon off course both showed torture like in a dungeon.

\"Madame Wang,\" I didn\'t hear what happened for the rest of the turns because Rebecca and Rob moved up but soon it was Me,
Rob, and Ivy left cause Rebecca had passed and disappeared.

\"Jessalyn Smith,\" Dad said.
I waited until she got it right her visions were 2 ones showing magic and a circus so her weapon was dumb bell like the worlds strongest man.
Then Rob got it right with the candlestick and both his pictures showed fire.
(You can see that I\'m not putting as much effort into writing any more because I\'m getting tired of writing about this.
This is Ruby talking) Finally, it was my turn and I got it right with the type writer because one pictured showed a business mouse.
Finally we were done and I was back in the basement with dad and everyone else.
\"Okay now that was weird,\" We all said.
        </item>
        <item>

Riley stares at her mother as the morning officially begins.
Some people would signal these things with an alarm clock while others maybe await its arrival with the passage of the sun.
Riley waits for her mother to plug in the coffee maker and it doesn\’t officially count until her mother receives
the daily shock from the dilapidated outlet.
Dennis says that exposure to that much electricity is going to kill her one of these days but Riley\’s seen
people in this town go through worse and still walk away alive.
Why,
they say old man Tuner\’s been struck by lightening three times which is way worse than a little shock in the
\n\nmorning as far as Riley\’s concerned.

Either way, it\’s how she knows the day is going to start.
Sure enough, her mother pulls the old machine out of its place and mumbles as she looks around for that red bucket labelled simply \‘beans\’.
Nothing fancy or anything more than simple words etched on in black Sharpie.
It was written on long before Riley had learned what letters even were.
\n\nHer mom says she used to want to eat those sharpies because of their smell.

There\’s the zap she\’s expecting and her mother waves her now burned hand in the air
like that will take the sting away and share it with the kitchen at large.
\n\n\“Bastard!\” her mother spits out like a hissing pole cat and Riley smiles because the morning has officially begun.

\n\n\“Think it\’s gonna rain mama?\” she asks and slides into the kitchen to stand beside her mother who smells like coffee and cinnamon.

\“Rain?\” her mother asks, burned hand dropping as she forgets the sting and peers out the window to stare at the growing sunset.
\n\nIn the distance is a spot of darkness that looks like gathering clouds. The making of a nasty storm.

Riley is excited for the future blanket forts and the sound of rain lashing onto their roofs.
Her mother heaves a sigh at the knowledge that the small house
\n\nwill be cramped of energetic children with a desire to move and do and nowhere to go.

\n\n\“I guess it is. Riley, go wake your father up and tell him he needs to tie down the tarp for his project.\”

\“Okay mama.\”
\n\nRiley says obediently and goes to warn her dad that a storm is threatening to undo months\’ worth of work on his father\’s old truck.

\n\nDennis stares blankly at his bare wall and wonders if anybody else in the house is up yet.
Probably not because nobody in this house ever wakes up before 7 and only then because three
different alarms will blare and scream to be heard, demanding to be turned off personally.
Mom will smack her hand down with venom and Dad will sit up before politely stopping his.
Andy will roar and there\’ll be the sound of smashing followed by Mom yelling to stop breaking shit.
\n\nIt\’s the morning routine.

A routine he\’s not allowed to share because nobody outside of their house is ever to tell another
soul that they\’re anything less than plastic perfection.
They used to say they were perfect but ever since Mom started seeing a surgeon about her wrinkles,
Andy\’s been calling it plastic perfection.
Dennis doesn\’t feel like it\’s quite accurate because plastic itself is different in every conceivable way
\n\nbut he does enjoy the way his parents go red. Anything that annoys them that much has got to be good.

He\'s awake and not sure if telling a doctor about these sleepless nights is going outside of the idea of perfect.
He read somewhere that he has insomnia and that there\’s medication to help one sleep but is that too abnormal for his perfect life?
He needs to sleep but he has no money to buy it on his own.
Maybe if he promises to stop mentioning plastic whenever his parents are nearby, they\’d let him ask somebody.
Maybe they\’ll stop looking at him like he\’s broken when he shares his knowledge.
\n\nMaybe they wouldn\’t have to live so far away from town for fear that the neighbors would look in and see them being human for a moment.

Their house is on the very edge of a town too small to make itself known on the map which is just where his dad claimed was perfect.
Dennis thinks it\’s because it\’s the perfect place to hide.
rom what, nobody will ever let him know but there\’s got to be a reason why his dad looks over his shoulder whenever they enter town.
Nobody here is anything deserving of suspicion,
and they know everyone\’s name yet his father is always looking behind him when he pulls out his wallet.
\n\nHe twitches like he\’s never safe and sometimes, Dennis wonders.

The wondering is stopped short when Dennis notices that his lamp is flickering on and off.
It struggles vainly before shrieking and giving out with a pop.
His room is now lit only by the light on the ceiling which is now beginning its own struggle to remain alight.
It too gives a hearty groan before surrendering and flickering out as well.
The room is bathed in darkness and Dennis finds himself afraid and unable to breathe.
\n\nFor the first time since he was little, he wants to call out for his Mom.

He hears the lights in the house begin to crackle and imagines that every bulb is
flickering to stay alive and then there\’s the pops as each one begins to lose its fight.
\n\nAround him the house begins to groan like it\’s being burdened with a weight too heavy to bear.

Old man Turner had lived in this town before it was even a town.
It\’d been nothing more than a handful of families who respected each other\’s privacy and left well enough alone.
He\’d seen people move in and people move out.
He\’d even seen his fair share of deaths.
\n\nBeing struck by lightening had made him feel like it was finally his turn to explore the innards of a wooden box but fate had kept him going.

Developers had even come and made this place a town but they\’d left with their money more gone than Old man Turner\’s imaginary funeral.
Nobody else had come in after them and he\’d laughed and laughed at their foolishness.
This wasn\’t the town for profit or growth.
This was a town for the forgotten and hopeless, the sinners hiding from their crimes.
\n\nNobody was going to care about this place and Old man Turner had been waiting a long time for the day its end would come.

Three bolts of lightening had tried to end him but he\’d carried on, determined to see the end.
Decades of living had finally resulted in the ending he awaited.
There wasn\’t any sense in telling these people because nobody would listen to a man old enough to lose his teeth and all he\’d known.
Wouldn\’t matter anyways because nobody in this town was the type to defy fate.
\n\nTell them doom is coming and like lowing cows, they\’d lower their heads and stare at the grass all docile like.

But he knew.
He\’d been waiting long enough.
Turner made sure to pull out his favorite rocking chair that he\’d carved himself and sits down with a groan as his bones pop and protest his age.
His favorite pop makes a delightful hiss as he opens the tab and takes a sip and carbonation burns all down his throat.
\n\nHe\’s on his porch and thinks there\’s nowhere better to end.

The darkness is coming for them and it\’s thicker than any cloud and darker than any sky.
The sun isn\’t rising and brining with it all the oranges and pinks of morning.
There\’s a darkness thicker than night and it\’s brining death and decay.
Maybe not even that.
Maybe it brings only an end and nothingness but either way,
\n\nit\’s crawling in all silent and thick like growing tar pretending it\’s a cat sneaking up on prey.

Tendrils of black creep lightly towards him and Turner watches with a placid grin as it crushes his old trees, as old as he is now.
They crumble like toothpicks beneath the weight of so much darkness and he knows that they\’ll demolish his house built over the years,
in less than a handful of seconds.
Behind Turner is the town just starting to wake up for the morning and none of them fools know the darkness is coming
\n\nand that morning is never really going to make it because nothing but an eternal night is creeping towards them.

\n\nAnd Turner, he can hardly wait for the end to come
        </item>
        <item>

\t\t\t<u><i><b>SPIDER-MAN PYJAMAS ,\"THE FALSE AWAKENING.\"</b></i></u>\n\n
\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t<u><i><b>EPILOGUE.</b></i></u>\n\n

I will never wear Spider-Man pyjamas in my entire life, possibly in my dreams that can happen,
that\'s because
i don\'t like Spider-Man,and I\'m hoping my kids won\'t like superheroes too,because they
often live double life and bring emotional pain to those
who love them by concealing their heroic character.\n\n

\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tBEGINNING OF THE STORY.\n

\n\nSometimes I take a discreet look at her without her recognizing, because she\'s a shy person,
she will cast a glance away if she ever catch me looking at her, at that starry moment I become breathless,
I never seen a thing so pleasing to look at ,yet it took me some time to see how beautiful she is
,and having to spend time with her I lost the reasons why I love her, hoping she doesn\'t woke up
one morning and ask me,why do you love me?,
i\'ll have no answer and i hope the lack of reasons doesn\'t convey lack of love,
in fact, adversely I love her more than the seasons I first met her with infinite number of reasons for my love.
Because here\'s the thing, in the morning and atwix the starry moment I\'d be so sure that her beauty was the reason
,and during the day I\'ll be having a different one and that is the way she makes me feel ,then later at night
my heart beats in the different rhythm and falsely convince myself that it\'s because she\'s intellectually smart,
I\'m saying \"falsely \" because when I wakeup in the morning I will handover all my unknown reason to god and
say \"fuck it I don\'t know why but I love her\" and if she ask I\'ma\' tell her \"I don\'t know\" and \"god please
play your role in defending me because you know how you made these women they will lose it over a tiny uncertainty\",
I just love everything about her with her unfavorable peccadilloes.
\n\nActually let me make it clear that she\'s not yet my girlfriend ,I have been trying my best to make her fall in love with me,
but she doesn\'t love me ,and just as I do not have
reasons for loving her ,she too doesn\'t have any why she doesn\'t love me,I ran out of ways to make her give me a chance
because it\'s half a decade now and not even a sign of hope ,and with this argument
maybe that\'s a reason why I love her this much,she\'s worth more than a half decade and I will keep on trying.
And that is why I don\'t like Spider-Man,the movie itself it great I enjoy it ,it only disappointing when he fell in love with marry,
how can he forcefully try to defy and deny the force of love marry Jane has for him?,whilst people like
me spend time trying to convince people who do not have love for us that we really love
them but anyway,maybe she is a superhero too,concealing her heroic personality.


\n\nSo when she finally said to me I love you and I\'d like us to try, I couldn\'t believe she finally
took her \"Cape\" off, I felt nervous yet happy, it was a bittersweet sense ,because she came when I was
least expected, unprepared and hopeless ,and now I\'m left to decide if I should give all my heart away
or give half as a \"decade\" in case this is her trial,however my happiness was above all my sentimental qualm at this
moment,I felt an extra heartbeat the whole universe went quiet and still as if storm
is about to strike,you should remember that this is the women who takes away my breath probably the love of my life,
so to act over my excitement a second later
I pulled her towards me and gently pushed her against the wall with my palm behind her head to protect
her from hard-hitting the wall while my body in contact with hers ,I then kissed her and sighed heavily my
patience out for waiting so long as a sign of relieve,I whispered \"what made you take so long?\", she looked at me and said,
your loved scared me, it\'s so excessive and it will take time to get used to it.
Even when I could feel the atmosphere,the texture of her skin and the scent of her perfume even her tasteless
lips I still couldn\'t believe it ,I thought I was in the dream.
I wrapped my arms around her small body and rest my forehead against hers.
In a fraction of a second a bright light coming from my window shone onto my face and ruined the moment,
when I open my eyes I realized I was really dreaming,that was a car taking a U-turn,these drivers takes advantage
since I do not have a fence encircling my yard,so I woke-up and got agitated immediately when I
found out it was all a dream,
but before the intensity of my wrath leveled-up, I felt a slight warmth from the body that was laying next to me,
\"This is my bedroom and I sleep alone here,
did my little brother crashed in since the past few days was busy renovating his room?
how can\'t I remember?\" I didn\'t drink last night to accuse alcohol for my oblivion,
I rolled my eyes over the entire room to confirm if I\'m in the right place.


\n\nThis moment of dementia reminded me of some silly group of boys in village who were well known for their wicked hobby for
using voodoo to make people fall in to slumbers and swap them in their sleep to different house
and in the morning they find themselves in bed with spouse which are not theirs ,even though
it was one of fables my grandmother use to share when I was a kid, at this time I was certain it was happening
to me waking up in the house that is not my own, that the boys they\'ve done it again,.
But "Sure I\'m in the right place here ,who\'s that sleeping on my bed?\"
At this point I\'m astound of how calm I was handling this enigmatic situation ,
I reached for the edge of blanket and slowly uncloak the body to reveal what I assume to be the face
\"if whatever was resting next to me was a person\".
And when I did I couldn\'t believe my eyes,\"am I dreaming again or what?,but I can not I just came back from one\"
I softly rubbed my eyes and grabbed the bottle of water on the table beside my bed and drank,
the girl who finally gave us a chance to be together from the
dream I just woke up from a minute ago was sleeping right next to me,
I got off the bed and round over to the side where her body was facing to get a proper look of her face,
I was so starry and again mesmerized by her beauty that the discomfiture of how she got here was no longer a concern
and surprisingly I enjoyed her mysterious presence , I accepted the reality and there I am happy again my heart
that was once broken when I realized I was dreaming was again mended.
But when I tried to caress her face ,before I even got to touch it I noticed I had a ring on my finger
\"a wedding ring on my finger!?\" ,are we married? ,I thought to myself.
No ways ,it can\'t be!, new thing I\'ve learned about her ever since we met is that she\'s a deep sleeper
\"like she has been worked by the voodoo boys\",she didn\'t even move when I pulled her hands which
she squeezed between her thighs and I looked at it she had a ring too.
It wasn\'t easy to accept simply because the notion of us dating was the most impossible one and far from reality
looking at how long I\'ve been waiting and trying I had no hope she\'ll give me a chance ,I always looked at myself as
nothing to her I carried no value ,this is because I have paid a close attention on how she treats me
she was so careless with my heart yet I went on loving her,\"this love thing\",
and if we\'re really married she must\'ve thought about it for so long and realize I was a best choice for her or
she ran out of options and made me a favour, but either way
I have to take care of this princess because my love has no favour.
But thus far I\'m still not sure what\'s going on ,I slided back her hand to where it was and as I do so for a moment I
felt like sliding mine instead,the warmth between her thighs it really did arouse me.

If it\'s not her I married ,then to whom am I married to, I cannot think of anyone else ,
she\'s been the only woman I have dreamed to be with.
I thought of every possibilities until I damned myself, I\'ve been investigating this mystery for too long ,I
finally decided to wake her up to hear what the horse its has to say,
I shook her and when she opened her pretty big eyes and gave me a look and said \"what!?\",I tried to be polite and said
,\"Hi what are you doing here ?\",my subconsciousness self warned me about this terrible question,I was setting
myself ablaze,from the first \"what!?\" I braced myself for the worse that is next about to come out of her lips.
She again said \"what!? \" this time her voice was firm and her eyes were fixed, her facial expressions showing great
irksomeness accompanied by surprise to my question.
my subconsciousness looked at me and said \"I warned you\".
What are you doing here? I asked again
She said we\'re married and I\'m your wife stupid and went back to sleep,
I swear I never felt so good being called a stupid in my entire life.
I was happy that she\'s mine and sleeping
right her next to me, I gave a kiss to her forehead and whispered \"I love you princess\", I sighed \"how long
I\'ve been dreaming ?\"and when I walk back to the bed I noticed I was wearing red \"Spider-Man pyjamas\" ,
I held my head high and exclaimed \"Damn not again!\",

        </item>
        <item>

The light flickers back and forth I curl in a ball and begin to cry.
The light flickers again and a woman stands in front of me,
looking at her reflection, with blood on her hands she yells her veins bulge in her neck and forehead.
I close my eyes out of fear of my life.
When I open them again another woman stands before me wearing an ankle length multi-color skirt with a long sleeve white button-down shirt.

There\’s a pool of black water in front of her she holds her hand out for me to follow her in.
I shake my head no \“Sorry I don\’t know you.\”\n
She fades before I could say anything else.\n
I\’m standing now observing the walls of the room surrounding me.\n
They form a cylinder.\n
I look up this isn\’t a room but a hole.\n
I look up to see a small light that seems to sway back and forth.\n
I begin to yell for help.\n
Someone any one can you hear men
No one says anything.\n
It\’s almost pitch black, but I can see small items.\n
I begin to search around with my hands to find a small rope and two hunting knives.\n
I begin to trace my hand along the wall feeling the softness in my hands.\n
A spark hope flickers in my chest.\n
I punch the wall to see if I can make a dent.\n
Dust falls but no dent not even a sound.\n
I take the knife and attempt to shove it in.\n
I have little success.\n
I do it again with a small running head start.\n
The knife goes in.\n
I do the same with the other knife a little higher than the next.\n
I attempt to pull myself up on the handle of the knife.\n
Success! I start using the knifes to climb out of the hole.\n
I look up the light flickers briefly bringing light into the black hole.\n
I can make out a tree and a woman with bright red hair looking down at me, she smiles and just as she appears she vanishes.\n
A little help I thought unable to speak between heavy breaths.\n
I\’m not even halfway there.\n
My arms grow tired, and my hand began to bleed the blood runs from my palms up my arm and drips on my forehead as I continue to pull myself up.\n
The lady with the red hair returns.\n
\“You need to stop.\”\n
\“Why?\” I ask.\n
She says noting only smiles and disappears again.\n
My arms are shaking so bad I can barely lift the knife and my arms are drenched in blood and dirt.\n
My face is covered in sweat dirt and blood I try to imagine my face but no imagine comes to mind.\n
How long had I been down here?  It\’s time to take a break I thought my body ached and shook all over.\n
I don\’t want to fall to the bottom.\n
I\’m unsure of how far I\’ve climbed.\n
I\’m no longer able to make out the floor of the hole.\n
This brings a smile to my face accompanied by a spark of energy.\n
I bring the knives together turn my back to the wall and begin to kick using the knives to hold my body wait up from behind.\n
I hold myself still and begin to swing my legs from side to side using my feet to dig while moving dirt.\n
I keep this up until I can swing my feet back and forth without resistance.\n
A side wall deep enough for me to stand in is behind me.\n
I slowly step down.\n
My legs almost give out.\n
My head starts to spin.\n
I use the wall to keep me standing.\n
I begin to use my hand to dig into dirt.\n
I take off my shirt and rip it in half to wrap my hands and stop the bleeding.\n
I continue to dig until I\’m capable to turn around.\n
Soon a there\’s a place big enough for me to sit and later to lay.\n
My body aches all over my skin feels like its crawling.\n
The dirt blood and sweat makes me sticky and I smell of iron, salt and must.\n
My eyes are no longer able to make out anything around me and my heart rings in my ears and rocks me to sleep.\n
I wake to complete darkness I\’m uncertain of how long I\’ve been sleep.\n
Time feels nonexistent.\n
I have a sensation of pins and needles all over.\n
My stomach starts to growl.\n
I use the wall to hold my body as I stand heat rushes all over me.\n
My knees buckle and my head drops.\n
I need to eat.\n
I stand still straighten my composure and focus on my breath to gain control of my body.\n
I begin to roll my stomach in taming my hunger.\n
I make a beat with my hands on my chest my hips follow.\n
My hunger fades.\n
I bend, stretch, and rise.\n
I throw a rock down to get an idea of how far I\’ve climbed a few moments later there\’s a small thud.\n
I smile turn around and jump a short distance to my knives.\n
I\’m almost to the top won\’t be much longer.\n
I focus on breathing and create a stable breath as I return to climbing.\n
It feels like my muscles are ripping.\n
My bones breaking.\n
I keep going I\’m almost too the top.\n
The flickering light gets closer and closer.\n
The heat of the hole gets hotter.\n
It becomes harder to breath.\n
I look to see two little girls run to the top of the hole one with
black hair and midnight skin the other with a caramel tone and bright red hair they look at me and smile.\n
\“You\’re so beautiful.\n
I want to be you when I grow up.\”\n
Tears began to fall from my eyes.\n
They look at each other and fade away.\n
The same as before I turn around and dig a place for me to sit.\n
I sob tears washes dirt from my face.\n
I let out a yell followed by a roar.\n
Why has no one come to help.\n
Is my life a show or something!? No one responds, except the walls echoing my voice.\n
I fall asleep sitting up straight.\n
A wake to the first woman yelling at me \“GET OUT NOW!!!!!!!\” An orange and red light surrounds her followed by smoke.\n
I can see details of the walls surrounding me.\n
How did she get down here? Before I could think further; She begins running towards me full force with two knives dripping blood.\n
Her eyes narrow.\n
Her muscles bulge against the wind her hair red flows around her face.\n
In a few seconds I can feel her body heat nearing mine and she begins to raise knife emotionless precise.\n
Without thinking I begin to climb faster and faster not looking back or down only on the knives in front me climbing out of the hole.\n
I yell.\n
I cry.\n
My hand began bleeding again.\n
I feel noting but the beat in my chest reminding me I\’m alive.\n
In a few moments I\’m at the top of the hole pulling myself out.\n
I take a deep breath and sprint to a tree in front of me.\n
I use the tree for cover from the crazy woman behind me.\n
As I turn the woman is not there instead smoke and lava takes her place.\n
It doesn\’t spill over but it splatters and bubbles small rocks form around the hole as the lava settles down to the volcano floor.\n
I examine the area around me to my left there\’s a black body of water I run to it.\n
Suddenly realizing my thirst.\n
I look at my reflection as I use the water to wash my hair.\n
My hands tingle.\n
The blood stops.\n
My wombs start to disappear.\n
My hair shines bright red and wild against the moonlight
        </item>
        <item>

Nights like these woke the demons – when the stars blinked coldly in the lonely expanse of the sky and the sea heaved and sighed like
a wounded beast.

\n\nMatt poured a double from the side-table on the veranda and took a swig.

\n\nThe flickering lights of the town across the bay reminded him of the lights of long ago:
neon lights winking down the coast; fire light from their beach barbeque tangled in her hair; the light gleaming
in Derek\’s eyes as he put his arm around her shoulders, his mocking gaze daring anyone to challenge his right of possession.
No-one did.
Everyone laughed, sucked up to him – the alpha male in the pack.

\n\nMatt could barely disguise his dislike for the man.
It wasn\’t just because Derek stole the love of his life.
If Julie had been happy, he could’ve made peace with it.
May the best man win, and all that jazz.
But she wasn\’t.
He knew her well enough to detect not only unhappiness but fear.
It bothered him immensely.

\n\nMatt poured another whisky.
Fact is, there was something about Derek.
Perhaps it lay in what he did for a living.
An ex-member of the military special forces, he was a human killing machine. Matt suspected he now worked as a mercenary.
Every now and then he would disappear to God knows where, each time returning with his self-confidence and recklessness reinforced.

\n\nA dangerous man.

\n\nThe yachts bobbing in the harbour suddenly awoke in Matt an intense urge to escape, to just board one of them and sail away.

\n\nRidiculous.
He was already half a world away from that night, not long after their beach barbeque,
when Julie came to his apartment, her eyes stirring a premonition in his belly.

\n\n\“Matt… I\’m in trouble.\”

\n\nA great stillness came over him.

\n\n\“Derek?\”

\n\nShe nodded, biting her lip.

\n\n\“Oh, Matt, I\’m so sorry…I don\’t know what possessed me to get involved with him.
I never really loved him.
It has always been you.\”

\n\nHer face crumpled and he buried it against his chest, holding her tightly until her sobs subsided.

\n\n\“What happened?\”

\n\n\“I tried breaking up with him.
We had such a fight.
He hit me.
Said if he couldn\’t have me, nobody would, and I\’d better believe it.\”

\n\nHer eyes filled with tears as she lifted her T-shirt.
Her ribcage and stomach were black and blue.
Bruises and broken skin on her wrists peeped from her sleeves.

\n\nA red fog filled Matt\’s head.

\n\n\“I\’m taking you to the police station, now!\”

\n\n\“No, no, Matt! He said if I go to the police, he will kill me, make it look like an accident.
I believe him, Matt.
You know he\’s capable it.\”

\n\n\“What? You want to let him get away with this? Not a chance!\”

\n\nShe took his face between her palms, her petrified face inches from him, her eyes pleading.

\n\n\“You have to help me disappear, Matt. Without a trace. And quickly.\”

\n\n\“Calm down, Julie.
This thug must be brought to justice.
They\’ll lock him up. You\’ll be safe.\”

\n\n\“He\’ll kill me before they can put him behind bars.\”

\n\n\“Get a restraining order.\”

\n\n\“Hah! As if that will stop him.
And he won\’t be locked up for life over this.
When he gets out of jail, the nightmare will start all over.\”

\n\nEmotions warred in his chest.
He knew she was right, but every instinct rebelled against running away and letting this brute win.

\n\n\“We\’re reporting this to the police.
You\’re putting in leave and moving in with me today.
He won\’t get to you here.
We\’re on the thirtieth storey and the apartment block has strict security.
Once he\’s behind bars, we can sort out the future.\”

\n\nTwo days later, Matt exited the elevator in his office block\’s parking garage when Derek stepped from the shadows, a menace in his glare.

\n\n\“I know she\’s with you.
I\’ll get her.\”

\n\n\“Why aren\’t you behind bars where you belong?\”

\n\n\“Bail, my friend.\”

\n\n\“I\’m getting a restraining order against you, Derek.\”

\n\nMatt stepped around him and walked to his car.
Suddenly, he was spun around with a force that nearly dislocated his shoulder.

\n\nDerek\’s face was centimetres from his.

\n\n\“You think you can steal Julie from me? I\’ll make you both pay.\”

\n\nThe voice was soft, the threat unmistakable.

\n\nWrenching his arm free, Matt shrugged back into his jacked, straightening his tie.

\n\n\“We\’ll see about that.\”

\n\nHe walked away with Derek\’s eyes boring into his back and dread sliding down his spine.
At that moment, he knew there\’s no protecting Julie from this man.

\n\nA month later, the two of them winged their way to New Zealand to start a new life.

\n\nIt was five years later when Matt found a parcel addressed to him in his mailbox.
Curious, he tore it open.
Inside, neatly folded, was a woman\’s blouse.

\n\nMatt frowned.
There was something familiar about the garment…the fragrance…Recognition hit him: it was the blouse Julie had worn at the beach barbeque.

\n\nHorror ripped through his gut.
He poured himself a double from the liquor cabinet and chucked it back, an icy fist clenching his heart. Derek had found them.
He took a few deep breaths.

\n\nDamn Derek to hell.
The past was the past and that\’s where it would stay.
This time they would disappear without a trace.

\n\nHis mind worked feverishly.
Tomorrow they would empty the bank accounts and catch the first available flight out – to wherever.

\n\n\“Hi, Matt.\”

\n\nJulie dropped her handbag on the sofa and walked over to kiss him. Her eyes fell on the blouse and the smile dropped off her face.

\n\n\“Noooo!\”

\n\nShe dropped to her knees, her faced buried in her hands, her shoulders shaking.

\n\nThe following afternoon, Matt unlocked the front door and froze as he stepped into the hall.
There were voices in the lounge, Derek\’s voice!

\n\nTwo strides brought him to the door. Julie, ashen faced, sat on the floor in front of the music centre.

\n\n\“The flash drive was in the mailbox.\”

\n\nHe remembered the night it was recorded.
It was a karaoke evening they went to on his birthday.
They were pretty smashed, and Derek recorded their witticisms and singing.

\n\nThe bastard! Matt wouldn\’t allow him to steal the rest of their lives.
They flung their clothes into suitcases, grabbed their passports from the desk drawer and fled,
snatching their laptops on the way to the front door.

\n\nOn the highway, a sense of danger niggled at the back of his mind, and he kept checking the rear-view mirror on their way to the airport.

\n\nIt wasn\’t until he took the mountain pass off-ramp that he noticed the car behind him. Was it following them?

\n\nHe accelerated as much as the steeply winding road allowed him.
The red sports car behind him followed suit.

\n\nPerspiration broke out on his forehead.
As he screeched around the bends, he watched the red car narrowing the gap between them until its headlights were a blinding glare in his mirror.

\n\n\“What\’s wrong, Matt?\”

\n\nHe heard the panic in Julie\’s voice.
Turning left sharply, he took a narrow turn-off, fighting to keep the wildly swerving car under control.
His rear bumper nicked the red sports car as it flashed past, sending it flying off the cliff.
Julie screamed. The driver looked back, his shocked face clearly illuminated by a passing vehicle.

\n\nDerek.

\n\nMatt stopped the car and rushed to the edge of the abyss.
The red car hit the bottom, bursting into flames.

\n\nMatt rubbed his face with a shaking hand, staring into the dark.
The lights of the city far below reminded him of the lights of long ago…neon lights flickering down the coast towards home.
        </item>
        <item>

I\’ve never seen a ghost, but I believe the people that have.
I spend a lot of my time pondering what lies on the other side of this life,
knowing deep down that my \‘research\’ will only ever lead into a purgatory of unresolve,
deep diving into an unanswerable abyss.
That infamous Houdini secret word is ever present in my mind during my other worldly pursuits.
The story goes that during their own quest for answers about what exists in the afterlife,
Harry and Bess also set out to unmask fraudulent psychics (oxymoron?) in the process.
Bess, fulfilling a promise they had made to each other,
went from psychic-to-psychic following Harry’s untimely death for the remainder of her life seeking their secret word from beyond the grave.
\“Believe.\”\n
She never heard it.\n
This story haunts me.\n
In life, human beings are so capable, at times transcending even their own limits, discovering things barely fathomable,
below earth\’s surface and out into space and beyond.
If we are so astonishingly capable on this earthly plane how could it be that no one has been able to send a
definitive message to the living from beyond? What awaits us?
The creation of religion an often-deadly salve created to soothe the suffering brought
upon us by evolution and the ultimate development of a frontal lobe.
Without setting out to do so I had unwittingly revolved my life around the inexplicable,
by day as a robotics engineer searching for answers in deep space and by night with my best friend, Serena,
a self-proclaimed \“gypsy\” who performed weekly seances in her living room.

\n\nI had developed a most unlikely friendship with Serena through a shared disdain for an ex-boyfriend we had dated simultaneously, unknowingly.
Once we uncovered his deceit,
we did the female unthinkable, and wrote ourselves a triumphant finale sprung from a nonexistent feminist fairytale.
We chose each other over him.
We thought if we could perform this kind of magic in the real world, maybe our shared powers could extend to the beyond.
Blond and meek in stature,
Serena was the more fairy-like in appearance of the two of us as well, my dark hair and features foreshadowing my skeptical nature.
I admit it was an unusual bond,
as I lived the life society and my parents had dreamt up for me in an effort to pursue all the
commercial trappings advertised to make you happy like designer bags and clothes while Serena needed no more than hand-me
downs and thrift shop specials, always pulling off her eclectic look.
Serena would take me to her favorite psychic shops on the weekends where she would wave various incense sticks under
my nose and shuffle through gorgeous sets of tarot cards.
I adored these trips with her although I could never truly shake my cynical nature or the education that had so severely glued my feet to earth.
I have, however seen death tempt even the most hardcore atheist
to hope against all available earthly evidence that something lies beyond,
a happy place where our beloved ones exist still, a place where we will be united in dreamlike perpetuity.
And even after all the evidence to the contrary is presented to me day after day,
I am still a person who wants to believe that magic exists.

\n\nSo even though the ghosts Serena and I have summoned have not yet appeared, she is not a doubter like me.
She is a knower, needing no proof to believe, magic appearing to her everywhere,
all her actions denoting a plan laid forth for her by the universe as she speaks to her dead relatives over our weekly Ouija board sessions.
My copious research to-date had provided no evidence for the afterlife,
but personal prayers had led to some tangible success and I had even met with a
preeminent South Carolina psychic who provided some bone chilling details about the specific
chardonnay preferences of my deceased Grandma and the dog that accompanies her in the spirit world (\“little and brown\”). Koko.
I missed them both.
This could not have been the result of googling as this information was not mentioned in her obituary and she passed
prior to the invention of social media.
In absence of definitive answer could it be her? Them? My beloved grandma and our little brown dog,
come to tell me everything is ok, that I am loved here and beyond.
Serena took this as proof to support her case for magic while
I was just game to drink wine and play a Hasbro board game and unwind with her after a stressful work day.
It couldn\’t hurt to see if my Grandma wanted to do the same.

\n\nTonight was my turn to supply the wine for our and Ouija Wine Wednesday at Serena\’s apartment.
I arrive at her apartment door and stand atop her \“Witches Welcome\” mat while
I balance two bottles of red wine under my arm and knock on the door.
My knock doesn\’t incite any barking behind the door, a reminder that
I should, but never will, accept the fact that cats are the more peaceful, if not less affectionate apartment companion.
The door knob begins to jiggle as Serena unlocks and opens the door.
She is an impish vision in her pink robe and black leggings, platinum blond hair pinned back displaying the sprouting of dark roots.
My beautiful hippie friend opens the door and immediately walks away leaving me pushing the door open to let myself in.
\“Come in Cupcake, I\’m just finishing up a few things in here.\”

\n\nI walk through the cherry-paneled kitchen to the living room where velvet chairs sit on opposite sides of Serena\’s small,
circular dining room table, appropriately covered by a red patterned table cloth, the ominous Ouija board sitting pristinely on top.
The living room is blanketed by burgundy tapestries and the window blinds are drawn tightly closed beneath rows of curtain lights.
The result is a cozy, dark psychic haven.
A dubious thought creeps in as I stop for a second and wonder why ghosts are more likely to come to a dark place.
I push the logic away.
Serena bends down and lights the incense on the coffee table which is set amongst a
smattering of her favorite gypsy tchotchkes including a beige antique tea leaf reading cup and several divination candles in neon colors.

\n\n\“Where is your wine opener?\” I ask her as she sits down at the Ouija table.

\n\n\“It\’s in the drawer to the right of the stove I think, \“she responds without looking over to me.
I open the drawer and it\’s not there, so I continue searching through other drawers.
As I hunt, I ask her how her day was.
She recently got a new job in retail,
the commercial designer kind, not the mystical variety and I wonder how she fares in that cold, harsh bottom-line business.

\n\n\“Eh, you know, no Stephens or anything but I hope I don\’t need to stay at this corporate monstrosity too long.\”
Stephen is the name we created in rejection of the misogynistic \“Karen\” term so readily
accepted and disseminated by society to describe a difficult, whiny customer.

\n\n\“How was your day?\” she asks me as she places the planchette delicately in the neutral zone in the middle of the board.

\n\n\“Oh, you know another day of space bewilderment,\”
I respond as I fumble with her clunky wine opener.
She looks up from the board and flashes her contagious smile at me.
\“Well, it\’s time to shed all that white coat energy and come over here to enter the shimmery netherworld,\” she says.

\n\nI pour out two sizable portions of wine and bring them over to the Ouija table sitting myself opposite Serena.
She always begins our sessions with her little spirit chant, which I accept as readily as I would any pre-meal prayer performed by a host.
I tell her the Houdini story and how adversely affects my supernatural expectations.
Serena grabs my hand and squeezes it in understanding and
I instantly relax at the touch of warm skin on my hands that have spent a long day spent handling cold, robotic metal.
She closes her eyes and bows her head and I follow suit.

\n\n\“Spirits and heavenly creatures of the light, we beckon you tonight with love and acceptance in our hearts.
Bring your love and light to us spirits so we can know you too.\”
She lifts her head, looks at me and winks.
\“Ok Cupcake, you ready?\” she asks as she sets her pointer and middle fingers on the plastic toy.

\n\n\“As ready as I\’ll ever be for a ghost visit,\” I say and place my fingers on the other side of the device.

\n\n\“Are we searching for someone specific tonight or are you still trying to get Houdini to tell you that word?\”
she asks me as casually as if she is inquiring about how I take my coffee.

\n\n\“I didn\’t know spirits took request,\” I reply somewhat snidely.
\“Can we get JFK here because we’ll be able to make some good money on a book talking about what really happened that day.\”

\n\nSerena gives me a sideways glance, purses her lips, and closes her eyes.
\“Spirits of the netherworld,\” she begins.
\“Please ignore my good friend Rose as she is a skeptic who has lost her sense of wonder for the other world.
Is anyone there to restore her faith in the unseen?\” I stare down at our hands on the planchette,
and it begins to move slowly up and to my right, the plastic centerpiece landing on, \‘yes.\’

\n\nWe both look down, clock the answer, and move the planchette back to the middle of the board.
Serena lifts her chin up and closes her eyes again.
\“Welcome spirit,\” as if narrating Dickens.
\“Is there a Harry Houdini in the netherworld?\”
Her eyes stay closed as I look from her back down to the board and it begins moving in the same direction and lands on the same answer.
\“Yes.\” I smirk and we replace the Planchette.

\n\n\“Can we speak to Harry Houdini?\” asks Serena dramatically.
Our fingers land on the affirmative again.

\n\n\“Mr. Houdini\,” Serena starts.
I silently commend her deference to the dead.
\“We are here to acknowledge your existence in the other world. Mr. Houdini, what is your secret word?\”

\n\nNothing happens for a few seconds as I glance back and forth from Serena\’s closed eyes to our fingers on the board.
I am wondering if the spirits would allow me to life my finger for just a quick sip
of wine when the plastic device starts moving around the center of the board, the alphabet.
Over to my left, down to my right, \‘R…. O…S…A…B…E…L…B…E…L…I…E….\’

\n\n\“Very funny Serena,\” I say grinning.
\“What did you do, google Houdini\’s phrase?\”

\n\n\“No, I didn\’t!\” Serena declares opening her eyes wide and staring at me.

\n\nI stand up more quickly than I anticipated.
\“Listen Serena, it\’s fine if you looked it up, but just be honest.
I mean, come on, you don’t really expect me to believe this is real,\” I say to her still good naturedly.

\n\n\“Rose I swear I didn\’t. I don\’t even know what it\’s saying.\”

\n\n\“He\’s saying the full secret phrase, \“Rosabel, Believe,\” I say \‘he\’ as if Harry Houdini really is the culprit behind the ruse.

\n\n\“Well, I didn\’t even know that. I swear,\” she looks up at me innocently.

\n\n\“No of course I believe you,\” I reply.
\“But could that mean I was pushing it and I didn\’t realize it? Because come on Serena I love our weekly hangouts,
but this stuff isn\’t real.\”

\n\n\“Maybe you need to believe a little more,\” she says to me.
\“They are right there, on the other side waiting to converse with us, and if you don\’t believe it, you\’ll never be able to hear it!\”

\n\nI looked at my faithful friend in awe.
I hoped we\’d continue our Ouija Wine Wednesdays and that I never rubbed off on her, only the other way around.
        </item>
        <item>

My town of Burning, South Carolina had two unspoken rules: go to church on Sunday and don\'t touch The Dead Tree.
On a Halloween night, my gran revealed our tiny town\’s local legend.
My parents were at some party and she had been tasked with taking me trick o\’ treating.
We were out later than I was allowed to be and Gran grabbed my hand leading the way home.

\n\nI was annoyed.
I couldn\’t see the beautiful colors of the crunchy leaves and my princess costume had turned more uncomfortable than cute.
The tiara was too tight and my shoes too big.
My mamma had warned me of this when I picked out the costume, and I was determined to make it home without any complaints.

\n\n\“Piper, you must listen to me carefully,\” my gran\’s voice was firm, an abrupt change from how it had been a minute ago.

\n\n\“What is it, gran?\” I looked up, unable to make out her expression in the dark night.

\n\n\“Your parents would rather me not tell you this but it\’s something you must know,
something you must be warned of,\” Gran\’s hand tightened around mine. \“Have you heard the story of The Dead Tree?\”

\n\nI rolled my eyes.

\n\n\“Of course I have.
Some older kids at school told me about it, they wanted to scare me,\” I sniffed, unbothered.

\n\n\“What exactly did they tell you?\” She stopped us.
We were in front of her house, and she ushered me to the white bench in the garden.
The porch light illuminated her face.
My hands started to sweat.
Even at nine years old I could tell this conversation meant something.

\n\n\“Um, they said that 106 years ago some witch put a curse on an old tree in the abandoned field.
They said the 100th person to touch it like dies or something?\” I rushed out.

\n\n\“The 113th person to touch it, Piper.
That\’s important.
That\’s the most crucial thing, honey.
The 113th person,\” her blue eyes were wide and she leaned closer to me.

\n\n\“Gran, you don\’t actually believe this, um, tale, right?\” I asked her, pulling off my tiara,
wincing when a few strands of my red hair came with it.

\n\nShe grabbed both of my hands.

\n\n\“Piper, this isn\’t some campfire story meant to keep kids in bed at night.
This story is real,\” her hands started to shake.

\n\n\“Gran, are you trying to scare me? Is this some Halloween prank?\” I tilted my head, trying not to let her see how much this was
frightening me.

\n\n\“No, I promise on your late grandad, my handsome George,\” she squeezed my hands.
This was what made me accept she wasn\’t joking.

\n\nMy gran never spoke of my dead grandpa.

\n\n\“Piper, exactly 106 years ago a woman by the name of Willa was accused of witchcraft.
The town sentenced her to be hung.
Before she was killed she cursed the tree and the townspeople of Burning,\” Gran avoided my eyes and looked down her dark street.

\n\n\“Willa declared that the 113th person to touch the tree where she had been sentenced to hang would meet a fate worse than death.\”
She paused, finally meeting my eyes.

\n\n\“Why would you believe all this, Gran?\”

\n\n\“When I was older than you, three days before my 17th birthday, I touched The Dead Tree. Burning High School
has a tradition where two seniors take two juniors to touch it, one boy and one girl.
I wasn\’t afraid, I was excited.
Everyone knew that if you went through with it, you were guaranteed to win prom queen and king.\”
My gran shook her head, a sad smile on her face.

\n\n\“You did it then? Didn\’t you?\” I remembered her showing me her prom queen sash, she kept it in a dusty box in the basement.

\n\n\“Yes, I did,\” Gran shivered.

\n\n\“You\’re fine though, Gran! The story is just that, a story,\” I nodded my head,
standing from the bench, wanting to go inside to organize my candy.

\n\n\“Honey, please listen to me,\” she grabbed my hand, spinning me around to face her.
\“When I touched that tree I felt something.
Not with my hands.
But deep down in my bones.
I could feel the black magic surging through that tree, the witch\’s enchantment flowing through my body, demanding me to be hers,\”
Gran\’s eyes were scaring me, her usual baby blues were turning dark.

\n\n\“Gran, you\’re fine.
You have a happy life!\" I argued.

\n\n\“Yes, because I wasn\’t the 113th person to touch the tree,\” she gripped my hands too tight.

\n\n\“Ow, you\’re hurting me!\” I screamed.

\n\nShe let go and I backed away from her.

\n\n\“I\’m sorry sweetheart.
Just please promise me, if you are the unlucky girl to be chosen,
do not go. Do not touch Willa\’s Tree.
I beg you. You can refuse, a lot of people do. Please don\’t do that to your parents.
Please don\’t do that to yourself,\” her eyes were back to normal and I wondered if I had imagined it.

\n\n\“I promise, Gran. I won\’t touch that dumb tree,\” I told her and darted into her house.

\n\nI didn\'t come out of her spare bedroom until my parents came to pick me up.

\n\nThe crunchy yellow grass made satisfying sounds under my black boots.
I was doing the exact thing my Gran had asked me not to do all those years ago.
But it didn\’t matter, Gran was no longer around, and that Halloween story was stupid.

\n\nMagic didn\’t exist.

\n\nI took a swig from the bottle Ben brought.

\n\nBesides, it wasn\’t like I was technically ignoring her wishes. I wasn\’t popular like Gran had been, far from it.
My friends and I didn\’t care what people think.
They probably didn\’t even know about our town\’s stupid legend.
We used the field to party.

\n\n\“Why the frown, Piper?\” Ben asked me, stealing his bottle back and chugging from it.
His brown eyes studied my face making me blush.

\n\n\“Hey, guys! Hurry up!\” Our friend, Amelia yelled at us.
Our friend group was gathered around The Dead Tree, closer to it than I was comfortable with.

\n\nEven if it was just some silly story.

\n\n\“Let\’s go join in the Halloween festivities,\” Ben took my hand, winking at me.

\n\n\“Now that everyone\’s here we can start the game,\” Amelia said, smiling at us, her short black hair barely noticeable in the dark.
I turned on my phone\’s flashlight pointing it at her.
She nodded at me, thankful for her spotlight.

\n\n\“We\’re all going to take turns touching The Dead Tree,\” Amelia\’s dark eyes flashed around the circle.

\n\nMy heart was on the ground.
I could no longer feel it beating in my chest.

\n\n\“That\’s stupid, Amelia.
I don\’t want to play some kid\’s game,\” I said once I could feel my heartbeat again.

\n\n\“Scared, Piper?\” Amelia mocked me for my reluctance.

\n\n\“No, I just don\’t put much stock into Burning\’s legends,\” I turned off my phone\’s light and crossed my arms.

\n\n\“I\’ll touch the dumb tree,\” Ben shrugged.
He strode confidently and placed his hand on the peeling bark.

\n\nBen immediately crumpled to the ground.

\n\n\“Ben!\” I screamed and rushed forward to help him.

\n\n\“Someone call 911!\” Ben\’s best friend, Rowan shouted.

\n\nBefore I could touch him, I noticed Ben was shaking.

\n\nFrom laughter.

\n\n\“Ben! That was so not funny,\” I chastised him as he gracefully stood and put his arm around me.

\n\n\“Oh, come on, babe,\” he kissed me on the cheek.
\“You think I\’m cute even when I\’m annoying,\” Ben teased me.

\n\n\“Hm,\” I gave him a non-answer, still mad I had been tricked.
Then Rowan did an impersonation of Ben falling and I was glad I wasn\’t the butt of the joke.

\n\n\“You\’re right, it\’s just some dumb legend,\” I said, walking to the tree.
It didn\’t look as menacing as before.
I paused right before I placed my hand on it.
An odd sensation came over me. I could no longer hear my friends.
I couldn\'t hear anything.
I tried to turn back, but an invisible force was keeping me rooted at the spot.

\n\nIt was just me staring at The Dead Tree.
Almost like we were fighting, our energies grappling for the upper hand.
Tears were streaming down my face and I could feel sweat running down my back.
Something or someone wanted me to give up.

\n\nI wouldn\’t, I couldn\’t.

\n\nIt felt like hours, time meant nothing on this endless night.
I was just standing there, a battle taking place in my mind.
Once I was sure I couldn\’t take it anymore, the feeling stopped as suddenly as it had started.
My hearing came back, painfully pulsing in my ears.

\n\nThen I felt two hands on my back.
They violently pushed me into the tree and I caught myself on the rough bark.

\n\nI could feel warm blood gushing down my hands. It made interesting patterns on my arm.

\n\nNormal cuts didn\’t bleed like that.

\n\nIt spelled out,

\n\n1 1 3

\n\nQueasy, I turned away from the tree. The scene I was met with was like a punch in the gut.
I was looking at my friends and… and myself.
They were laughing, dancing, and partying.
I was doing all those things.

\n\nBut how was that possible? I was here.

\n\nAmelia walked up to me and I tried to speak to her.

\n\nBut my words were lost in the wind like I hadn\’t even spoken them. She touched… she touched me.
I felt the palm of her cool fingers on me.

\n\nAfter an hour of this torture, they all turned to leave.

\n\nEven me.

\n\nOr the me I was staring at.

\n\nI willed my feet to move, to follow them, but I was paralyzed.

\n\nThe new me looked back with an awful grin on her face. She waved at me, her arm reminding me of a branch in the breeze.

That\’s when I realized The Dead Tree had a new prisoner.
        </item>
        <item>

People laugh about it all the time now.
Even after I explain the reasoning for it they will sit in silence for a moment,
digesting the sweet but bitter reality of it and then they laugh some more.
I have always had a keen eye for good people and no-one has ever judged me for anything
in my life other than myself but this part of my home always came with an explanation.
My family played Yacht when I was a kid instead of Yahtzee.
We were poor as any normal middle class adult could see, but as kids we didn\’t know this at all.
My parents did everything to protect the façade that we were like everyone else as evidenced by them
carefully constructing their words with \“let\’s play board games\” without actually naming the games.
My mother carefully filled the ketchup jar (same jar my entire life) with packages she saved from fast food establishments.
And at Christmas they never got gifts for each other and told us it was family tradition that us kids all receive one gift
\“to appreciate family time more.\”

\n\nWe were never allowed to have friends over and my parents instilled a very strong assertion in us on valuing privacy.
\"Don\'t be telling everyone our familia business\" Mom would say.
\"We don\'t the entire neighborhood mirando our life inside.\"

\n\nWe respected their rules because they raised us that way.
Strict and family oriented Hispanics is what we were.
My mother worked hard to keep us proper and never made it unclear when we stepped out of line.
And we never questioned it, all three of us and one year apart each,
drenched in innocence and a childlike trustworthy demeanor we never thought for a moment that any of the tiny details of our lives
was in fact carefully constructed to hide us from the truth.
And the truth was that we were poor, very poor.
But it wasn\’t until we became older that we really understood the intensity with which our parents protected this secret.
My favorite tradition was game night.
This was before cell phones, pre internet, pre pagers, even cable was for the elite.
So game night was my favorite night of the week.
I loved all the games, card games, dice games, trivia games.
I had become a master at them all.
I was the family game night champion.
If we were on teams I already had a system for who I wanted on my team,
I learned math quickly by playing our dice games and game night was an astute teacher in all things negotiating.

\n\nBut it wasn\'t until I went to visit my friend Javier at 16 that I learned my family was different.

\n\n\"You wanna play a game?\" Javier reached up into his closet to show me his families display of board games.

I instantly felt an electric pulse shake through my body.
Did I want a play a game? Of course I wanted to play a game! I was always competing with Javier in everything at school,
soccer at lunch, spelling bee contests in elementary school, girls attention and teachers grades.
And as much as I hated to admit it, Javier was better than me in a lot of ways.
\n\nBut the stars were aligned different today, because today I was gonna kick Javier\'s ass in whatever board game he wanted to play.

Then, something happened…

\n\nI was about to yell yes when I began to look at the board games.
They were a lot like the board games I knew from home but slightly different.
Yacht was called Yahtzee, Moneyopoly was Monopoly and Tumbling Blocks was called Jenga.
I was confused.

\n\nI giggled in confusion, \"what\'s wrong with your games?\"

\n\nJavier looked over at me and then quickly back at his closet.

\"What do you mean?\"

\n\nI stood there for a moment to digest what was happening.
What did I mean? And then the truth washed into my mind like a hurricane entering a town, ready to demolish.

\"Nothing, never mind, lets play.\"

\n\nWe played \'Yahtzee\'.
Everything was the same as our game at home except for the title.
And I still beat Javier, but the game went quietly.
I tiptoed into the game and wasn\'t my usual arrogant self when I rolled the dice with my new found knowledge
that we had grown up with second rate copy cat board games.
We had a smaller home as Javier which never really sparked anything in my mind,
but this display of board games,
this display of superiority washed over my entire childhood and
I realized in that moment that this was the moment my parents had wanted to protect us from.
I suddenly felt inferior in all matters of the world to Javier.

\n\nI went home that night and argued with my mom over what she made for dinner.

\n\n\"What is wrong with you tonight Miguel?\"

\n\nI didn\'t tell her about the board game or how they had a game called Yahtzee and not Yacht.
I understood now why she never took us shopping or why we had the one Christmas present rule.
Some may think that it was naivety but I simply never questioned the idea that she had been withholding a truth from us.
A small innocence in me had been washed away that day.

\n\nWhen we got older and our parents passed away, we joked about it.
About the times that mom made us play Yacht and Moneyopoly.
We joked about the family tradition of one Christmas present (which I still follow to this day).
I kept all the games after my siblings refused.
I cherish them,
I love them,
they are a reminder of the love of a family and the love of my parents who protected us from the materialistic world while still
providing us with all the love and family that we ever needed.
And now, when I have friends over I smile happily, pour a glass of wine and say, \"wanna play Yacht?\"
        </item>
        <item>

\“Why are you insisting we play a game when our friend has been missing for days?
Not to mention that your little sister is missing as well,\” said Jona frustrated that Jinórilie didn\’t seem fazed by the current events.

\n\n\“I just want to play, is all.
It\’s…um, my coping mechanism.
I know my sister is missing, but what can I do? There are police searching for her everywhere.
As for Derihia, he\’s probably at his girlfriend\’s,\” Jinorilie stood with the controller in his hand, extending it over to Jona.

\n\nJona slapped the controller out of his hand, stood up from the beanbag he had been sitting on, and walked out of Jinórilie\’s game room.

\n\nDerihia and Jinórilie had been friends since pre-school and neighbors. Both their moms worked as nurses in the local hospital.
They worked mainly nightshifts, so their children were under the care of babysitters together.
Derihia\’s father worked in construction where he died of a heart attack,
while Jinorilie\’s father was a lawyer who had disappeared in the middle of the night.
He had told his wife that he was going out for a smoke—that was midnight.
What Tabilia, Jinorilie\’s mother, found strange was that the game room smelled of cigarettes, but she didn\’t put two and two together.

\n\nJinórilie sat back on his gaming chair and continued playing.
He played well into the night until his mother walked in.

\n\n\“Jinórilie lights out,\” said Tabilia reaching for the lights on the wall.

\n\n\“Mom, not yet. I\’m almost done,\” said Jinórilie trying to achieve the top score in his game.


\n\nTabilia went to her room, unloaded her work gear, and then entered her private bathroom to shower.
She was trying not to think of her circumstances.
Her baby daughter had been missing now for a month and her husband had walked out on them over a year ago.
She missed work for two weeks straight, frantically looking for her daughter, even getting in the way of the police.
The police told Tabilia to go home and resume her life and that they would handle everything.
She couldn\’t stay home and just wait, so she returned to work.
She had a timeline in her office of the events that leadup to the disappearance of her five-year-old Lulayca.
She knew that the babysitter said that Lulayca never went outside.
Jazrial had locked all the doors from the inside.
Jazrial, the babysitter, had been told that Lulayca wanted to play a videogame with Jinórilie,
so she let her go into the game room while she went off to wash dishes. Later that evening,
Jinórilie went off to sleep; Jazrial thought that Lulayca was still in the game room, perhaps asleep.
She went in looking for her, but she was nowhere to be found.
Jazrial awoke Jinórilie asking him if he knew where his sister was, and he said that last he\’d seen her, she was in the game room asleep.

\n\nTabilia also remembered that her husband had said he was going outside for a smoke but never returned.
She remembered that when she walked into the game room looking for him, it smelled faintly of cigarette smoke, but he was nowhere in sight.
She had gone outside looking for him and going into the shed where he usually went, but he was nowhere to be found.

\n\nAfter bathing, she went to see if Jinórilie was in his room.
She found him getting ready for bed, so she walked into his room.

\n\n\“Are you fine with what\’s going on?\” asked Tabilia looking down at her hands while making folds on her nightgown,
her voice trembling a bit.

\n\n\“Sure, what\’s up?\” said Jinórilie as he put away the game controllers in his closet on a
shelf so no one could play unless he invited them.

\n\n\“Aren\’t you the least bit worried about Lulayca? She\’s only five years old, and she\’s somewhere alone,\” Tabilia cried as she spoke,
trying to keep calm and not have another explosive conversation with her son.

\n\n\“It is what it is.
She\’s probably with dad somewhere,\” he casually said as he leaned on his dresser while biting into an apple.

\n\n\“What about your friend Derihia? Have you heard anything?
Did I tell you that his mother was rushed to the hospital the other day suffering from a heart attack?\”
said Tabilia looking up at him with tears still streaming from her eyes.

\n\n\“I know, ma, you already told me several times,\” he said, tossing his apple into a bin.

\n\n\“How can you take these disappearances so calmly? I\’m here losing my mind, and you are unfazed,\”
she said, raising her voice with every word.

\n\n\“What do you want me to say or do? I don\’t know the first thing about search and rescue,
and perhaps those people don\’t want to be found,\” said Jinórilie rolling his eyes.

\n\n\“You mean to tell me that Lulayca doesn\’t want to be found? That she doesn\’t want to be with me, her mother,
the only person she has in the world aside from you?\” She rose from the bed where she had sat,
looking for some sympathy from her son but finding none.
Tabilia ran her fingers through her hair and then turned to face her son.

\n\n\“I suggest you start acting sympathetic because you could be considered guilty.
You were the last seen with Lulayca and Derihia.
Come to think of it, you were asleep in the game room when your father went missing as well,\” she spoke at first without thinking,
just to give him a jolt of sympathy, but it led her down a path that she didn\’t know existed.

\n\nShe walked out furious and headed to her room.
Tabilia managed to call the head detective on the search for her daughter before she went to sleep.
Sleep wasn\’t her friend nowadays.
She simply rested her head on the pillow thinking about her daughter and husband.
Sleep would eventually overcome her with dreams of her family altogether, dreams that once she awoke turned into nightmares.

\n\nDetective Gamilio brought her up to speed on the search,
informing her that there were no leads and that everyone in the neighborhood had confirmed that there wasn\’t any activity the night
Lulayca went missing.
The doors had been locked by Jazriel, and she clearly saw Lulayca enter the game room.
He suggested bringing Jinórilie back in for questioning and she agreed.

\n\nJinórilie heard the entire conversation before going back to his room to think about what was his next move.
Tired from playing video games all day he retreated to his room to sleep.


\n\nSleep eventually overcame Tabilia, but this dream wasn\’t normal.
In the dream, she was definitely in her house, but she kept hearing her daughter and husband screaming for help.
She searched, but every step she took led her back to the game room.
Awaking with a scream she found herself covered in sweat and trembling.
Sleep was no comfort so she started her day at 4 am only having slept 3 hours.

\n\nTabilia searched the game room from top to bottom, knowing that Jinórilie wouldn’t awake so early.
She felt the walls searching to see if the walls had been disrupted somehow.
She looked under the sofa and around the love seat for clues.
Tabilia removed all the cushions, looking, searching for any sign that could help find her family.
She put everything back before Jinórilie would awake and settled in the kitchen prepping for breakfast.

\n\nOn this day Tabilia had called off work to take Jinórilie to the precinct for more questioning.
His demeanor seemed too calm for a teenager that is missing his younger sister and his father not to mention his best friend.
Something was wrong and Tabilia wanted to get to the bottom of it.

\n\nJinórilie was awakened before he could even invite his mother to a game.

\n\n\“Get up. We have to go somewhere,\” Tabilia said as she walked past Jinórilie\’s room.

\n\nJinórilie arose without having his little sister come in screaming for him to wake up instead it was his mother. He missed his girlfriend,
it seemed that the mornings were when he thought of her the most.
Many nights she would sneak into his room and spend the night without his parents knowing.
One night, as Jinórilie remembered,
he was helping Kainara, his girlfriend, climb out the window when he heard his father in a heated conversation with someone on the phone.
Normally, Kainara would stay up until the sun rose, but this time she had decided to leave sooner.
It upset Jinórilie that she wanted to leave so badly, but eventually, he gave in and let her leave.
As she walked in the opposite direction from where his dad was talking Jinórilie managed to get closer to hear the conversation.

\n\n\“I don\’t care if you\’re pregnant, I am not leaving my family for you,\” Quinton said into the receiver
after blowing out some cigarette smoke.
The plume encircled his head in a halo.
Accidentally, his finger somehow hit the speaker button and Jinórilie heard the woman say, \“Kainara is here, I have to let you go.\”

\n\n\“What is Kainara doing there and so late at night?\” Quinton said as he smashed the discarded cigarette under his foot and did not bother
to silence the speaker.

\n\n\“She and Derihia have been dating lately.
She\’s been sleeping here for over a couple of weeks now.\”

\n\nJinórilie turned and went up the trellis and into his room; he had heard enough.
He recognized the voice to be Derihia\’s mother even before she mentioned his name.
That night Jinórilie decided to go play a game in the game room.
His father walked in telling him to go to sleep.

\n\n\“I can\’t sleep, must be pre-S.A.T jitters. Wanna play a game?\” Jinórilie extended the controller toward his father.
Quinton grabbed the controller and sat next to his son.

\n\nJinórilie knew of the powers of the controller and so started a horror game.
His father started the game and soon he was sweating up a storm.
He pulled out a cigarette and started to smoke not realizing that he had pushed the wrong buttons making him lose the game.
Suddenly, a whirlwind of dust came out of the controller and surrounded Quinton.
When the dust cleared Quinton was gone. Jinórilie picked up the dropped controller, turned off the game, and went to his room.
He knew that he needed to wait at least a year before he would play with Derihia.

\n\nA year later after having broken up with Kainara, Jinórilie invited Derihia over for a game.
Derihia felt horrible for sleeping with his best friend\'s girlfriend and so had decided to come clean after so long.
Derihia arrived at Jinórilie\’s house and they quickly settled into the game room.
Derihia wanted to get the secret off his chest, but Jinórilie insisted they play a game before they spoke about anything so serious.
At one point Jinórilie thought that he\’d lose to Derihia, but quickly the game turned in his favor and Derihia lost.
Once again a whirlwind of dust came out of the controller and enveloped Derihia.

\n\nLulayca had been such a bother to Jinórilie that he decided on getting rid of her as well.


\n\nWhen Jinórilie exited his room he smelled the aroma of sweet bread and pancakes.
He rushed over to the kitchen to find his mother at the kitchen table waiting for him.
His plate was in front of her facing the empty seat.

\n\n\“Why are you here? You don\’t work today?\” Jinórilie said pulling the chair out to sit in front of his mother.

\n\n\“I told you that we have to go somewhere,\” Tabilia said trying to eat as calmly as possible.

\n\n\“Okay, but where?\” Jinórilie said looking straight at his mother.

\n\n\“To the precinct.
Detective Gamilio wants to ask you some questions,\” Tabilia said, swallowing hard on her pancakes.

\n\n\“Can we play a game before we leave? It\’ll be a quick game.\”

\n\n\“You know very well that I don’t waste time on those games.
Now hurry up we need to leave,\” she arose dumping the rest of her food into the sink and down the garbage disposal.


\n\nDetective Gamilio told Tabilia to leave Jinórilie there and she would be called when they were done.
Jinórilie thought that his mother would wait for him until he was done, but instead, she left to search his bedroom for clues.

\n\nOnce back home Tabilia rushed to her son\’s bedroom.
There she found a bag of weed, which she didn\’t even know that her son was getting high.
What else could he be into? thought Tabilia.
She went to enter his bathroom when suddenly the doorbell rang; it was the police.
They had issued a search warrant and were going to do it while Jinórilie was being questioned.
Tabilia welcomed the help.
They searched his room and found the many controllers in his closet, several porn magazines, and a bent-over spoon with burns on the bottom.
Tabilia knew exactly what it was for.

\n\nWhile the search was being done one of the officers accidentally dropped the controller breaking it into two pieces.

\n\n\“It\’s okay, don\’t worry he has enough controllers,\” Tabilia said worried as to what her son had done.
        </item>

        <item>

Recent events, namely the destruction of the Temple, have freed the village of Jebus from the tyranny of its ancient dictums.

\n\nAll Truth belongs to Illumeos.

\n\nThough half dead, and decrepit, the law of Ilumeos was immortal–an undead vampire.
Like the temple from which its oppressive principles were espoused,
The Standard towered over the people through the ages,
casting a shadow with its antiquated axioms, but never sheltering them.
It was a vampire reigning from his cursed castle,
feeding on the inhabitants–slowly siphoning away their very souls.

\n\n\“Who shall we praise?\” They ask.

\n\nWho can the people of Jebus thank, for piercing the heart of that ancient oppressor,
and for toppling his canvas castle? My pride would have me speak my own name,
for it was I who set the tent ablaze, and I, who shattered the ordinances of injustice inscribed in that hideous clay–The Standard.
But I am humble, and when I hear the inquiries of families on the street, or in my shop, I bridle my tongue.
I did not tear down one temple, just to raise another.

\n\n\“Praise whom you wish,\” I say, as I gesture to my wares \“now, you may choose your gods freely.\”

\n\nThe images on my table are carved by my own hands, mostly from the oak of the Temple.
Fragments of that dethroned carcass fashioned into the preferences of each patron.
It\’s my way of distancing myself from my heritage.
I am a Tusan, the blood of the Illumeos priests courses through my veins; I share their wheat-gold eyes.
But I\’ve set my hands to better work,
no longer complict in their oppression and I am fortunate to have a thriving business during these transitional times.
Many struggle to earn wages, men beg in the streets for a mere morsel to bring home to their children.

\n\nBut our poverty is temporary–growing pains.
Jebus will thrive in our new freedom.

\n\nThere is no denying the land was prosperous before.
Thousands journeyed to our city to drink from the vine of its produce–but they couldn\’t have known about The Standard, or else,
they wouldn\’t have come so far.
But their numbers are few now, even famished travelers refuse to sojourn here.
Word mustn\’t travel fast–but it will.
The tenets are lost to the flame.
Now that our chains are broken, and that symbol of tyranny reduced to a heap of wood and ash, foreigners will flock here.
The Free City, they\’ll call it.

\n\nThe Voice of Illumeos shall break the bonds.

\n\nA shoeless man hopped across the sun-baked streets and ducked beneath the shade of my tent.

\n\n\“Anything I can offer you, good sir?\” I gestured to my table.

\n\nA beautiful young woman, with an infant wrapped against her chest in a tattered grey scarf, trailed behind him.
Craning my neck to see past the collection of ornate rugs displayed in my neighbor\’s stall,
I followed the visitor\’s eyes to a tent further down the street–sandals dangled from cords in pairs.
My tent was nothing more than brief respite for his burning feet.
I tried anyway.

\n\n\“I have pre-fashioned idols,\” I gestured to a dozen of the most popular gods: Creshon, Saryth, Grii,
Shetemoc, \“but,\" I said, pausing for effect, \“I can also create whatever god you like.\”

\n\nAnd there it was–a glimmer in his eye.
He glanced down at the unformed oak blocks, and the whittling blade I\’d strategically posed against it.
I said nothing, letting his mind do what it could never do in years past. Wander.

\n\n\“You do custom work?\”

\n\nI grinned, \“I do.
Anything you like.
And I don\’t just do wood, I do hammered work as well.
Bronze mostly, but I can do whatever you want.\”

\n\n\“No,\” the man nodded, \“wood is good.”

\n\nI pretended to drink from my wineskin to hide my smile, whittling was the fastest for me.
Except for the most intricate requests, I could finish an idol carving in a couple days.

\n\n\“Do you have a specific god in mind, or something new?\”

\n\n\“Jelyph,\” the woman touched his shoulder, \“we can\’t afford this right now.
Jabi needs medicine. You need shoes.\”

\n\nThe man pulled away from her touch. \“Perhaps if we had a god that didn\’t curse us, we\’d have what we needed.\”

\n\nShe opened her mouth to speak, but shut it when he shot her a look–an unspoken threat that contained a whole book of words.
She tried to hide it, but I caught a subtle quiver of her lips before she turned away, looking out into the streets.

\n\n\“I\’ve heard about household gods,\” the man said,
as he lifted a block of unformed wood from my table, \“folks are becoming the priests of their own houses,
applying their own hard-won wisdom to craft new laws.\”

\n\nI nodded. \“The liberation of the soul.\”

\n\n\“How does this work?\” the man said, handing me the block.
“Do I just tell you what I want the design to be, and then you carve it up?\”

\n\n\“Essentially,\” I said, \“we will work together on the design.
The purchase of one household idol, will come with a few small modifications, should it not be to your liking.\”

\n\n\“And the tenets?\”

\n\n\“Entirely up to you.\” I exchanged the unformed block for one of my more popular idols,
one that I judged the man would appreciate–a sculpture I\’d carved especially well.
\“My only job, Jelyph, is to help you visualize your own gods.\” I turned the object toward him.
\“Take Grii for example, she is the god of a distant southern tribe who\’s praised for her respect of men.
She represents the humble acceptance of our born role.
\” I pointed to six oversized breasts I\’d expertly carved to represent her role as a mother, then to my depiction of her legs spread.
\“She knows her place.
A thing the Grishon people of the south value.
Kings are born to rule, slaves to serve, and women to please.\”

\n\nAt the word, slave, his expression dimmed.
I\’d set the hook, but as I tried pulling him in I lost him with the mention of servitude, perhaps he was once a servant.
But I recovered.

\n\n\“But that\’s the beauty of freedom, we do not need to take the bad with the good.\” I clapped my hands together.
\“Tell me, what kind of god would you want to worship?
What do you believe are the commandments of life? What should the rewards of obedience to those tenets be?\”

\n\nAgain, that glimmer in his eye. I\’d given him authority–asked him what the rewards should be.
By asking the question, I\’d made a god out of his own appetite–that compass of the heart,
he had never been allowed to follow under the yoke of Illumeos oppression.

\n\nIt worked every time.

\n\nWhen he left my tent, he did not stop at the stall with the sandals, my custom idols cost a month\’s wages.
But in a few days, I\’d have his household god, Jelyphias,
depicted exactly as he envisioned–a young girl on her knees, wrists bound, leash attached at her throat, and a face downturned in agony.
He\’d leave with a clean conscience, I\’d send him away justified by his own god.
In that respect, I was a sort of redeemer, a priest of many deities.

\n\nTheir compass was their craving. Northless.

\n\nAutumn should have been upon us by now, but the sun continued to burn cloudlessly for the next few weeks. One night,
as I turned-in to sleep, I found my wineskin empty, so I filled it with water from my cistern, which was unusually shallow.
The next day, I woke before dawn to draw from the village well before the crowds arrived.
My path to the city cut through an olive orchard, that I was surprised to see had not yet flowered.
One of the trees–contorted like an old man–bent into my path between the rows. For a moment,
it seemed to me a beggar, hunched and reaching out for a sip from my flask.

\n\n\“What\’s wrong with you?\” I asked aloud.
I knelt and ran my hands through the soil.
It was like sand in my palm, dry and coarse.

\n\nI knew then, that my tent would soon be filled with farmers, people seeking to fashion for themselves gods of
the harvest, or perhaps a new rain deity,
who does not demand anything from his worshippers, but showers the land freely, where men can reap even if they do not sow.

\n\nThe first of these farmers to commission me required an idol of hammered bronze–a bowl, broad, and deep.
\“Deep\”, he said, \“to hold the fruit of every man\’s labor, but broad, so that all men\'s hands could draw from it at the same time.\”

\n\nHe named his god, Osheq, for he said, \“Why should one man beg for dust, when another eats merrily from his figs?\”

\n\nTwiddle the thumbs, and hunger will pierce the stomach.

\n\nBy the end of the week, my workload was full.
I\’d been commissioned for as many jobs as I could handle,
but I did not like turning away anyone, especially those who sought, like I did, to free themselves from The Standard.
So, I raised my prices.
When that didn\’t slow the requests, I raised them again.
Several inquirers left unhappy, feeling robbed by my inflated rates, but what was I to do? I had no apprentice,
that I should delegate my workload. My commissions only slowed, they did not cease.

\n\nI realized then, that people will pay any sum to feel free to pursue what they love.
My idols had redeemed the people of Jebus from The Standard, not to it, like so many felt compelled to do in the days of Illumeos.
Eventually, I\’d finished all the idols, both whittled and forged, but I felt no need to lower my prices,
people continued to commission my work.

\n\nWhen the sandstorm came, destroying the pomegranates, and apples, and turning the wells to mud, the customers came. In droves.

\n\nTo placate the masses, I offered my pre-fashioned idols at a discount.
But the droughts, and sand storms, and waning tourism, had caused enough disruption in the lives of the people of Jebus to unsettle them.
They feared that they might break the laws, even of the foreign gods, and would not risk incurring any more wrath.
They wanted gods of their own, gods that did not condemn their actions, but rewarded them. God’s who supported them.

\n\nI did my best to keep up with demand.

\n\n\“Crime is on the rise.\” They say.

\n\nAgain, just growing pains.
It is only temporary.
What do you expect from a people who\’d been oppressed,
unable to express themselves or their desires? The people of Jebus were caged lions, majestic, beautiful creatures.
Now that they were released, it is only natural that they would act violently for that brief moment before they recognize their freedom,
and sprint gratefully into the wild.

\n\nCrime is on the rise.
What is crime? Crimes against Illumeos–who is that? Crimes against The Standard–what is that? Did not the Clay itself say,
Where there is no Dictum, there is no debt?

\n\nAll of it is ash now.

\n\nCrime is relative.
The very word is a device employed by the zealots–the Illumeos troglodytes who treat
The Standard like it wasn\’t written by humans who squat and shit like everyone else.

\n\nAll Truth belongs to Illumeos.

\n\nMy neighbor\’s cart was robbed in the night. Fortunately for me, all my wares fit easily in my sack;
I bring them home every evening.
But each of his rugs represent months, sometimes years, of labor.
I\’d feel for him, perhaps even give generously to him, if he wasn\’t an Illumeos sympathizer.
Now that my craftsmanship is coveted across all Jebus, I could fill two of his hands with coin from my coffer, and still want for nothing.
But where is his lesson in that?

\n\n\“It\’s a shame,\” I said, draping a wet scarf over my neck. \“you didn\’t deserve this.\”

\n\nBut he did.

\n\n\“We\’re not staying here.\” Abris said, as he rolled up the only rugs left behind by the thieves. \“Jebus isn\’t what it used to be.\”

\n\nI frowned, wondering what new temple he thought he’d found, that could cast a longer shadow than that of Illumeos. \“Where will you go?\”

\n\n\“Rezika has family in Nadil, out East.\” He bound the rugs together in twine and heaved them onto his shoulder.
\“We won\’t spend another day here.\”

\n\nI bowed. \“I am sorry my friend, perhaps you will find peace in Nadil,\” I offered my hand.
\“Peace and justice.\”

\n\nThe man turned toward me, but did not take my hand. His eyes glistened, defeated, then he said, \“What is justice?\”

\n\nI did not see Abris again, but I have no doubt he\’s happily conformed to the ideal and dogma of some new tyrant.
I did miss the shade his rugs cast on my tent during the morning blaze, but the sweat was a worthy sacrifice.
I felt freer with him gone, I could breathe.
Though he said nothing, I knew in his heart he judged me for my idols.
My carvings offended the rules of his precious Standard, and despite his silence on the matter,
I resented any man who threatened my autonomy.

\n\nThey covered their ears to his voice, their eyes to his light.

\n\nWhen the rains came, celebration erupted in the city.
It was the first festival since that day I scorched the tent.
Everyone had experienced the cruel effects of that long drought, so the shared suffering united us in our jubilation.
I was perhaps the most delighted of us all, for unity had arisen without conformity.
Without being compelled to a standard, we were propelled to each other.

\n\nHow proud I was of my people.

\n\nInspired, I called a gathering of the elders, the mightiest families in Jebus,
and requested that they declare the celebration a holiday, one that we all shared, and could hold annually–despite our various gods.

\n\n\“Rain, is rain,\” I said. \“despite the source. Can we not all rejoice in rain?\”

\n\n\“Celebration is hollow without thanksgiving.\” said the elder of the Tusan clan–my own clan.
\“To whom shall we be grateful?\”

\n\n\“It is on my behalf, that my god has blessed this city.\” said Beni, the father of the Benecians.
\“Let the celebration be held in my honor.\”

\n\n\“It is a sin against Toril,\” said another elder, \“to revere one day above another.\”

\n\n\“My grandchild was trampled in the commotion,\” spoke another man, \“this day is forever cursed to me and my clan.\”

\n\nTheir words did not discourage me, our solidarity would come with time.

\n\nThe cretin commits to his contradictions, the dullard, to his own devices.

\n\nThe families that embraced their new freedoms began to prosper more than others.
Everyone, great and small, who were capable of letting go of the Standard,
thrived in their hearts for they did not walk in shame.
I predicted that the golden days of Jebus were upon us.
Of course, there were rumors, of rivalries between the families, of anarchy in the streets,
but it is only the propaganda of bigots–men desperate to control the thoughts and actions of others.

\n\nThey cite the killings–men and woman found mutilated in the streets.
They delcare this the rule, rather than the exception,
but they are deceivers, perhaps even the very offenders,
who chop the innocent to pieces so they have some evidence to show.
But Jebus is becoming enlightened.
My kinsman are waking up.
We will not be tricked, we will not beg for the chains of Illumeos, or any god for that matter.

\n\nWe are free.
Jebus will thrive.

\n\nMy new apprentice had just handed me his lasted work–an oaken foot crushing the head of a bronze-skinned Prescian–when two young men,
head and shoulders taller than me, entered my tent.
They wore blue robes of many layers,trimmed in scarlet–the colors of the house Beni.
A gold chain drooped from one man\’s ear, to his nose–latched on both ends to bejewled piercings.

\n\n\“Good afternoon,\” I said, returning the idol to the boy\’s hand and shooing him away.
\“Anything I can offer you, good sirs?\”

\n\nThe men looked at each other and grinned.

\n\n\“A custom job,” one said, his voice was youthful, despite his size.

\n\n“I can do that.
What do you have in mind?\” I lifted a block from my table, my last piece of that toppled Temple.

\n\n\“We want a Benecian fist,\” the man with the gold chains said,
\“clenching the hair of a severed Tusan head.\”

\n\nBoth men laughed.

\n\nI swallowed, my wheat-gold eyes were decidedly Tusan.
\“I can surely craft anything you like.
But I should say that I\’ve raised my prices substantially.\”
I hoped this would deter the visitors, but the diamond crested ring of house Beni on his finger told me otherwise.

\n\n\“No,\” the man said. \“money is not a concern.\”

\n\n\“Well, what material would you like? I can do metal work, but my specialty is wood.\” I held up the block and smiled uncomfortably.

\n\nThe men looked to each other and laughed again, more heartily this time.

\n\n\“Do you have a time frame?\” I held up my whittling knife.
\“If you want wood, I can carve up just about any commission in less than a week, if it isn\’t too complex.\”

\n\n\“We\’ll need it today,\” the Benecian man said.

\n\nI chuckled. \“I\’m good, but complex or not, I can\'t make any god that fast.\”

The man smiled, \“No need,\” then his companion reached beneath his robes and drew a long curved sword, \“in Jebus, we make our own gods.\”
        </item>

        <item>
The morning of June 27th was clear and sunny, with the fresh warmth of a full-summer day; the flowers
were blossoming profusely and the grass was richly green. The people of the village began to gather in
the square, between the post office and the bank, around ten o\'clock; in some towns there were so many
people that the lottery took two days and had to be started on June 2th. but in this village, where there
were only about three hundred people, the whole lottery took less than two hours, so it could begin at ten
o\'clock in the morning and still be through in time to allow the villagers to get home for noon dinner.
The children assembled first, of course. School was recently over for the summer, and the feeling of
liberty sat uneasily on most of them; they tended to gather together quietly for a while before they broke
into boisterous play. and their talk was still of the classroom and the teacher, of books and reprimands.
Bobby Martin had already stuffed his pockets full of stones, and the other boys soon followed his
example, selecting the smoothest and roundest stones; Bobby and Harry Jones and Dickie Delacroix— the
villagers pronounced this name \"Dellacroy\"—eventually made a great pile of stones in one corner of the
square and guarded it against the raids of the other boys. The girls stood aside, talking among themselves,
looking over their shoulders at rolled in the dust or clung to the hands of their older brothers or sisters.
Soon the men began to gather. surveying their own children, speaking of planting and rain, tractors and
taxes. They stood together, away from the pile of stones in the corner, and their jokes were quiet and they
smiled rather than laughed. The women, wearing faded house dresses and sweaters, came shortly after
their menfolk. They greeted one another and exchanged bits of gossip as they went to join their husbands.
Soon the women, standing by their husbands, began to call to their children, and the children came
reluctantly, having to be called four or five times. Bobby Martin ducked under his mother\'s grasping hand
and ran, laughing, back to the pile of stones. His father spoke up sharply, and Bobby came quickly and
took his place between his father and his oldest brother.\n
The lottery was conducted—as were the square dances, the teen club, the Halloween program—by Mr.
Summers. who had time and energy to devote to civic activities. He was a round-faced, jovial man and he
ran the coal business, and people were sorry for him. because he had no children and his wife was a
scold. When he arrived in the square, carrying the black wooden box, there was a murmur of
conversation among the villagers, and he waved and called. \"Little late today, folks.\" The postmaster, Mr.
Graves, followed him, carrying a three- legged stool, and the stool was put in the center of the square and
Mr. Summers set the black box down on it. The villagers kept their distance, leaving a space between
themselves and the stool. and when Mr. Summers said, \"Some of you fellows want to give me a hand?\"
there was a hesitation before two men. Mr. Martin and his oldest son, Baxter. came forward to hold the
box steady on the stool while Mr. Summers stirred up the papers inside it.\n
The original paraphernalia for the lottery had been lost long ago, and the black box now resting on the
stool had been put into use even before Old Man Warner, the oldest man in town, was born. Mr.
Summers spoke frequently to the villagers about making a new box, but no one liked to upset even as
much tradition as was represented by the black box. There was a story that the present box had been
made with some pieces of the box that had preceded it, the one that had been constructed when the first
people settled down to make a village here. Every year, after the lottery, Mr. Summers began talking
again about a new box, but every year the subject was allowed to fade off without anything\'s being done.\n\n

The black box grew shabbier each year: by now it was no longer completely black but splintered badly
along one side to show the original wood color, and in some places faded or stained.
Mr. Martin and his oldest son, Baxter, held the black box securely on the stool until Mr. Summers had
stirred the papers thoroughly with his hand. Because so much of the ritual had been forgotten or
discarded, Mr. Summers had been successful in having slips of paper substituted for the chips of wood
that had been used for generations. Chips of wood, Mr. Summers had argued. had been all very well
when the village was tiny, but now that the population was more than three hundred and likely to keep on
growing, it was necessary to use something that would fit more easily into he black box. The night before
the lottery, Mr. Summers and Mr. Graves made up the slips of paper and put them in the box, and it was
then taken to the safe of Mr. Summers\' coal company and locked up until Mr. Summers was ready to take
it to the square next morning. The rest of the year, the box was put way, sometimes one place, sometimes
another; it had spent one year in Mr. Graves\'s barn and another year underfoot in the post office. and
sometimes it was set on a shelf in the Martin grocery and left there.\n
There was a great deal of fussing to be done before Mr. Summers declared the lottery open. There were
the lists to make up—of heads of families. heads of households in each family. members of each
household in each family. There was the proper swearing-in of Mr. Summers by the postmaster, as the
official of the lottery; at one time, some people remembered, there had been a recital of some sort,
performed by the official of the lottery, a perfunctory. tuneless chant that had been rattled off duly each
year; some people believed that the official of the lottery used to stand just so when he said or sang it,
others believed that he was supposed to walk among the people, but years and years ago this p3rt of the
ritual had been allowed to lapse. There had been, also, a ritual salute, which the official of the lottery had
had to use in addressing each person who came up to draw from the box, but this also had changed with
time, until now it was felt necessary only for the official to speak to each person approaching. Mr.
Summers was very good at all this; in his clean white shirt and blue jeans. with one hand resting
carelessly on the black box. he seemed very proper and important as he talked interminably to Mr. Graves
and the Martins.\n
Just as Mr. Summers finally left off talking and turned to the assembled villagers, Mrs. Hutchinson came
hurriedly along the path to the square, her sweater thrown over her shoulders, and slid into place in the
back of the crowd. \"Clean forgot what day it was,\" she said to Mrs. Delacroix, who stood next to her, and
they both laughed softly. \"Thought my old man was out back stacking wood,\" Mrs. Hutchinson went on.
\"and then I looked out the window and the kids was gone, and then I remembered it was the twenty
seventh and came a-running.\" She dried her hands on her apron, and Mrs. Delacroix said, \"You\'re in time,
though. They\'re still talking away up there.\"\n
Mrs. Hutchinson craned her neck to see through the crowd and found her husband and children standing
near the front. She tapped Mrs. Delacroix on the arm as a farewell and began to make her way through
the crowd. The people separated good-humoredly to let her through: two or three people said. in voices
just loud enough to be heard across the crowd, \"Here comes your, Missus, Hutchinson,\" and \"Bill, she
made it after all.\" Mrs. Hutchinson reached her husband, and Mr. Summers, who had been waiting, said
cheerfully. \"Thought we were going to have to get on without you, Tessie.\" Mrs. Hutchinson said.
grinning, \"Wouldn\'t have me leave m\'dishes in the sink, now, would you. Joe?,\" and soft laughter ran
through the crowd as the people stirred back into position after Mrs. Hutchinson\'s arrival.
\"Well, now.\" Mr. Summers said soberly, \"guess we better get started, get this over with, so\'s we can go
back to work. Anybody ain\'t here?\"\n\n

\"Dunbar.\" several people said. \"Dunbar. Dunbar.\"
Mr. Summers consulted his list. \"Clyde Dunbar.\" he said. \"That\'s right. He\'s broke his leg, hasn\'t he?
Who\'s drawing for him?"\n
\"Me. I guess,\" a woman said. and Mr. Summers turned to look at her. \"Wife draws for her husband.\" Mr.
Summers said. \"Don\'t you have a grown boy to do it for you, Janey?\" Although Mr. Summers and
everyone else in the village knew the answer perfectly well, it was the business of the official of the
lottery to ask such questions formally. Mr. Summers waited with an expression of polite interest while
Mrs. Dunbar answered.\n
\"Horace\'s not but sixteen vet.\" Mrs. Dunbar said regretfully. \"Guess I gotta fill in for the old man this
year.\"
\"Right.\" Sr. Summers said. He made a note on the list he was holding. Then he asked, \"Watson boy
drawing this year?\"
A tall boy in the crowd raised his hand. \"Here,\" he said. \"I\'m drawing for my mother and me.\" He blinked
his eyes nervously and ducked his head as several voices in the crowd said things like \"Good fellow,
lack.\" and \"Glad to see your mother\'s got a man to do it.\"
\"Well,\" Mr. Summers said, \"guess that\'s everyone. Old Man Warner make it?\"
\"Here,\" a voice said. and Mr. Summers nodded.\n
A sudden hush fell on the crowd as Mr. Summers cleared his throat and looked at the list. \"All ready?\" he
called. \"Now, I\'ll read the names—heads of families first—and the men come up and take a paper out of
the box. Keep the paper folded in your hand without looking at it until everyone has had a turn.
Everything clear?\"\n
The people had done it so many times that they only half listened to the directions: most of them were
quiet. wetting their lips. not looking around. Then Mr. Summers raised one hand high and said, \"Adams.\"
A man disengaged himself from the crowd and came forward. \"Hi. Steve.\" Mr. Summers said. and Mr.
Adams said. \"Hi. Joe.\" They grinned at one another humorlessly and nervously. Then Mr. Adams reached
into the black box and took out a folded paper. He held it firmly by one corner as he turned and went
hastily back to his place in the crowd. where he stood a little apart from his family. not looking down at
his hand.\n
\"Allen.\" Mr. Summers said. \"Anderson.... Bentham.\"
\"Seems like there's no time at all between lotteries any more.\" Mrs. Delacroix said to Mrs. Graves in the
back row.\n
\"Seems like we got through with the last one only last week.\"
\"Time sure goes fast.— Mrs. Graves said.\n\n


\"Clark.... Delacroix\"
\"There goes my old man.\" Mrs. Delacroix said. She held her breath while her husband went forward.
\"Dunbar,\" Mr. Summers said, and Mrs. Dunbar went steadily to the box while one of the women said.
\"Go on. Janey,\" and another said, \"There she goes.\"\/
\"We\'re next.\" Mrs. Graves said. She watched while Mr. Graves came around from the side of the box,
greeted Mr. Summers gravely and selected a slip of paper from the box. By now, all through the crowd
there were men holding the small folded papers in their large hand. turning them over and over nervously
Mrs. Dunbar and her two sons stood together, Mrs. Dunbar holding the slip of paper.
\"Harburt.... Hutchinson.\"
\"Get up there, Bill,\" Mrs. Hutchinson said. and the people near her laughed.
\"Jones.\"\n
\"They do say,\" Mr. Adams said to Old Man Warner, who stood next to him, \"that over in the north
village they\'re talking of giving up the lottery.\"
Old Man Warner snorted. "Pack of crazy fools,\" he said. \"Listening to the young folks, nothing\'s good
enough for them. Next thing you know, they\'ll be wanting to go back to living in caves, nobody work any
more, live hat way for a while. Used to be a saying about \'Lottery in June, corn be heavy soon.\' First thing
you know, we\'d all be eating stewed chickweed and acorns. There\'s always been a lottery,\" he added
petulantly. \"Bad enough to see young Joe Summers up there joking with everybody.\"
\"Some places have already quit lotteries.\" Mrs. Adams said.
\"Nothing but trouble in that,\" Old Man Warner said stoutly. \"Pack of young fools.\"
\"Martin.\" And Bobby Martin watched his father go forward. \"Overdyke.... Percy.\"
\"I wish they\'d hurry,\" Mrs. Dunbar said to her older son. \"I wish they\'d hurry.\"
\"They\'re almost through,\" her son said.
\"You get ready to run tell Dad,\" Mrs. Dunbar said.
Mr. Summers called his own name and then stepped forward precisely and selected a slip from the box.
Then he called, \"Warner.\"
\"Seventy-seventh year I been in the lottery,\" Old Man Warner said as he went through the crowd.
\"Seventy-seventh time.\"\n\n


\"Watson\" The tall boy came awkwardly through the crowd. Someone said, \"Don\'t be nervous, Jack,\" and
Mr. Summers said, \"Take your time, son.\"
\"Zanini.\"
After that, there was a long pause, a breathless pause, until Mr. Summers. holding his slip of paper in the
air, said, \"All right, fellows.\" For a minute, no one moved, and then all the slips of paper were opened.
Suddenly, all the women began to speak at once, saving. \"Who is it?,\" \"Who\'s got it?,\" \"Is it the
Dunbars?,\" \"Is it the Watsons?\" Then the voices began to say, \"It\'s Hutchinson. It\'s Bill,\" \"Bill
Hutchinson\'s got it.\"
\"Go tell your father,\" Mrs. Dunbar said to her older son.
People began to look around to see the Hutchinsons. Bill Hutchinson was standing quiet, staring down at
the paper in his hand. Suddenly. Tessie Hutchinson shouted to Mr. Summers. \"You didn\'t give him time
enough to take any paper he wanted. I saw you. It wasn\'t fair!\"
\"Be a good sport, Tessie.\" Mrs. Delacroix called, and Mrs. Graves said, \"All of us took the same chance.\"
\"Shut up, Tessie,\" Bill Hutchinson said.
\"Well, everyone,\" Mr. Summers said, \"that was done pretty fast, and now we\'ve got to be hurrying a little
more to get done in time.\" He consulted his next list. \"Bill,\" he said, \"you draw for the Hutchinson
family. You got any other households in the Hutchinsons?\"
\"There\'s Don and Eva,\" Mrs. Hutchinson yelled. \"Make them take their chance!\"
\"Daughters draw with their husbands\' families, Tessie,\" Mr. Summers said gently. \"You know that as
well as anyone else.\"
\"It wasn\'t fair,\" Tessie said.
\"I guess not, Joe.\" Bill Hutchinson said regretfully. \"My daughter draws with her husband\'s family; that\'s
only fair. And I\'ve got no other family except the kids.\"
\"Then, as far as drawing for families is concerned, it\'s you,\" Mr. Summers said in explanation, \"and as far
as drawing for households is concerned, that\'s you, too. Right?"
\"Right,\" Bill Hutchinson said.
\"How many kids, Bill?\" Mr. Summers asked formally.
\"Three,\" Bill Hutchinson said.
\"There\'s Bill, Jr., and Nancy, and little Dave. And Tessie and me.\"

\"All right, then,\" Mr. Summers said. \"Harry, you got their tickets back?\"
Mr. Graves nodded and held up the slips of paper. \"Put them in the box, then,\" Mr. Summers directed.
\"Take Bill\'s and put it in.\"
\"I think we ought to start over,\" Mrs. Hutchinson said, as quietly as she could. \"I tell you it wasn\'t fair.
You didn\'t give him time enough to choose. Everybody saw that.\"
Mr. Graves had selected the five slips and put them in the box. and he dropped all the papers but those
onto the ground. where the breeze caught them and lifted them off.
\"Listen, everybody,\" Mrs. Hutchinson was saying to the people around her.
\"Ready, Bill?\" Mr. Summers asked. and Bill Hutchinson, with one quick glance around at his wife and
children. nodded.
\"Remember,\" Mr. Summers said. \"take the slips and keep them folded until each person has taken one.
Harry, you help little Dave.\" Mr. Graves took the hand of the little boy, who came willingly with him up
to the box. \"Take a paper out of the box, Davy.\" Mr. Summers said. Davy put his hand into the box and
laughed. \"Take just one paper.\" Mr. Summers said. \"Harry, you hold it for him.\" Mr. Graves took the
child\'s hand and removed the folded paper from the tight fist and held it while little Dave stood next to
him and looked up at him wonderingly.
\"Nancy next,\" Mr. Summers said. Nancy was twelve, and her school friends breathed heavily as she went
forward switching her skirt, and took a slip daintily from the box \"Bill, Jr.,\" Mr. Summers said, and Billy,
his face red and his feet overlarge, near knocked the box over as he got a paper out. \"Tessie,\" Mr.
Summers said. She hesitated for a minute, looking around defiantly. and then set her lips and went up to
the box. She snatched a paper out and held it behind her.
\"Bill,\" Mr. Summers said, and Bill Hutchinson reached into the box and felt around, bringing his hand
out at last with the slip of paper in it.
The crowd was quiet. A girl whispered, \"I hope it\'s not Nancy,\" and the sound of the whisper reached the
edges of the crowd.
\"It\'s not the way it used to be.\" Old Man Warner said clearly. \"People ain\'t the way they used to be.\"
\"All right,\" Mr. Summers said. \"Open the papers. Harry, you open little Dave\'s.\"
Mr. Graves opened the slip of paper and there was a general sigh through the crowd as he held it up and
everyone could see that it was blank. Nancy and Bill. Jr.. opened theirs at the same time. and both
beamed and laughed. turning around to the crowd and holding their slips of paper above their heads.
\"Tessie,\" Mr. Summers said. There was a pause, and then Mr. Summers looked at Bill Hutchinson, and
Bill unfolded his paper and showed it. It was blank\n\n

\"It\'s Tessie,\" Mr. Summers said, and his voice was hushed. \"Show us her paper. Bill.\"
Bill Hutchinson went over to his wife and forced the slip of paper out of her hand. It had a black spot on
it, the black spot Mr. Summers had made the night before with the heavy pencil in the coal company
office. Bill Hutchinson held it up, and there was a stir in the crowd.
\"All right, folks.\" Mr. Summers said. \"Let\'s finish quickly.\"
Although the villagers had forgotten the ritual and lost the original black box, they still remembered to
use stones. The pile of stones the boys had made earlier was ready; there were stones on the ground with
the blowing scraps of paper that had come out of the box Delacroix selected a stone so large she had to
pick it up with both hands and turned to Mrs. Dunbar. \"Come on,\" she said. \"Hurry up.\"
Mr. Dunbar had small stones in both hands, and she said. gasping for breath. \"I can\'t run at all. You\'ll
have to go ahead and I\'ll catch up with you.\"
The children had stones already. And someone gave little Davy Hutchinson few pebbles.
Tessie Hutchinson was in the center of a cleared space by now, and she held her hands out desperately as
the villagers moved in on her. \"It isn\'t fair,\" she said. A stone hit her on the side of the head. Old Man
Warner was saying, \"Come on, come on, everyone.\" Steve Adams was in the front of the crowd of
villagers, with Mrs. Graves beside him.
\"It isn\'t fair, it isn\'t right,\" Mrs. Hutchinson screamed, and then they were upon her

                    </item>

    </string-array>

    <string name="Fiction_Title">

        Two Stubborn Women, Mysterium, The Dark Comes Closer, Spider-Man Pyjamas, Awakening, Dead Even, Ouija Wine Wednesdays, 113, Wanna play Yacht?, Play With Me, Household Gods
    </string>
    <string name="Fiction_Title_A">
        Fiction Title List
    </string>

</resources>