<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="story_names3">
        <item>Home Alone</item>
        <item>Not Smart Enough For A Smart Phone</item>
        <item>My One-Eyed Love</item>
        <item>A Thing About Hair!</item>
        <item>English Is A Pane</item>
        <item>I Hate Peanut Butter</item>
        <item>Time</item>
        <item>Would It Be Ok?</item>
        <item>What I Love About You</item>
        <item>Silence Is Golden</item>
        <item>Let Me</item>
        <item>If You Forget Me</item>
        <item>If Only She Knew</item>
        <item>Tonight I Can Write The Saddest Lines</item>
        <item>The Siren</item>
        <item>Prayer For The Morning</item>
        <item>Just Between You And Me, Lord</item>
        <item>A Cry From The Soul</item>
        <item>My Name</item>
        <item>The Raven </item>
        <item>The Road Not Taken</item>
        <item>Annabel Lee</item>
        <item>Nothing Gold Can Stay</item>
        <item>O Captain! My Captain!</item>
        <item>If—</item>
        <item>Endymion (Excerpt)</item>
        <item>How Do I Love Thee?</item>
        <item>Shall I compare thee to a summer\'s day?</item>
        <item>She Walks in Beauty</item>
        <item>The Passionate Shepherd to His Love</item>
        <item>Alone</item>
        <item>Drinking Alone in the Moonlight</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Author_Name3">
        <item>By Innarenko</item>
        <item>Nandita Shailesh Shanbhag</item>
        <item>Andrew Jefferson</item>
        <item>Brian A. Bendall</item>
        <item> Alan Balter</item>
        <item>Innarenko</item>
        <item>Erin Friedrichs</item>
        <item>Ryan Stiltz</item>
        <item>Nidhi Kaul</item>
        <item>Shelagh Bullman</item>
        <item>Randy Batiquin</item>
        <item>Pablo Neruda</item>
        <item>Kiara Wilson</item>
        <item> Pablo Neruda</item>
        <item>YoungPoet</item>
        <item> Carol A. Andrews</item>
        <item> Alora M. Knight</item>
        <item>Charlene Valladares</item>
        <item>Magoleng Wa Selepe</item>
        <item>Edgar Allan Poe</item>
        <item> Robert Frost</item>
        <item>Edgar Allen Poe</item>
        <item>Robert Frost</item>
        <item>Walt Whitman</item>
        <item>Rudyard Kipling</item>
        <item>John Keats</item>
        <item>Elizabeth Barrett Browning</item>
        <item> William Shakespeare</item>
        <item>George Gordon, Lord Byron</item>
        <item>Christopher Marlowe</item>
        <item>Edgar Allen Poe</item>
        <item>Li Po</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories3">
        <item>

My family\'s gone; there\'s no one home.\n
It\'s only me who\'s home alone.\n
I shouldn\'t hear a single squeak.\n
There shouldn\'t even be a creak,\n\n

So what\'s that thumping that I hear?\n
It must mean one thing: death is near.\n
\"You\'re an adult, you\'ll be just fine.\"\n
I tell myself as I dial \"nine\"...\n\n

Was that a knock upon the door?\n
My heart beats faster than before\n
I know it\'s closed; I\'ve checked the lock.\n
At least my killer knows to knock?\n\n

I cannot sleep, though I\'m in bed.\n
I\'ve made amends with God instead.\n
If He decides that it\'s my time,\n
Then this will be my very last rhyme.\n\n

I hear a bang and then a break.\n
My head shoots up; there\'s no mistake!\n
I turn my music volume high\n
So I won\'t hear the way I die.\n\n

I run upstairs, desk lamp in hand.\n
Over my head, ready to land,\n
And right before it did just that..\n
I remembered - I have a cat\n\n


</item>
        <item>


My son gifted me a phone, said it was very smart.\n
He said it would ease my life, that it was a new start.\n\n

Connect to internet, search for all you want to know.\n
No need for TV; on it, watch your favorite show.\n\n

It\'s time to throw out your ancient alarm clock.\n
You can shop for anything, from a ship to a sock.\n\n

You can find every address with the hi-tech map.\n
You can get rid of the wrinkles on your photo with an app.\n\n

You can pay your bills online with a single click.\n
You can order a meal, with just a finger-flick.\n\n

Now you can chat and tweet from your armchair.\n
Photos of your grandkids you can see and share.\n\n

You have the world at your fingertips now, said he,\n
But I struggle to make a simple call, Stupid Old Me!\n\n

I wanted to send a message to my oldest friend.\n
For dear, I typed dead and then pressed send.\n\n

I tried to watch a movie, but it made my eyes spin.\n
How to see those mini-figures on a tiny screen.\n\n

I tried to use the calculator; it took me an hour to find.\n
I could have added up the numbers faster in my mind.\n\n

Things get opened and switched on without my will.\n
I break into a sweat at the thought of my data bill.\n\n

Stop sending me \"Good day texts\" for goodness sake.\n
Those pings and rings give me a blasting headache.\n\n

So, for others, a smart phone may be trendy and hot.\n
For me, it\'s useless; as it\'s smart, but I am not.\n\n

        </item>
        <item>


I\'ve fallen in love- I don\'t know why\n
I\'ve fallen in love with a girl with one eye.\n\n

I knew from the start. It was plain to see
\n
That this wonderful girl had an eye out for me\n\n

She\'s charming and witty and jolly and jocular\n
Not what you\'d expect from a girl who\'s monocular.\n\n

Of eyes - at the moment - she hasn\'t full quota\n
But that doesn\'t change things for me one iota.\n\n

It must be quite difficult if you\'re bereft.\n
If your left eye is gone and your right eye is left.\n\n

But she\'s made up her mind. She\'s made her decision.\n
She can see it quite clearly in 10/20 vision.\n\n

She\'ll not leave me waiting, not left in the lurch\n
If she looks slightly sideways she\'ll see me in church.\n\n

I\'ll marry my true love who\'s gentle and kind.\n
And thus prove to everyone that loves not quite blind.\n\n

        </item>
        <item>

I\'ve looked all over, but I don\'t know where\n
I got stuck with all this hair.\n
Some hair\'s where there once was none!\n
I must have more than anyone!\n\n

Hair on my head and hair on my toes,\n
Near and on and up my nose.\n
Hair in my ears and hair on my face.\n
That gosh darn hair\'s all over the place!\n\n

I got hair on my hands and on my hips,\n
Around my eyes and on my lips.\n
My tongue, my back, my chest and neck.\n
How can I keep this hair in check?!\n\n

It\'s under my arms, on top of \'em, too.\n
Around my tummy, but what can I do?!\n
My ankles, fingers, elbows, knees!\n
\"Give me a razor, will ya, please?!\"\n\n

So tell me why! Is there a reason?\n
Maybe I\'m in werewolf season!\n
Or maybe I\'m a nice gorilla,\n
Bigfoot, bear or huge chinchilla!\n\n

Or maybe I\'m a cute alpaca,\n
Or a racka... or Chewbacca!!\n
But one thing puts my mind at ease;\n
At least I don\'t have any fleas!!\n

So now, while looking in the mirror,\n
I see myself a little clearer.\n
A lot of hair is what I see.\n
\"OMG!... It\'s really me!\"\n\n

Know what? I like it, after all!\n
It cushions me if I should fall!\n
I know it may look awfully wild,\n
But better once I\'ve had it styled.\n\n

A body perm might fill the bill\n
And really test a stylist\'s skill.\n
A dye job, too, would be attractive,\n
But that might be over reactive.\n\n

So, at the dresser\'s I will note,\n
\"No, it\'s not a furry coat!\n
It\'s just my hair!\" I\'ll say to him,\n
\"Do your best, please... just a trim.\"\n\n




</item>
        <item>


Hear eye sit inn English class; the likelihood is that eye won\'t pass
An F on my report card wood bee worse than swallowing glass
It\'s knot that eye haven\'t studied, often till late at knight
Butt the rules are sew confusing, eye simply can\'t get them write\n\n

Hour teacher says, \"Heed my advice, ewe must study and sacrifice\"
Butt if mouses are mice and louses are lice, how come blouses aren\'t blice
The confusion really abounds when adding esses two nouns
Gooses are geese, butt mooses aren\'t meese; somebody scent in the clowns\n\n

Two ultimatums are ultimata, and a couple of datum are data
Sew wouldn\'t ewe expect it wood bee correct fore a bunch of plums to be plata?
And if more than won octopus are octopi, and the plural of ox is oxen
Shouldn\'t a couple of busses bee bussi and a pare of foxes bee foxen?\n\n

Let\'s talk about spelling a wile, specifically letters witch are silent
Words like \"psychologist\" and \"wreck\" shirley make awl of us violent
And another example quite plane witch is really hard two explain
If it\'s eye before e except after sea, then what about feign and reign?\n\n

The final exam will determine how eye due, weather eye pass ore fail
I halve prepared as much as eye can down two the last detail
I\'m ready two give it my vary best inn just a little wile
And then isle take a relaxing wrest on a tropical aisle\n\n



</item>
        <item>


These words I say without a stutter:\n
I hate the taste of peanut butter!\n
In Reese\'s chocolate it may stay\n
But keep the butter far away.\n\n

It leaves a lump inside my belly,\n
It\'s even worse when paired with jelly!\n
I hate its texture, hate its smell;\n
If I go near it, I\'m unwell.\n\n

My family tells me I\'m dramatic\n
But against PB I stay emphatic.\n\n

If you\'re craving butter thick,\n
You might as well just eat the stick,\n
Or wear it as a winter coat\n
But keep it furthest from your throat!\n
Last time I ate it, things went south;\n
My tongue got glued inside my mouth!\n
If you include it in my lunch,\n
I\'ll very likely throw a punch.\n
I\'d gladly eat a Brussels sprout\n
But keep the peanut butter out!\n\n


</item>
        <item>

The question that is asked the most; we hear it everyday,
\"What time Is it?\" they want to know, and then they go away.
It\'s time for bed, it\'s time for work, or time to feed the fishes\n\n

It\'s time to take your medicine, or wash and dry the dishes.
Time in seconds, time in hours, so many freckles past a hair,
depending on the zone, or whether daylights savings there.
Time is measured many ways from minutes to months,
Time is what keeps everything from happening at once!\n\n

A time to live, a time to die, a time for having fun,
Clocks and calenders alike, all scheduled by the sun.
Intervals that can\'t be hurried, will not be denied,
a season that we know that\'s coming, as surely as the tide.\n\n

If there ever comes a time when time will be no more,
I wonder how we\'ll know to quit, or when it was before.
Do we hurry? Do we loaf? It depends upon the time...
Had we started earlier, we\'d be finished with this rhyme.\n\n

        </item>
        <item>
Would it be ok if I took some of your time?
Would it be ok if I wrote you a rhyme?\n\n

Would it be ok if I opened my heart?
Would it be ok if I took on the part\n\n

Of being your man and showed you a view,
One that only a real man could do?\n\n

Would it be ok if I could make you smile?
Would it be ok if I held you awhile?\n\n

Would it be ok if I kissed your face?
Would it be ok if I were to replace\n\n

All the men in your past that just wouldn\'t do
And vow to be faithful and always be true?\n\n

Would it be alright to look in your eyes?
Would it be alright to never tell lies?\n\n

Would it be alright to find a way?
Would it be alright to long for the day\n\n

To pull you close and whisper in your ear
And tell you our feelings are nothing to fear?\n\n

Would it be ok if I took some of your time?
Would it be ok if I wrote you a rhyme?\n\n

To tell you there\'s nothing I\'d rather do
Than spend my whole life loving only you...\n\n

</item>
        <item>


The sparkle in your eye,
The warmth of your skin,
Your breath on my neck
That shakes me within.\n\n

The touch of your hand,
The smell of your hair,
The naughtiness in your smile,
That strength in your stare.\n\n

Your kiss on my lips,
Your body near mine,
The stroke of your touch,
Makes everything feel fine.\n\n

The compassion in your touch,
The power in your face,
The beating of your heart,
That we may never end our embrace.\n\n

The beauty of your kiss,
And that magic in your touch.
It is for all these reasons and more
Why I love you so much...\n\n
</item>
        <item>


They say silence is Golden,
I believe it is true,
Because in that Golden silence,
my thoughts occur of you.\n\n

You are the flame in my candle
that lights the darkness of my room,
You are the scented flowers
that makes my heart full bloom.\n\n

You are the butterflies
that flicker in my stomach all day long,
When I know I will be holding you
before my day is done.\n\n

You are the stars that shimmer and shine,
You light up the skies above
In this Golden silence
it\'s truly you I love.\n\n

You are the thunder of the night,
your lightning strikes whenever,
Into my soul that makes me whole,
and excites my heart forever.\n\n

You are my paradise, my oceans wide,
My mountains standing tall,
So in this Golden Silence
I love you most of all.\n\n

        </item>
        <item>


Let me take care of your broken heart
and show you how to fly.
Let me hold you gently by the hand
and kiss your tears goodbye.\n\n

Let me lead you to tomorrow\'s light
and out of needless rain,
\'cause all I want right now
is to see you smile again.\n\n

Let me sing you all the songs I wrote
\'til you sleep in my embrace,
and I\'ll keep you safe and warm until
the sunlight strokes your face.\n\n

Let me bring you up the mountain\'s peak,
and I\'ll let you touch the skies
to remind you of the strength I see
when I look into your eyes.

Let me kiss and show you what is love
and the happiness it brings.
You\'ll sail again like a butterfly
endowed with pretty wings.\n\n

Let me do all these to let you see
our fates are intertwined.
You\'re the accidental precious gem
I\'ve waited long to find.\n\n

The earth and sky conspired to make us meet.
They knew we both belong
to each other like words and lovely notes
give life to every song.\n\n

So fly with me, my beautiful one.
It\'s time we leave the past.
I\'m yours to keep, and you are mine.
We\'re finally home at last.\n\n

        </item>
        <item>


I want you to know
one thing.\n\n

You know how this is:
if I look
at the crystal moon, at the red branch
of the slow autumn at my window,
if I touch
near the fire
the impalpable ash
or the wrinkled body of the log,
everything carries me to you,
as if everything that exists,
aromas, light, metals,
were little boats
that sail
toward those isles of yours that wait for me.\n\n

Well, now,
if little by little you stop loving me
I shall stop loving you little by little.\n\n

If suddenly
you forget me
do not look for me,
for I shall already have forgotten you.\n\n

If you think it long and mad,
the wind of banners
that passes through my life,
and you decide
to leave me at the shore
of the heart where I have roots,
remember
that on that day,
at that hour,
I shall lift my arms
and my roots will set off
to seek another land.\n\n

But
if each day,
each hour,
you feel that you are destined for me
with implacable sweetness,
if each day a flower
climbs up to your lips to seek me,
ah my love, ah my own,
in me all that fire is repeated,
in me nothing is extinguished or forgotten,
my love feeds on your love, beloved,
and as long as you live it will be in your arms
without leaving mine.\n\n

</item>
        <item>


She has her own special way
Of turning around my terrible day.
She makes all the bad things go away
The second that she says hey.\n\n

And when I look into her eyes,
I see pure beauty with no disguise.
Just a glance at her makes my heartbeat rise.
I know for a fact that these feelings aren\'t lies.\n\n

If only she knew
How much my love for her grew,
Maybe, just maybe, we could start something new,
And then I\'d never feel blue.\n\n

And if beauty were inches, she\'d go on for miles.
I\'d better catch her before I go out of style.
I\'m going to let my heart be my dial
So I can tell her what I\'ve been feeling for a while.\n\n

        </item>
        <item>


Tonight I can write the saddest lines.\n\n

Write, for example, \'The night is shattered
and the blue stars shiver in the distance.\'\n\n

The night wind revolves in the sky and sings.\n\n

Tonight I can write the saddest lines.
I loved her, and sometimes she loved me too.\n\n

Through nights like this one I held her in my arms
I kissed her again and again under the endless sky.\n\n

She loved me sometimes, and I loved her too.
How could one not have loved her great still eyes.\n\n

Tonight I can write the saddest lines.
To think that I do not have her. To feel that I have lost her.\n\n

To hear the immense night, still more immense without her.
And the verse falls to the soul like dew to the pasture.\n\n

What does it matter that my love could not keep her.
The night is shattered and she is not with me.\n\n

This is all. In the distance someone is singing. In the distance.
My soul is not satisfied that it has lost her.\n\n

My sight searches for her as though to go to her.
My heart looks for her, and she is not with me.\n\n

The same night whitening the same trees.
We, of that time, are no longer the same.\n\n

I no longer love her, that\'s certain, but how I loved her.
My voice tried to find the wind to touch her hearing.\n\n

Another\'s. She will be another\'s. Like my kisses before.
Her voice. Her bright body. Her infinite eyes.\n\n

I no longer love her, that\'s certain, but maybe I love her.
Love is so short, forgetting is so long.\n\n

Because through nights like this one I held her in my arms
my soul is not satisfied that it has lost her.\n\n

Though this be the last pain that she makes me suffer
and these the last verses that I write for her.\n\n



</item>
        <item>

He wrote her a song, but it never got finished
They both fell in love, but it was soon diminished
She sits on his bed and cries in his lap
He cries back at her, knowing they can\'t go back.\n\n

Hours go by and neither one can accept
That by letting go they are doing what\'s best
At the end of the day, comes the part which he fears
To let her go without shedding a tear\n\n

Never again will he kiss her goodbye
And just that thought makes him start to cry
Now he\'ll finish that song, and he\'ll write it today
This is the start and here\'s what it says\n\n

\"You are my siren, you drew me in
With a voice like an angel and the softest skin
Your eyes shine like diamonds and your smile melts my heart
I know that nothing could tear us apart\"\n\n

That\'s what he wrote and let me just say
That he\'d never do anything to throw that away
But that\'s not how it works; this world\'s bitter and harsh
And then something happened, which drew them apart\n\n

An old boyfriend showed up and that\'s when he knew
That her feelings for him were not shiny and new
This person left her and crushed her heart
But she had loved him since the very start.\n\n

When our boy came along she saw a way
To end her pain and make it all go away
But by loving this person through thick and through thin
She looked at our boy and wished it was him\n\n

Now this is where the second verse starts
It\'s about how she seemed to break his heart
He found out her feelings, it went straight to his head
So he carried on writing and here\'s what he said\n\n

\"You make me smile when no one else can
It just makes me happy to be your man
But it hurts me deeply that you long for his heart
I thought we would last, but this breaks us apart\"\n\n

He sat in his room and just wished he
Could be just like her ex so that they could be
But as long as he was there they could never be true
So he\'d sit in his room feeling sad and blue\n\n

Now comes the part where she\'s crying in his lap
They both just decided to never go back
The pain is immense but it\'s saving his heart
Because staying with her would rip him apart\n\n

Here\'s where he decides to finish the song
The story of how it all went wrong
He starts the last verse with tears dripping off his nose
The papers all wet but here\'s how it goes.\n\n

\"You were my siren, you drew me in
You taught me to love and you taught me to sin
I never thought you could break my heart
But I guess we were wrong right from the start\"\n\n

\"You were my siren, now I\'m dead at sea
You drew me in, but you didn\'t want me
I just wish I knew where it all went wrong
But now another lost sailor can hear your song\"\n\n

        </item>
        <item>

My Heavenly Father,
How wondrous are Your ways.
As this new day is dawning
My soul will sing Your praise.
I am so grateful that You love me
Grateful your love stays
Grateful that You\'re here with me
And remain with me always.\n\n

Lord, please grant me wisdom
As I go about my day today
That I will handle anything,
Whatever comes my way.
Help me to know Your will, my God,
Give me courage, Lord, I pray
That I do only what You want me to
And speak only what You\'d say.\n\n

As the world awakes, this is my prayer
That what I say and do
Will honour Jesus, God the Son,
The One whose way is true
That my words and deeds reflect His light
And shine His way anew
To a waiting world, who\'s watching me
As I am representing You.\n\n

With You by my side I\'ll not be shaken
You are my shelter in my hardest hour
And in Your will I am not forsaken
For You are my high and strongest tower.
Then by Your might I\'ll not depart
For In Your strength I walk in power
You are the joy that fills up my heart
With grace comes blessings in showers.\n\n

My God, my Lord and Saviour
May You be glorified by my life this day,\n\n

Amen\n\n
</item>
        <item>

Just between you and me, Lord, I\'d like to say
It\'s not always easy to follow Your way.
I understand what you mean by the Golden Rule--
To create a good life, there is no better tool.\n\n

Still, what if you\'ve been taught to look down on others?
Do we want to believe that we are all sisters and brothers?
It\'s hard not to resent the neighbor next door
Who does so little work, yet has so much more.\n\n

There are so many tragedies that happen worldwide.
It brings much unhappiness - that can\'t be denied.
I sit here complaining when I know it is true
That all of those troubles were not caused by you.\n\n

Yes, it just seems to me, if I remember it right,
You did give instructions that could shed lots of light
On the way life could be if Your rules were obeyed.
What a wonderful world it could be if all prayed.\n\n

I\'m glad of the chance to discuss this with You.
I\'ll try not to forget what I know I should do.
You gave me free will, so it\'s now plain to see
I will need Your help often, just between You and me.\n\n

        </item>
        <item>


Trapped with nowhere to turn, life is changing beyond my control,
causing this deep ache in the bottom of my soul.\n\n

Someone else is pulling the strings,
oh to fly, oh for wings.\n\n

Escape, I want to dig my self out,
filled with despair, filled with doubt.\n\n

Mute not able to express,
this gnawing pain and feeling of relentless distress.\n\n

Tears that are not visible to the naked eye,
silent screams that no one can hear.\n\n

I try to speak but nothing can express,
this feeling of sadness and worthlessness.\n\n

Emotional pain, walks with me through the day,
and sleeps with me through the night,
leaving me depletes with no strength to fight.\n\n

Anger for not having the courage to turn things around,
keeping me anchored to this remorse,
not able to untie the chains and change my course.\n\n

False pride rules supreme,
always there to whisper in my ear.\n\nn

Time, wasted and badly spent,
lots of hurt, lots to repent.\n\n

Solace, please come and calm my soul,
for this is what I need to make me whole.\n\n

Empathy, what I need is for someone to see,
someone to see the real me.\n\n

Love with no strings,
just giving generously amongst other things.\n\n

Words, when used as a weapon can cut like a knife,
capable of doing so much damage and take the joy out of life,\n\n

but softly spoken and softly expressed
can bring so much happiness.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>


Nomgqibelo Ncamisile Mnqhibisa\n

\nLook what they have done to my name……..\n

\nthe wonderful name of my great-great-grandmother

\nNomgqibelo Ncamisile Mnqhibisa\n

\nThe burly bureaucrat was surprised\n

\nWhat he heard was music to his ears\n

\n \‘Wat is daai, se nou weer?\’\n

\n\‘I am from Chief Daluxo Velayigodle of emalu podweni\n

\nAnd my name is Nomgqibelo Ncamisile Mnqhibisa.\’\n

\nMessia, help me !\n

\nMy name is simple\n

\n And yet so meaningful\n

\nBut to this man it is trash…..\n

\nHe gives me a name\n

\nConvenient enough to answer his whim…..\n

\nI end up being\n

\nMaria…..\n

\nI…………..\n

\nNomgqibelo Ncamisile Mnqhibisa\n\n
        </item>
        <item>

Once upon a midnight dreary,
While I pondered, weak and weary,
Over many a quaint and curious
Volume of forgotten lore—
While I nodded, nearly napping,
Suddenly there came a tapping,
As of some one gently rapping,
Rapping at my chamber door.
\"\'Tis some visitor,\" I muttered,
\"Tapping at my chamber door
Only this, and nothing more.\"

\n\nAh, distinctly I remember,
It was in the bleak December,
And each separate dying ember
Wrought its ghost upon the floor.
Eagerly I wished the morrow;
Vainly I had sought to borrow
From my books surcease of sorrow
Sorrow for the lost Lenore—
For the rare and radiant maiden
Whom the angels name Lenore—
Nameless here for evermore.

\n\nAnd the silken, sad, uncertain
Rustling of each purple curtain
Thrilled me,—filled me with fantastic
Terrors, never felt before;
So that now, to still the beating
Of my heart, I stood repeating,
\" \'Tis some visitor entreating
Entrance at my chamber door
Some late visitor entreating
Entrance at my chamber door;
This it is, and nothing more.\"

\n\nPresently my soul grew stronger;
Hesitating then no longer,
\"Sir,\" said I, \"or Madam, truly
Your forgiveness I implore;
But the fact is I was napping,
And so gently you came rapping,
And so faintly you came tapping,
Tapping at my chamber door,
That I scarce was sure I heard you."—
Here I opened wide the door;
Darkness there, and nothing more.

\n\nDeep into that darkness peering,
Long I stood there, wondering, fearing,
Doubting, dreaming dreams no mortals
Ever dared to dream before;
But the silence was unbroken,
And the stillness gave no token,
And the only word there spoken
Was the whispered word, \"Lenore!\"
This I whispered, and an echo
Murmured back the word, \"Lenore!\"
Merely this, and nothing more.
Back into the chamber turning,

\n\nAll my soul within me burning,
Soon again I heard a tapping,
Something louder than before.
\"Surely,\" said I, \"surely, that is
Something at my window lattice;
Let me see then, what thereat is,
And this mystery explore—
Let my heart be still a moment,
And this mystery explore;—
\'Tis the wind, and nothing more.\"

\n\nOpen here I flung the shutter.
When, with many a flirt and flutter,
In there stepped a stately Raven
Of the saintly days of yore;
Not the least obeisance made he;
Not a minute stopped or stayed he,
But, with mien of lord or lady,
Perched above my chamber door—
Perched upon a bust of Pallas
Just above my chamber door—
Perched, and sat, and nothing more.

\n\nThen this ebony bird beguiling
My sad fancy into smiling,
By the grave and stern decorum
Of the countenance it wore,
\"Though thy crest be shorn and shaven,
Thou,\" I said, \"art sure no craven,
Ghastly, grim, and ancient Raven,
Wandering from the nightly shore,
Tell me what thy lordly name is
On the night\'s Plutonian shore!\"
Quoth the Raven, "Nevermore.\"

\n\nMuch I marveled this ungainly
Fowl to hear discourse so plainly,
Though its answer little meaning—
Little relevancy bore;
For we can not help agreeing
That no living human being
Ever yet was blest with seeing
Bird above his chamber door—
Bird or beast upon the sculptured
Bust above his chamber door,
With such name as \"Nevermore.\"

\n\nBut the Raven, sitting lonely
On that placid bust, spoke only
That one word, as if his soul in
That one word he did outpour.
Nothing farther then he uttered,
Not a feather then he fluttered,
Till I scarcely more than muttered,
\"Other friends have flown before—
On the morrow he will leave me,
As my Hopes have flown before.\"
Then the bird said, \"Nevermore.\"
Startled at the stillness broken

\n\nBy reply so aptly spoken,
\"Doubtless,\" said I, \"what it utters
Is its only stock and store,
Caught from some unhappy master
Whom unmerciful Disaster
Followed fast and followed faster
Till his songs one burden bore—
Till the dirges of his Hope that
Melancholy burden bore
Of \'Never—nevermore.\' \"

\n\nBut the Raven still beguiling
All my sad soul into smiling,
Straight I wheeled a cushioned seat in
Front of bird, and bust, and door;
Then, upon the velvet sinking,
I betook myself to linking
Fancy unto fancy, thinking
What this ominous bird of yore—
What this grim, ungainly, ghastly,
Gaunt, and ominous bird of yore
Meant in croaking "Nevermore.\"
This I sat engaged in guessing,

\n\nBut no syllable expressing
To the fowl whose fiery eyes now
Burned into my bosom\'s core;
This and more I sat divining,
With my head at ease reclining
On the cushion\'s velvet lining
That the lamplight gloated o'er,
But whose velvet violet lining,
With the lamplight gloating o'er
She shall press, ah, nevermore!

\n\nThen, methought, the air grew denser,
Perfumed from an unseen censer
Swung by Seraphim, whose footfalls
Tinkled on the tufted floor.
\"Wretch,\" I cried, \"thy God hath lent thee—
By these angels he hath sent thee
Respite—respite and nepenthe[1]
From thy memories of Lenore!
Quaff, oh quaff this kind nepenthe,
And forget this lost Lenore!\"
Quoth the Raven, "Nevermore."
\"Prophet!\" said I, \"thing of evil!—

\n\nProphet still, if bird or devil!—
Whether Tempter sent, or whether
Tempest tossed thee here ashore,
Desolate, yet all undaunted,
On this desert land enchanted—
On this home by Horror haunted—
Tell me truly, I implore—
Is there—is there balm in Gilead?
Tell me—tell me, I implore!\"
Quoth the Raven, \"Nevermore.\"

\n\n\"Prophet!\" said I, \"thing of evil,—
Prophet still, if bird or devil!—
By that heaven that bends above us,
By that God we both adore,
Tell this soul with sorrow laden,
If, within the distant Aidenn,
It shall clasp a sainted maiden
Whom the angels name Lenore—
Clasp a rare and radiant maiden,
Whom the angels name Lenore.\"
Quoth the Raven, \"Nevermore.\"

\n\n\"Be that word our sign of parting,
Bird or fiend,\" I shrieked, upstarting;
\"Get thee back into the tempest
And the night\'s Plutonian shore!
Leave no black plume as a token
Of that lie thy soul hath spoken!
Leave my loneliness unbroken!—
Quit the bust above my door!
Take thy beak from out my heart, and
Take thy form from off my door!\"
Quoth the Raven, \"Nevermore.\"

\n\nAnd the Raven, never flitting,
Still is sitting, still is sitting
On the pallid bust of Pallas
Just above my chamber door;
And his eyes have all the seeming
Of a demon\'s that is dreaming,
And the lamplight o\'er him streaming
Throws his shadow on the floor;
And my soul from out that shadow,
That lies floating on the floor,
Shall be lifted—nevermore!
        </item>
        <item>

Two roads diverged in a yellow wood,
And sorry I could not travel both
And be one traveler, long I stood
And looked down one as far as I could
To where it bent in the undergrowth;

\n\nThen took the other, as just as fair,
And having perhaps the better claim,
Because it was grassy and wanted wear;
Though as for that the passing there
Had worn them really about the same,

\n\nAnd both that morning equally lay
In leaves no step had trodden black.
Oh, I kept the first for another day!
Yet knowing how way leads on to way,
I doubted if I should ever come back.

\n\nI shall be telling this with a sigh
Somewhere ages and ages hence:
Two roads diverged in a wood, and I—
I took the one less traveled by,
And that has made all the difference.
        </item>
        <item>
It was many and many a year ago,
In a kingdom by the sea,
That a maiden there lived whom you may know
By the name of Annabel Lee;
And this maiden she lived with no other thought
Than to love and be loved by me.

\n\nI was a child and she was a child,
In this kingdom by the sea,
But we loved with a love that was more than love—
I and my Annabel Lee—
With a love that the wingèd seraphs of Heaven
Coveted her and me.

\n\nAnd this was the reason that, long ago,
In this kingdom by the sea,
A wind blew out of a cloud, chilling
My beautiful Annabel Lee;
So that her highborn kinsmen came
And bore her away from me,
To shut her up in a sepulchre
In this kingdom by the sea.

\n\nThe angels, not half so happy in Heaven,
Went envying her and me—
Yes!—that was the reason (as all men know,
In this kingdom by the sea)
That the wind came out of the cloud by night,
Chilling and killing my Annabel Lee.

\n\nBut our love it was stronger by far than the love
Of those who were older than we—
Of many far wiser than we—
And neither the angels in Heaven above
Nor the demons down under the sea
Can ever dissever my soul from the soul
Of the beautiful Annabel Lee;

\n\nFor the moon never beams, without bringing me dreams
Of the beautiful Annabel Lee;
And the stars never rise, but I feel the bright eyes
Of the beautiful Annabel Lee;
And so, all the night-tide, I lie down by the side
Of my darling—my darling—my life and my bride,
In her sepulchre there by the sea—
In her tomb by the sounding sea.
        </item>
        <item>

Nature\'s first green is gold,\n
Her hardest hue to hold,

\n\nHer early leaf\'s a flower;\n
But only so an hour.

\n\nThen leaf subsides to leaf.\n
\nSo Eden sank to grief,

\n\nSo dawn goes down to day.\n
Nothing gold can stay.
        </item>
        <item>

O Captain! My Captain! our fearful trip is done;
The ship has weather\'d every rack, the prize we sought is won;
The port is near, the bells I hear, the people all exulting,
While follow eyes the steady keel, the vessel grim and daring:

\n\nBut O heart! heart! heart!
O the bleeding drops of red,
Where on the deck my Captain lies,
Fallen cold and dead.

\n\nO Captain! my Captain! rise up and hear the bells;
Rise up—for you the flag is flung—for you the bugle trills;
For you bouquets and ribbon\'d wreaths—for you the shores a-crowding;
For you they call, the swaying mass, their eager faces turning;

\n\nO captain! dear father!
This arm beneath your head;
It is some dream that on the deck,
You\'ve fallen cold and dead.

\n\nMy Captain does not answer, his lips are pale and still;
My father does not feel my arm, he has no pulse nor will;
The ship is anchor\'d safe and sound, its voyage closed and done;
From fearful trip, the victor ship, comes in with object won;

\n\nExult, O shores, and ring, O bells!
But I, with mournful tread,
Walk the deck my captain lies,
Fallen cold and dead.
        </item>
        <item>

If you can keep your head when all about you
Are losing theirs and blaming it on you,
If you can trust yourself when all men doubt you,
But make allowance for their doubting too;
If you can wait and not be tired by waiting,
Or being lied about, don\’t deal in lies,
Or being hated, don\’t give way to hating,
And yet don\’t look too good, nor talk too wise:

\n\nIf you can dream—and not make dreams your master;
If you can think—and not make thoughts your aim;
If you can meet with Triumph and Disaster
And treat those two impostors just the same;
If you can bear to hear the truth you\’ve spoken
Twisted by knaves to make a trap for fools,
Or watch the things you gave your life to, broken,
And stoop and build \’em up with worn-out tools:

\n\nIf you can make one heap of all your winnings
And risk it on one turn of pitch-and-toss,
And lose, and start again at your beginnings
And never breathe a word about your loss;
If you can force your heart and nerve and sinew
To serve your turn long after they are gone,
And so hold on when there is nothing in you
Except the Will which says to them: \‘Hold on!\’

\n\nIf you can talk with crowds and keep your virtue,
Or walk with Kings—nor lose the common touch,
If neither foes nor loving friends can hurt you,
If all men count with you, but none too much;
If you can fill the unforgiving minute
With sixty seconds\’ worth of distance run,
Yours is the Earth and everything that\’s in it,
And—which is more—you\’ll be a Man, my son!

        </item>
        <item>
A thing of beauty is a joy for ever:
\nIts loveliness increases;
\nit will never
Pass into nothingness; but still will keep
A bower quiet for us, and a sleep
Full of sweet dreams, and health, and quiet breathing.
Therefore, on every morrow, are we wreathing
A flowery band to bind us to the earth,
Spite of despondence, of the inhuman dearth
Of noble natures, of the gloomy days,
Of all the unhealthy and o\'er-darkened ways
Made for our searching:
\nyes, in spite of all,
Some shape of beauty moves away the pall
From our dark spirits. Such the sun, the moon,
Trees old and young, sprouting a shady boon
For simple sheep; and such are daffodils
With the green world they live in; and clear rills
That for themselves a cooling covert make
\'Gainst the hot season;
\nthe mid forest brake,
Rich with a sprinkling of fair musk-rose blooms:
And such too is the grandeur of the dooms
We have imagined for the mighty dead;
All lovely tales that we have heard or read:
An endless fountain of immortal drink,
Pouring unto us from the heaven\'s brink.

\n\nNor do we merely feel these essences
For one short hour; no, even as the trees
That whisper round a temple become soon
Dear as the temple\'s self, so does the moon,
The passion poesy, glories infinite,
Haunt us till they become a cheering light
Unto our souls, and bound to us so fast,
That, whether there be shine, or gloom o\'ercast;

\n\nThey always must be with us, or we die.
Therefore, \'tis with full happiness that I
Will trace the story of Endymion.
The very music of the name has gone
Into my being, and each pleasant scene
Is growing fresh before me as the green
Of our own valleys:
\nso I will begin
Now while I cannot hear the city\'s din;
Now while the early budders are just new,
And run in mazes of the youngest hue
About old forests;
\nwhile the willow trails
Its delicate amber; and the dairy pails
Bring home increase of milk. And, as the year
Grows lush in juicy stalks, I\'ll smoothly steer
My little boat, for many quiet hours,
With streams that deepen freshly into bowers.
Many and many a verse I hope to write,
Before the daisies, vermeil rimm\'d and white,
Hide in deep herbage; and ere yet the bees
Hum about globes of clover and sweet peas,
I must be near the middle of my story.
O may no wintry season, bare and hoary,
See it half finish\'d:
\nbut let Autumn bold,
With universal tinge of sober gold,
Be all about me when I make an end.
And now, at once adventuresome, I send
My herald thought into a wilderness:
There let its trumpet blow, and quickly dress
My uncertain path with green, that I may speed
Easily onward, thorough flowers and weed.
</item>
        <item>
How do I love thee? Let me count the ways.
\nI love thee to the depth and breadth and height
My soul can reach, when feeling out of sight
\nFor the ends of being and ideal grace.
I love thee to the level of every day\'s
\nMost quiet need, by sun and candle-light.
\nI love thee freely, as men strive for right.
\nI love thee purely, as they turn from praise.
I love thee with the passion put to use
\nIn my old griefs, and with my childhood\'s faith.
I love thee with a love I seemed to lose
With my lost saints. I love thee with the breath,
Smiles, tears, of all my life; and, if God choose,
\nI shall but love thee better after death.
</item>
        <item>

Shall I compare thee to a summer\'s day?
Thou art more lovely and more temperate:
Rough winds do shake the darling buds of May,
And summer\'s lease hath all too short a date:
Sometime too hot the eye of heaven shines,
And often is his gold complexion dimm\'d;
And every fair from fair sometime declines,
By chance, or nature\'s changing course, untrimm\'d;
But thy eternal summer shall not fade,
Nor lose possession of that fair thou owest;
Nor shall Death brag thou wander\'st in his shade,
When in eternal lines to time thou growest;
So long as men can breathe, or eyes can see,
So long lives this, and this gives life to thee.
        </item>
        <item>
She walks in beauty, like the night
Of cloudless climes and starry skies;
And all that\’s best of dark and bright
Meet in her aspect and her eyes;
Thus mellowed to that tender light
Which heaven to gaudy day denies.

\n\nOne shade the more, one ray the less,
Had half impaired the nameless grace
Which waves in every raven tress,
Or softly lightens o\’er her face;
Where thoughts serenely sweet express,
How pure, how dear their dwelling-place.

\n\nAnd on that cheek, and o\’er that brow,
So soft, so calm, yet eloquent,
The smiles that win, the tints that glow,
But tell of days in goodness spent,
A mind at peace with all below,
A heart whose love is innocent!
        </item>
        <item>

Come live with me and be my love,
And we will all the pleasures prove,
That Valleys, groves, hills, and fields,
Woods, or steepy mountain yields.

\n\nAnd we will sit upon the Rocks,
Seeing the Shepherds feed their flocks,
By shallow Rivers to whose falls
Melodious birds sing Madrigals.

\n\nAnd I will make thee beds of Roses
And a thousand fragrant posies,
A cap of flowers, and a kirtle
Embroidered all with leaves of Myrtle;

\n\nA gown made of the finest wool
Which from our pretty Lambs we pull;
Fair lined slippers for the cold,
With buckles of the purest gold;

\n\nA belt of straw and Ivy buds,
With Coral clasps and Amber studs:
And if these pleasures may thee move,
Come live with me, and be my love.

\n\nThe Shepherds\’ Swains shall dance and sing
For thy delight each May-morning:
If these delights thy mind may move,
Then live with me, and be my love.
        </item>
        <item>
From childhood\’s hour I have not been
As others were—I have not seen
As others saw—I could not bring
My passions from a common spring—
From the same source I have not taken
My sorrow—I could not awaken
My heart to joy at the same tone—
And all I lov\’d—I lov\’d alone—
Then—in my childhood—in the dawn
Of a most stormy life—was drawn
From ev\’ry depth of good and ill
The mystery which binds me still—
From the torrent, or the fountain—
From the red cliff of the mountain—
From the sun that \’round me roll’d
In its autumn tint of gold—
From the lightning in the sky
As it pass\’d me flying by—
From the thunder, and the storm—
And the cloud that took the form
(When the rest of Heaven was blue)
Of a demon in my view—
        </item>
        <item>


Beneath the blossoms with a pot of wine,

\n\nNo friends at hand, so I poured alone;

\n\nI raised my cup to invite the moon,

\n\nTurned to my shadow, and we became three.

\n\nNow the moon had never learned about drinking,

\n\nAnd my shadow had merely followed my form,

\n\nBut I quickly made friends with the moon and my shadow;

\n\nTo find pleasure in life, make the most of the spring.

\n\nWhenever I sang, the moon swayed with me;

\n\nWhenever I danced, my shadow went wild.

\n\nDrinking, we shared our enjoyment together;

\n\nDrunk, then each went off on his own.

\n\nBut forever agreed on dispassionate revels,

We promised to meet in the far Milky Way.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="Poem_Title">

       Home Alone, Not Smart Enough For A Smart Phone, My One-Eyed Love, A Thing About Hair!, English Is A Pane, I Hate Peanut Butter, Time, Would It Be Ok?, What I Love About You, Silence Is Golden, Let Me, If You Forget Me, If Only She Knew, Tonight I Can Write The Saddest Lines, The Siren, Prayer For The Morning, Just Between You And Me, Lord, A Cry From The Soul, My Name, The Raven, The Road Not Taken, Annabel Lee, Nothing Gold Can Stay, O Captain! My Captain!, If—, Endymion (Excerpt), How Do I Love Thee?, Shall I compare thee to a summer\'s day?, She Walks in Beauty, The Passionate Shepherd to His Love, Alone, Drinking Alone in the Moonlight
    </string>
    <string name="Poem_Title_A">
        Poem Title List
    </string>

</resources>