<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="story_names2">
        <item>Berenice</item>
        <item>Harrington’s Hearse (Lake Lopez)</item>
        <item>Darkness in the Rear View Mirror</item>
        <item>Instant Messaging</item>
        <item>KIDS IN THE DARK</item>
        <item>The Oneirophage</item>
        <item>I Sat On The Bus</item>
        <item>The man in the bunny costume</item>
        <item>The ghost babysitter</item>
        <item>Stranger in the house</item>
        <item>When the dead walk the halls</item>
        <item>Sleep Story</item>
        <item>just ask for mercy</item>
        <item>The Intrusive Demon</item>
        <item>la vie en rose</item>
        <item>The Perfect Curse</item>
        <item>a ghost story</item>
        <item>Casa Del Mal</item>
        <item>Why Doesn\'t Anyone Rent This Place?</item>
        <item>THE GRAVEYARD SHIFT</item>
        <item>If the Walls Could Talk</item>
        <item>Three Loud Bangs on the Door</item>
        <item>The Best Seats In The House</item>



    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Author_Name2">
        <item>Edgat Allan Poe</item>
        <item>Lake Lopez</item>
        <item>unknown</item>
        <item>GingyGrl99</item>
        <item>Kookies_babie</item>
        <item>S.W Rice</item>
        <item>Issac Cook</item>
        <item>Ananya Mishr</item>
        <item>Ananya Mishra</item>
        <item>UNKNOWN</item>
        <item>UNKNOWN</item>
        <item> John Merino</item>
        <item> L. Maddison</item>
        <item> K. Antonio</item>
        <item> A.G. Scott</item>
        <item> Christina Farella</item>
        <item> Emiliano Cruz Villanueva</item>
        <item> Annette C</item>
        <item>Bad Cat Z</item>
        <item>Del Gibson</item>
        <item>Carter Msilisi</item>
        <item>Michał Przywara</item>
        <item>Cierra Lynn</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories2">
        <item>
\nMISERY is manifold. The wretchedness of earth is multiform.\n
Overreaching the wide horizon as the rainbow, its hues are as various as the hues of that arch, —as distinct too,
yet as intimately blended. Overreaching the wide horizon as the rainbow! How is it that from beauty
I have derived a type of unloveliness? --from the covenant of peace a simile of sorrow? But as,
in ethics, evil is a consequence of good, so, in fact, out of joy is sorrow born. Either the memory of
past bliss is the anguish of to-day, or the agonies which are have their origin in the ecstasies which might have been.\n

\nMy baptismal name is Egaeus; that of my family I will not mention.
Yet there are no towers in the land more time-honored than my gloomy, gray, hereditary halls.
Our line has been called a race of visionaries; and in many striking
particulars --in the character of the family mansion --in the frescos of the chief saloon --in the
tapestries of the dormitories --in the chiselling of some buttresses in the armory --but more
especially in the gallery of antique paintings --in the fashion of the library chamber --and, lastly, in the
very peculiar nature of the library\'s contents, there is more than sufficient evidence to warrant the belief.\n

\nThe recollections of my earliest years are connected with that chamber,
and with its volumes --of which latter I will say no more. Here died my mother.
Herein was I born. But it is mere idleness to say that I had not lived before --that the soul has no previous existence.
You deny it? --let us not argue the matter. Convinced myself, I seek not to convince. There is,
however, a remembrance of aerial forms --of spiritual and meaning eyes --of sounds,
musical yet sad --a remembrance which will not be excluded; a memory like a shadow,
vague, variable, indefinite, unsteady; and like a shadow, too, in the impossibility of my
getting rid of it while the sunlight of my reason shall exist.\n

\nIn that chamber was I born. Thus awaking from the long night of what seemed, but was not,
nonentity, at once into the very regions of fairy-land --into a palace of imagination --into the
wild dominions of monastic thought and erudition --it is not singular that I gazed around me with a
startled and ardent eye --that I loitered away my boyhood in books, and dissipated my youth in reverie;
but it is singular that as years rolled away, and the noon of manhood found me still in the mansion of my
fathers --it is wonderful what stagnation there fell upon the springs of my life --wonderful how total
an inversion took place in the character of my commonest thought. The realities of the world affected me as visions,
and as visions only, while the wild ideas of the land of dreams became, in turn, --not the material of my
every-day existence-but in very deed that existence utterly and solely in itself.\n

\nBerenice and I were cousins, and we grew up together in my paternal halls.
Yet differently we grew --I ill of health, and buried in gloom --she agile,
graceful, and overflowing with energy; hers the ramble on the hill-side --mine
the studies of the cloister --I living within my own heart, and addicted body and
soul to the most intense and painful meditation --she roaming carelessly through
life with no thought of the shadows in her path, or the silent flight of the
raven-winged hours. Berenice! --I call upon her name --Berenice! --and from the gray ruins
of memory a thousand tumultuous recollections are startled at the sound! Ah! vividly is her
image before me now, as in the early days of her light-heartedness and joy! Oh! gorgeous yet
fantastic beauty! Oh! sylph amid the shrubberies of Arnheim! --Oh!

Naiad among its fountains! --and then --then all is mystery and terror,
and a tale which should not be told. Disease --a fatal disease --fell like the simoom upon
her frame, and, even while I gazed upon her, the spirit of change swept, over her, pervading her
mind, her habits, and her character, and, in a manner the most subtle and terrible, disturbing even
the identity of her person! Alas! the destroyer came and went, and the victim --where was she,
I knew her not --or knew her no longer as Berenice.\n

\nAmong the numerous train of maladies superinduced by that fatal and primary one which effected a
revolution of so horrible a kind in the moral and physical being of my cousin, may be mentioned as
the most distressing and obstinate in its nature, a species of epilepsy not unfrequently terminating
in trance itself --trance very nearly resembling positive dissolution, and from which her manner of
recovery was in most instances, startlingly abrupt. In the mean time my own disease --for I have been
told that I should call it by no other appelation --my own disease, then, grew rapidly upon me, and
assumed finally a monomaniac character of a novel and extraordinary form --hourly and momently gaining
vigor --and at length obtaining over me the most incomprehensible ascendancy.
This monomania, if I must so term it, consisted in a morbid irritability of those
properties of the mind in metaphysical science termed the attentive.
It is more than probable that I am not understood; but I fear, indeed,
that it is in no manner possible to convey to the mind of the merely general reader,
an adequate idea of that nervous intensity of interest with which,
in my case, the powers of meditation (not to speak technically) busied and buried themselves,
in the contemplation of even the most ordinary objects of the universe.\n

\nTo muse for long unwearied hours with my attention riveted to some frivolous device on the margin,
or in the topography of a book; to become absorbed for the better part of a summer\'s
day, in a quaint shadow falling aslant upon the tapestry, or upon the door;
to lose myself for an entire night in watching the steady flame of a lamp,
or the embers of a fire; to dream away whole days over the perfume of a flower;
to repeat monotonously some common word, until the sound, by dint of frequent repetition,
ceased to convey any idea whatever to the mind; to lose all sense of motion or physical existence,
by means of absolute bodily quiescence long and obstinately persevered in; --such were a few of the
most common and least pernicious vagaries induced by a condition of the mental faculties, not,
indeed, altogether unparalleled, but certainly bidding defiance to anything like analysis or explanation.\n

\nYet let me not be misapprehended. --The undue, earnest, and morbid attention thus excited by
objects in their own nature frivolous, must not be confounded in character with that ruminating propensity
common to all mankind, and more especially indulged in by persons of ardent imagination. It was not even,
as might be at first supposed, an extreme condition or exaggeration of such propensity, but primarily and
essentially distinct and different. In the one instance, the dreamer, or enthusiast, being interested by an
object usually not frivolous, imperceptibly loses sight of this object in a wilderness of
deductions and suggestions issuing therefrom, until, at the conclusion of a day dream often
replete with luxury, he finds the incitamentum or first cause of his musings entirely vanished and forgotten.
In my case the primary object was invariably frivolous, although assuming, through the
medium of my distempered vision, a refracted and unreal importance. Few deductions,
if any, were made; and those few pertinaciously returning in upon the original
object as a centre. The meditations were never pleasurable; and, at the termination
of the reverie, the first cause, so far from being out of sight, had attained that
supernaturally exaggerated interest which was the prevailing feature of the disease.
In a word, the powers of mind more particularly exercised were, with me, as I
have said before, the attentive, and are, with the day-dreamer, the speculative.\n

\nMy books, at this epoch, if they did not actually serve to irritate the disorder,
partook, it will be perceived, largely, in their imaginative and inconsequential
nature, of the characteristic qualities of the disorder itself. I well remember, among others, the treatise
of the noble Italian Coelius Secundus Curio \"de Amplitudine Beati Regni dei\"; St.
Austin\'s great work, the \"City of God\"; and Tertullian \"de Carne Christi,\" in which the
paradoxical sentence \"Mortuus est Dei filius; credible est quia ineptum est: et sepultus
resurrexit; certum est quia impossibile est\" occupied my undivided time, for many
weeks of laborious and fruitless investigation.\n

\nThus it will appear that, shaken from its balance only by trivial things, my reason
bore resemblance to that ocean-crag spoken of by Ptolemy Hephestion, which steadily
resisting the attacks of human violence, and the fiercer fury of the waters and the winds,
trembled only to the touch of the flower called Asphodel. And although, to a careless thinker,
it might appear a matter beyond doubt, that the alteration produced by her unhappy malady,
in the moral condition of Berenice, would afford me many objects for the exercise of that
intense and abnormal meditation whose nature I have been at some trouble in explaining,
yet such was not in any degree the case. In the lucid intervals of my infirmity, her calamity,
indeed, gave me pain, and, taking deeply to heart that total wreck of her fair and gentle life,
I did not fall to ponder frequently and bitterly upon the wonder-working means by which so strange a
revolution had been so suddenly brought to pass. But these reflections partook not of the
idiosyncrasy of my disease, and were such as would have occurred, under similar circumstances,
to the ordinary mass of mankind. True to its own character, my disorder revelled in the less
important but more startling changes wrought in the physical frame of Berenice --in the singular and
most appalling distortion of her personal identity.\n

\nDuring the brightest days of her unparalleled beauty, most surely I had never loved her.
In the strange anomaly of my existence, feelings with me, had never been of the heart,
and my passions always were of the mind. Through the gray of the early morning --among
the trellised shadows of the forest at noonday --and in the silence of my library at night,
she had flitted by my eyes, and I had seen her --not as the living and breathing Berenice,
but as the Berenice of a dream --not as a being of the earth, earthy, but as the abstraction
of such a being-not as a thing to admire, but to analyze --not as an object of love, but as the
theme of the most abstruse although desultory speculation. And now --now I shuddered in her presence,
and grew pale at her approach; yet bitterly lamenting her fallen and desolate condition,
I called to mind that she had loved me long, and, in an evil moment, I spoke to her of marriage.\n

\nAnd at length the period of our nuptials was approaching, when, upon an afternoon in the
winter of the year, --one of those unseasonably warm, calm, and misty days which are the
nurse of the beautiful Halcyon*, --I sat, (and sat, as I thought, alone,) in the inner
apartment of the library. But uplifting my eyes I saw that Berenice stood before me.\n

\n*For as Jove, during the winter season, gives twice seven days of warmth, men have called
this clement and temperate time the nurse of the beautiful Halcyon --Simonides.\n

\nWas it my own excited imagination --or the misty influence of the atmosphere --or the
uncertain twilight of the chamber --or the gray draperies which fell around her
figure --that caused in it so vacillating and indistinct an outline? I could not tell.
She spoke no word, I --not for worlds could I have uttered a syllable. An icy chill ran through my frame;
a sense of insufferable anxiety oppressed me; a consuming curiosity pervaded my soul;
and sinking back upon the chair, I remained for some time breathless and motionless,
with my eyes riveted upon her person. Alas! its emaciation was excessive, and not one
vestige of the former being, lurked in any single line of the contour. My burning glances at length fell upon the face.\n

\nThe forehead was high, and very pale, and singularly placid;
and the once jetty hair fell partially over it, and overshadowed the hollow temples with innumerable
ringlets now of a vivid yellow, and Jarring discordantly, in their fantastic character, with the
reigning melancholy of the countenance. The eyes were lifeless, and lustreless, and seemingly pupil-less,
and I shrank involuntarily from their glassy stare to the contemplation of the thin and shrunken lips.
They parted; and in a smile of peculiar meaning, the teeth of the changed Berenice disclosed
themselves slowly to my view. Would to God that I had never beheld them, or that, having done so,
I had died!\n

\nThe shutting of a door disturbed me, and, looking up, I found that my cousin had departed from the chamber.
But from the disordered chamber of my brain, had not, alas! departed,
and would not be driven away, the white and ghastly spectrum of the teeth.
Not a speck on their surface --not a shade on their enamel --not an indenture in their edges --but
what that period of her smile had sufficed to brand in upon my memory.
I saw them now even more unequivocally than I beheld them then.
The teeth! --the teeth! --they were here, and there, and everywhere, and
visibly and palpably before me; long, narrow, and excessively white,
with the pale lips writhing about them, as in the very moment of their first terrible development.
Then came the full fury of my monomania, and I struggled in vain against its strange and
irresistible influence. In the multiplied objects of the external world I had no thoughts but for the teeth.
For these I longed with a phrenzied desire.
All other matters and all different interests became absorbed in their single contemplation.
They --they alone were present to the mental eye, and they, in their sole individuality,
became the essence of my mental life. I held them in every light. I turned them in every attitude.
I surveyed their characteristics. I dwelt upon their peculiarities. I pondered upon their conformation.
I mused upon the alteration in their nature.
I shuddered as I assigned to them in imagination a sensitive and sentient power,
and even when unassisted by the lips, a capability of moral expression. Of Mad\'selle
Salle it has been well said, "que tous ses pas etaient des sentiments," and of Berenice
I more seriously believed que toutes ses dents etaient des idees. Des idees! --ah here
was the idiotic thought that destroyed me! Des idees! --ah therefore it was that
I coveted them so madly! I felt that their possession could alone ever restore me to peace, in giving me back to reason.\n

\nAnd the evening closed in upon me thus-and then the darkness came, and tarried,
and went --and the day again dawned --and the mists of a second night were now g
athering around --and still I sat motionless in that solitary room; and still
I sat buried in meditation, and still the phantasma of the teeth maintained its
terrible ascendancy as, with the most vivid hideous distinctness, it floated about
amid the changing lights and shadows of the chamber. At length there broke
in upon my dreams a cry as of horror and dismay; and thereunto, after a pause,
succeeded the sound of troubled voices, intermingled with many low moanings of
sorrow, or of pain.
I arose from my seat and, throwing open one of the doors of the library,
saw standing out in the antechamber a servant maiden, all in tears, who told me that Berenice was --no more.
She had been seized with epilepsy in the early morning, and now,
at the closing in of the night, the grave was ready for its tenant, and all the preparations for the burial were completed.\n

\nI found myself sitting in the library, and again sitting there alone.
It seemed that I had newly awakened from a confused and exciting dream.
I knew that it was now midnight, and I was well aware that since the setting of the sun Berenice had been interred.
But of that dreary period which intervened I had no positive --at least no definite comprehension.
Yet its memory was replete with horror --horror more horrible from being vague,
and terror more terrible from ambiguity.
It was a fearful page in the record my existence,
written all over with dim, and hideous, and unintelligible recollections.
I strived to decypher them, but in vain; while ever and anon, like the spirit of a departed sound,
the shrill and piercing shriek of a female voice seemed to be ringing in my ears. I had done a deed --what was it?
I asked myself the question aloud, and the whispering echoes of the chamber answered me, "what was it?"\n

\nOn the table beside me burned a lamp, and near it lay a little box. It was of no remarkable character,
and I had seen it frequently before, for it was the property of the family physician;
but how came it there, upon my table, and why did I shudder in regarding it?
These things were in no manner to be accounted for, and my eyes at length dropped to the open pages of a book,
and to a sentence underscored therein. The words were the singular but simple ones of the poet Ebn
Zaiat, "Dicebant mihi sodales si sepulchrum amicae visitarem, curas meas aliquantulum fore levatas."
Why then, as I perused them, did the hairs of my head erect themselves on end, and the blood of my
body become congealed within my veins?\n

\nThere came a light tap at the library door, and pale as the tenant of a tomb, a
menial entered upon tiptoe. His looks were wild with terror, and he spoke to me in a voice tremulous,
husky, and very low. What said he? --some broken sentences I heard.
He told of a wild cry
disturbing the silence of the night --of the gathering together of the household-of a
search in the direction of the sound; --and then his tones grew thrillingly distinct as
he whispered me of a violated grave --of a disfigured body enshrouded, yet still breathing, still palpitating, still alive!\n

\nHe pointed to garments;-they were muddy and clotted with gore. I spoke not,
and he took me gently by the hand; --it was indented with the impress of human nails.
He directed my attention to some object against the wall; --I looked at it for some minutes; --it was a spade.
With a shriek I bounded to the table, and grasped the box that lay upon it.
But I could not force it open; and in my tremor it slipped from my hands, and fell heavily,
and burst into pieces; and from it, with a rattling sound, there rolled out some instruments of
dental surgery, intermingled with thirty-two small, white and ivory-looking substances that were
scattered to and fro about the floor.\n\n

</item>
        <item>
I was nine years old the first time I saw it, a week before Thanksgiving in 1953.
I heard it first, a car idling outside the house. Something was wrong with its motor,
like its pistons churned slower than they should. I stared into the shadows for a while,
listening to that slow growling engine. Then my curiosity got the better of me.\n\n

That winter was a record breaker for cold and I caught a chill the second my feet hit the floor.
I looked out my window and saw it parked on the street below, a new hearse. The street
lights gave its black paint a dark glimmer. Every other car on the street wore a layer of wet grime,
but the hearse was pristine. Must have just rolled off the assembly line, I thought, and that\’s all
I remember about the first time. I\’m not even sure how long I stood at the window, watching it chug grey exhaust into the night air.

\n\nI woke up to my mother nudging me out of sleep.\n\n

\“I have to tell you something bad, honey,\” she said. \“Your granddaddy passed away during the night.\”\n\n

I remember how my eyes immediately watered as my mind fixated on the black hearse.\n\n

\“If you’d like to see him for a minute,\” my mom said, \“he’s still in his room.\”\n\n

I nodded, wrestling with what I\’d seen and what had happened.\n\n

\“Your brother doesn\’t know yet,\” she added.\n\n

My father had worked the night shift. He was still in his police uniform, sitting next to grandpa\’s body.\n\n

\“I closed his eyes,\” he said.\n\n

I took in the complete stillness of Grandpa’s face and the bruised hand that was above his quilt.\n\n

\“Every day is precious,\” my dad said. \“You know that now, don\’t you?\”\n\n

\“Yes, Sir.\”\n\n

Mr. Bell, the town\’s undertaker, showed up later in his own hearse, which was clean but much older
than the one I\’d seen last night. I was a bright enough boy to figure out what had happened.
My grandpa had been sick. I\’d been worried about him. The worry had parked a spooky
hearse in my dreams.\n
I almost told my parents about it.\n
They were busy, though, and grieving.\n
At some point, I forgot all about the nightmare hearse. I didn\’t think about it again until 1975.\n\n

By that time, I\’d followed in my father\’s footsteps and gone to work for the state as a trooper.
That night in April of \‘75 I had worked a seven car accident on the interstate.
I was heading home late, irritated that I\’d missed dinner with my family and that my plate would have to be reheated.
You were ten years old and we lived in that nice three-bedroom with the wide driveway, and that\’s where the damn thing was waiting for me.

\n\nIt looked bran new again. Sleek and black, all of its chrome buffed to a high shine.
But I knew it was the same hearse. I recognized the off kilter engine.
The sight of it made me jam the brake pedal damn near through the floor board.
Law enforcement types don\’t freeze. Not ever. But I locked up right then,
every memory from that cold night in \’53 flooding back to me in a clammy whoosh.\n\n

I gawked at that hearse, its taillights gleaming red in the night, and one thought
went screeching through my mind. Not the boy. I sat there a few moments
longer, my heart galloping and my throat too tight to swallow. Then I got a hold of myself.
I\’d chased bad guys at a hundred miles per hour and been in gun fights with career criminals.
I was the wrong man to mess with and, in my mind, the hearse was about to find that out.\n\n

Not my boy.\n\n

I swung out of the car, my right hand already on my service weapon, and a second later I was at that
hearse\’s driver\’s side window, gun raised, finger on the trigger. You get out of here.
Nobody\’s leaving with you tonight.\n\n

I heard the front door of our house open.\n
Looked to my left for just a second.\n
Saw your mother in the doorway and thought she looked so beautiful, like she had the first
time I\’d laid eyes on her. I started to yell, \“Stay inside.\”
She didn\’t need to see whatever I was about to yank out of that hearse.
And when I looked back to the driveway the car was gone.\n
I\’d only glanced in her direction a fraction of a second. I was sure that I\’d kept that awful car and its
illegally blackened windows in my peripheral vision the entire time. Yet, it had gotten away.\n\n

\“What are you doing?\”\n\n

I must\’ve looked like the biggest fool to her, standing there with my .45 aimed at the empty driveway,
my cruiser in the street with its door open. I put the gun away quick.\n\n

\“Are you all right?\”\n\n

\“Uh huh,\” I told her. \“I\’ll explain later.\”\n\n

I told her I was running a scenario in my head. Cop stuff, I said. She didn\’t believe it.
Your mom was too smart for a line of bull like that. Her instinct must’ve told her to let it go,
though, because she didn\’t press me about it. I was happy to be home with my wife and son.
I went to your room, kissed your head. I was still watching you sleep when my mother called
and gave me the bad news. My father had died.\n\n

I\’m not ashamed to tell you that even as I wept for my dad I was glad that it was him and not you.
He\’d gotten to be everything a husband, a father and a lawman should be.\n
It was not lost on me though that both my granddaddy and my daddy had died in their own beds.\n
I told myself that any man who gets to go while under his own covers is a lucky soul indeed.\n\n

Your grandmother passed away two years later. The cancer had gnawed her into skin and bones,
but her death still came as a shock; there\’d been no terrible hearse to warn me.\n
The next time I saw it was in 1982.\n
By then I\’d become a Field Training Officer and most days I had a rookie trooper riding shotgun, learning the trade.
It was a clear day in June when the nightmare hearse, cleaner than any car on the showroom floor, pulled up beside me.
The rookie didn\’t know what lurked beside us. I suppose the hearse just wasn\’t his to see.\n\n

A few miles down the road it leapt ahead, its clomping engine grinding in a hot wail.
I watched it creep into my lane and disappear.\n
I swear, that car left as easily as a light fades once its switch is flipped off.\n\n

My heart stayed in my stomach as I ran all the facts through my head;
my grandfather in \‘48, my father in \‘75… Again, all I could think about was my family,
especially you. He\’s still a kid. Please, not my boy. Dispatch gave us a 10-19 – return to station. When we got there,
the lieutenant told me to phone home and your mom told me what had happened to my brother.\n\n

Your Uncle Bill had never been the law enforcement type, but he\’d done well with the work he\’d chosen.
He was a senior vice president for an advertising agency. He liked the job so much that he hardly ever took a day off.
When he cancelled all his appointments and stayed home with a flu four days in a row, it was only right that one of his
colleagues would check on him. It hadn\’t been the flu after all. It\’d been an infection around his heart. Bill was only forty two.

\n\nIn the years that followed, I wondered why it hadn\’t shown up when your grandmother died.
Then, when your mother left this world and there\’d been no black hearse to foreshadow the heart attack,
I understood. Both of those good women had taken the name Harrington,
but they hadn\’t been a Harrington by blood. It only comes for us, son.\n
It’s our omen. I bet it\’s been in our family since it was a horse and buggy,
trailing us, waiting for our days to end.\n\n

Now I know something else about that car. I learned it tonight when your youngest boy was talking our heads off.
He wasn\’t making up stories the way little kids do sometimes. You see, son, the hearse skips a generation.
It must because you looked so surprised when he described it.\n\n

\“Like they use at funerals, it was there… Honest.\”\n\n

I should\’ve asked him if it was a new. I\’m pretty sure it was. I think it\’s always new and impossibly perfect.
If you can figure out what that means, then you\’re a smarter man than me. Maybe one day,
when your boy\’s a little older, you can show him this letter. Maybe he\’ll know.\n\n

That\’s all I have to tell you, son, so I\’m calling it a night. Time for me to get some rest.
I\’m the right kind of tired and that makes me unafraid. I love you. I hope you\’ve always known that.
In the end, I guess that\’s all we really have before the hearse takes us away.\n
Hell, my own bed… I\’m a lucky man.\n\n

        </item>
        <item>

I have always been uneasy driving alone at night. It was worst the first few times, when
I had just gotten my license, but the nagging fear has never gone away to this day.
It’s disorienting to look into the mirrors and see nothing, and I mean nothing but the consuming blackness of the night.
It makes me hesitant to check the mirrors should I see this dark void, or worse, someone sitting in my back seat staring at me.

\n\nIn the summer of 2013, I found myself driving home alone on highway 902 from a party.
It was almost midnight, and needless to say it was pitch black. As was usual at night,
I was on edge. I had the radio off, and could hear nothing but the muffled roar of tires on pavement and the dull hum of the engine.
I stole a glance into the middle rear view mirror, and saw nothing but darkness through the back window.

\n\nI know that I looked backward and saw nothing. I\’m sure of it.
Just the seemingly endless blackness of the night.\n
I remember it so clearly because not ten seconds later a car passed me to the left. Headlights on.
I had one of those sudden adrenaline rushes like when you think you see a person outside your
bedroom window when it\’s just a tree, or when you start awake at night with the feeling of falling.
Ten seconds earlier, nothing had been behind me. Suddenly, a car. I drove all the way home
shivering and knowing something was off.\n\n

The next morning, I found two sets of scratches near the back of my van.\n
One was on the left rear, one was on the right. The car was pretty old.\n\n
They could have been there for months, but that was the first time that I distinctly remembered seeing them.


\n\nIn hindsight, there are two possibilities for what happened that night. Possibility one.
By some glitch in reality, or something paranormal,
this other car had somehow appeared behind me within ten seconds of me checking my mirror.
Like some weird ghost crap or something. However, the second option is what makes my blood run cold whenever I consider it.

\n\nIt didn\’t even occur to me until months after the fact, but it makes me dread driving alone at night even more.
Possibility two. The car was normal. It had approached me from the rear and passed me to my left.\n
However, something large, and wide, and as black as the night had been clinging to the rear of my car,
obscuring my view through the window and leaving deep scratches on the sides.\n
And I had inadvertently driven it home with me.
Advertisements
And I had inadvertently driven it home with me.\n\n
</item>
        <item>

It all started on the fourteenth night of March, the night of my parents’ 20th wedding anniversary.\n

It was a wonderful, sunny day, if memory serves. Surprisingly warm for before the beginning of spring.
The beautiful weather was perfect for the atmosphere of the day – being married for twenty years is obviously a
momentous occasion, so my parents had booked a table at our favourite Italian restaurant.\n\n

Of course, this was a formal occasion, so I had my best suit on. It was 5:33,
and I was just straightening my tie when my phone went off – I\’d received a message. That\’s strange,
I thought, that never happens. I checked the message: it was from my mum.\n
It was quite a jumble of numbers and letters, but through the vocabulary stew I could make out one legible phrase: \“Please help me.\”
It should go without saying that this worried me greatly, so I immediately replied, \“Are you okay?\” Just as instantly,
I got another text which read, \“Oops. Pocket text!\” I sighed with all the relief I had and continued to prepare myself.

\n\nA few minutes later,
I received yet another message, this time from my dad. I checked the text,
and once again it was a massive mixture of letters and numbers, with the phrase \“Please help me\” concealed within.
Creepy though this was, my dad was always a joker, so I presumed he was just joking around, until I was sent another text saying,
\“Oops. Pocket text!\” Now this sparked panic.
Pure,unmistakable panic. Exactly half a minute passed when I received the exact same two messages from my sister.
This could not be coincidental. It just couldn\’t.\n\n

In a state of sheer anxiety, I started to run to the restaurant.\n
I made it about a quarter of the way before I was stopped by a police officer. \“Main road\’s closed,\” he said, \“Huge car crash.\”
This was the exact moment I realised just what had happened. I demanded to see the wreckage, a request which I was surprised was allowed.
When I got there, it wasn\’t the remnants of the car that caught my eye, nor the flames billowing from the destroyed vehicle. No.
I was horrified to see the lifeless corpses of my mother, father and sister.\n
I asked for the estimated time of their deaths – all three of them were killed instantly by the collision, at 5:32.
A minute before the very first text.\n\n

</item>
        <item>
Growing up poor in the Deep South meant sharing a lot with my little brother, Ollie. Most often,
we\'d pass toys, clothes, and skin conditions between us. Up until he was six, we even shared a bed.
Neither of us was happy about that.\n\n

It was my tenth birthday when that changed. I got one present that year, and it was a bed of my own.
Ollie was jealous right away, and I could understand why. He had to keep that half-broken down frame with the worn out mattress.
The one I\'d gotten wasn\'t much better, but not being broken and worn was enough.\n\n


Sleeping apart was a great feeling.
It was freedom. No longer would I have to suffer the sudden and inexplicable kicks to the stomach.
No longer would I wake up with Ollie\'s foot pressed into my neck like he\'d stepped on Dracula the night before.

\n\nAt least, that\'s what I\'d thought.\n\n

Right away, right after I got the new bed, the shriek started.\n\n

At first I thought Ollie woke up in the middle of the night and screamed because he\'d gotten scared.
Then, the sound echoed through the tiny room again and I knew it wasn\'t a normal cry.\n\n

The room was always black as pitch after sunset.\n
The one window we had was pressed against a long leaf pine and even the biggest, brightest moon cast no light inside.

\n\nThe shriek just about drove me crazy. Every night, probably at the same exact time,
these sharp yelps would knock me right out of my dreams. It wasn\'t my Mom or Dad yelling, either.\n\n
I knew what that sounded like, believe me! Most worrying of all was the fact I could never tell where it was coming from.
It seemed completely random.\n\n


One night it\'d come from somewhere near the closet. The next, it\'d shoot out from a corner of the ceiling.\n\n

Any hope I\'d had of having my own space would get dashed every time as Ollie would silently slip into the bed with me,
shaking like crazy.\n He\'d clasp onto me and wouldn\'t let go until it was almost daybreak.\n
Most times I\'d take his hand and tell him everything was going to be okay, that it\'d be over by morning...
but I was never really sure.\n\n

Over time, the shriek started changing. At first it was only by small degrees,
but eventually it took on the primal hooting sound of a primate calling out its fierce warning.\n\n

I had to clasp pillows to my ears just to keep from going deaf.\n\n

Mom and Dad never believed me or Ollie, basically because the thing... whatever it was... refused to make a
peep when they were in the room. Apparently they couldn\'t even hear it through the walls even though it was damned sure loud enough!



\n\nThe shriek just got worse and worse until I felt like I couldn\'t take it anymore.
Me and Ollie were doing really bad in school, and we just had no energy at all.\n
I could sleep more deeply with my head propped up and eyes open in the middle of class than in my own room at night.

\n\nThen, thankfully, we moved out of the house nearly a year later.
I had contemplated all sorts of things, even a child\'s clumsy concept of suicide,
to get away from the horrific nightly noise.\n\n

There was no problem at the next house. It was a nice white cookie-cutter home on a dead end street, and
I welcomed the normalcy. What\'s more, when we moved in there was a bunk bed waiting for me and Ollie.
No more broken bed, no more second bed I ended up having to share anyway.\n\n

The only problem was deciding who\'d get the top bunk.\n\n

I told Ollie I deserved it. After all, I had gotten a new bed way back, and he ruined it by climbing in every night.

\n\n\"What?\" He shook his head, \"I never did that.\"\n

I had always wondered why the noise stopped the second I was sharing my bed. Now I had the answer\n\n


</item>
        <item>
In the late \’40s of the last century, after a decade of private research involving experiments with binaural
beat brainwave frequencies, extrasensory cognition, and rare extracts of a South American vine, Dr. Tomás Roessner
perfected a technique whereby one could actually intrude into the psyche and \“see\” another\’s thoughts.
Despite having exhaustively documented his rigorous work, he could find no institution that would even
offer to review it. Forced to sell his invention, he found by word of mouth among those through whom he
procured narcotics a prospective buyer, \nthe bête noire of an old New York family, Mr. John M. Dunn,
a voyeuristic connoisseur of the supernatural and the obscene, who had squandered his idle youth in the
great libraries of Paris, \nthose catacombs of departed authors, rummaging among their hordes of dusty and obsolete works;
a literary ghoul who disturbed with profane fingers the charnel-houses of decayed philosophies.\n
He readily agreed to the Dr.’s asking price without haggling, delighted at the prospect of exploring such a bizarre novelty.

\n\nOnce adept at the operation of the apparatus, Dunn paid Dr. Roessner off and under an assumed name
rented a shabby house within view of Sing Sing prison. In the timeless night, while the convicts fitfully slept,
with the aid of a set of stolen blueprints and his new mindreading device,
he raided their memories cell by cell at liberty to savor the forbidden thrill of thefts,
molestations, moonlit homicides, in secret, without remorse or consequence.

\n\n Within a month, the prisoners, telling each other about the nightmares from which they had all begun abruptly to awaken,
discovered they shared striking similarities: first, processions of alligators
and tortoises filed through a swamp crowded with faceless people and shrieking orchids; next, a shadow man, at
whom they looked directly but could never quite see, would watch them in utter stillness from an empty
house while invisible hands probed behind their eyes as they had to stand naked, legs locked in place, unable to run away.
Their compared descriptions of the house were identical, including its location just outside the walls.\n
By mutual agreement, it was planned that the first of them to receive parole or be released would search this
house out to find if it really existed, and investigate the source of their troubling dreams.\n\n

A few days after being freed, their chosen spy was able to inform them with a smuggled message in code that not only
was the house real, but he had broken into it at night and found a gaunt, moustached man in a silk smoking
jacket seated bolt upright, head thrust back, both eyes gaping, mouth stuck open in a
stiffened gasp, clenched hands gripping the arms of his chair, in front of a \“scientific machine.\” A handwritten journal
on the desk told the whole story of his adventures prying unconstrained through their psyches, plundering the haunted memories
of criminal after criminal, seeking ever more shameful and audacious experiences until finally he wrote, on July 7th,
of his overwhelming desire to witness telepathically the next execution in the prison\’s notorious electric chair.\n\n

</item>
        <item>

I sat on the bus, on my way to school.\n\n

Listening to music, and paying little to no attention to the other students.\n\n

At one of the stops my mind snapped back to reality.\n\n

I looked towards the small house. Tommy\’s house, I thought.\n\n

A hand slipped through the drapes of the window and waved the bus driver to move on.\n\n

\‘He\’s sick\’, I thought, paying no large amount of attention to the situation.\n\n

The day flew by.\n\n

I watched the local news channel after school, and what I heard paralyzed me.\n\n

Tommy\’s entire family was murdered that day by an unknown suspect.\n\n

After hearing this news, I moved back up to my room and quietly fell asleep.\n\n
</item>
        <item>

When I was younger I used to live by the woods and could see a cemetery from my back porch.
One Easter I remember waking up and seeing the Easter bunny (one of those terrifying costumes) and
what really gets me is I remember smelling the wet hay. When I woke up I didn’t tell anyone,
but there was an extra Easter egg in my house that my parents didn\’t hide.\n
Years later when I was in high school I asked my parents if they ever dressed up
like the Easter bunny and came into our room, they said they would never go through so much trouble.\n
Then my younger sister, who I shared a bunk bed with when this happened, said she remembers when
the Easter bunny came into our room and made a remark about the hay smell.\n
I was terrified that we both remembered seeing a person dressed as a bunny in our room.
To make it even stranger, I told the friends I sat with at lunch what happened.
One of the girls was my neighbor across the street.\n
She told me one Easter a long time she looked out her window during the night and saw
the Easter bunny standing in her driveway. I had chills. \nTo this day I am terrified of people in rabbit costumes.\n\n
</item>
        <item>

When my niece was really young, she was in a bouncer at my sisters house, I was house and babysitting.

I had left her to go to the kitchen to grab some water.\n
My sisters chocolate labs were probably sniffing and licking her head because I could hear
her giggling like she was having a blast. I hadn\’t notice how cold it had gotten. Then I heard it.\n
A loud wooden SNAP. Like a thick piece of wood had been snapped in half suddenly or a tree was knocked over.

\n\nI ran into the room and what I saw and smelled freaked me out.
The dogs were huddled in the corner whimpering,
my niece was just staring at the ceiling corner with wide eyes, and it was cold and smelled like Stetson.

\n\nI took her and we decided to go to a different room. When my sister finally came home,
I told her what happened. She just rolled her eyes and said \“that is Hugh.\” I was confused.
She said Hugh was the previous owner of the house who had died ten years before his wife sold it.
She said he likes to follow my niece around and you can tell it his him because the dogs freak,
it gets cold and smells like cheap cologne.\n\n

I don\’t believe in that shit, but I do believe that feeling you get in your gut when something doesn\’t feel right\n\n
</item>
        <item>
In college, I would go home every other weekend to work at the job I had since high school.
I would drive directly from campus after my last class on Friday to my job (about an hour) and,
after my shift was done, I’d go back to my parent’s house which was out in the middle of nowhere.\n\n

My parents weren\’t yet home when I got back from work (they often spend their Friday and
Saturday evenings drinking like they were the ones in college), so the house was dark and,
since it was mid fall, so was the yard – save for the yard light. I pulled into my normal parking spot,
got out of the car and then turned to open the back door of my car and get my backpack out of the back seat.

\n\nThat’s when I noticed that the bathroom light was on.

Was that light on when I pulled up? It must have been, right?\n\n

As I was contemplating the light and reaching for my backpack, there was suddenly a very angry
looking old woman standing in the window staring at me. We\’re not talking resting bitch face here either,
she was pissed off at me and I knew it.\n\n

We stood there staring at each other for a good ten seconds when my parent\’s pulled into the driveway
and distracted me from my stare down with the woman in the bathroom. By the time I turned back,
the light was still on, but the woman was gone\n\n

</item>
        <item>

I used to volunteer at a nursing home where we had several instances where new residents accurately
described former residents down to specific nightgowns or color of glasses who
I and the staff knew had died in that room and complain about them coming into the room at night.
Then once I was walking through the hallway and it was normally uncomfortably warm inside but I felt a chill and goosebumps.
One of the CNAs said I had just walked through a ghost. I couldn\’t get warm again for the rest of the day.
There were flickering lights and tvs turning themselves on.\n
Several of the staff were from the same southeast Asian country and they were talking about ghosts and
disrespect for the dead so much that management had someone come in to do a candle
light ceremony and this Lady with crystals and dreadlocks came in to do a sage brushing.\n
Things calmed down after that. Lights stayed on better and the residents seemed calmer.\n\n
</item>

        <item>


\n\nInsomnia runs in my family, afflicting both sides of it with equal intensity.
That’s nearly four centuries of Mexican tossing and Italian turning, with fits of German cursing and crying in between.
A long heritage of discomfort, and,
according to family gossip, one that has only been interrupted by the rotting medicines that tempt anyone who’s had to put up with an extended period of lost sleep – drugs, alcohol,
compulsive anger, and every possible combination of the three.
With the advent of psychotherapy, and the discovery that trauma is an actual illness and not a defect of character,
many of us have learned to deal with insomnia in less destructive ways.\n


\n\nIn 2010, my father was prescribed a small dose of the sleep aid Zolpidem, brand name Ambien, by his psychiatrist - a neat,
gentle little drug that has chemical kinship with tranquilizers like Valium and Xanax, but without their addictive and narcotic qualities.
To my dad, who had long suffered from sleepless nights and long days spent dragging himself through his work as an electrician,
this was the answer to all of his prayers.
After his inaugural dose, he smiled and drifted off into what I’m sure was the finest sleep he’d had in decades.
I’m also sure this is all he remembers of that first night, and he’s better off for it. Zolpidem has a blackout effect on the mind,
like a drinking binge without the hangover. My mother and I recall it in deeper, less relaxing ways.
For her, it brought on the uncomfortable squeeze of an abused past, and, for me, it brought forth the very shadow of death.
It was an alien shape seen in my peripheral vision that night. We all have to see that shape at least once in our lives.
Knowing I’ll have to see it twice frightens me.\n

\n\n Watching my dad’s face slacken at the dinner table after taking his first dose was distressing.\n\n
It bore the stamp of deep intoxication, and it was immediate, without any intervening period of jollity or talkativeness.
No time to acclimate to it. Only a high-school junior at the time, I was unfamiliar with the actual sensation of being drunk,
but I would later come to know it well as a solitary confinement for the soul.\n

\n\nIn certain quantities, liquor utterly disables your ability to step outside yourself.
For the constructive drinker, often an artist, leaving this ability behind is useful and focusing, like a monk retreating into his cell to pray.
Booze simply becomes a chemical means of getting to that same, isolated room.
For the drunk however, who often harbors a deep hatred for what he sees in the mirror, this blind isolation is an addictive,
absolute deliverance, and an absolute terror for those around him. There are few things in this world as wonderful as being drunk,
and even fewer as awful as seeing someone else drunk.
(This is why I’ve always thought of the designated-driver concept as something nice in theory and unimaginable in practice.
Drunk people are only bearable when you’re also drunk,
and being sober among drinkers has the same world-shattering effect as catching a glimpse of yourself having sex.
“Is this what it really looks like when I do this?”) Blissfully sliding about inside his cell without mirrors,
or even the faint reflectivity of a window,
it becomes nearly impossible for anyone to make the drunk see that he is trapped, or that there is a world outside.
My mother watched helplessly from outside like this for most of her childhood as my grandfather,
Andrew, committed himself to this living death,
dumping frightening amounts of alcohol into himself and raging as if there were no one else in the room.
My dad’s face that night, so relaxed it might have melted right off of his skull, brought these times closer to her than she’d felt in years.\n

\n\nbBy the time I began to know him, Andrew had long been sober, and the sleep story he told me when I was seven was an isolated horror from an age so far away I could barely imagine it.
I had no idea that he was, in his own way, doing a dry run of the apology he would never get to make to his own children.
A veteran of the Battle of Iwo Jima, the Second World War’s bloodiest passage in the Pacific,
and the first and only battle in which American casualties exceeded the Japanese,
he recalled trying to sleep in the rare moments between fighting,
curled up against the black volcanic dust that blankets the island like a mourning veil. This dust is soft and pliant,
and might have been comfortable for him to lay on, drawing him down into sleep for seconds so split they barely existed.
The Japanese had dug a vast network of bunkers and tunnels through the island before he arrived, and he would wake up again,
and again, and again, to their muffled voices only a few feet underneath him.
Imagine drifting off to the sounds of men planning how best to kill you.
It’s the boogeyman in the childhood closet made real.
It’s the suppressed nightmare of ancient humanity, resting in caves and clearings while hungry beasts waited behind the trees.
Who wouldn’t try to drink until they’d totally drowned such a memory?\n

\n\nSome, but not all, of these thoughts were with me as my dad began to nod off over his unfinished dinner.
The absent ones, the adult ones, the ones I’ve laid down here, made themselves known that night as a warm tightness in my chest,
my body figuring things out for me long before my brain did.
My mother and I woke him up with a gentle shake and told him it was time for bed,
but he simply hovered above his seat for a moment and plopped back down under the weight of his medication.
We approached him, realizing we would have to actually walk him to his bedroom,
but before we arrived, he pointed across the table and into the kitchen,
calmly informing us there was a little girl standing in front of our refrigerator.\n

\n\nI once saw a production of The Crucible in Austin, Texas, and at a climax in the play,
one of the bewitched girls feigned seeing a demonic bird perched just beyond the tribunal.
The actress pointed to it, and roughly half the audience turned around in their seats to look where she had pointed.
I looked at them looking, and silently judged them fools.
It was only a play.
Did they really expect something to be there? I can’t remember if either one of us turned around to see the little girl.
Such a decision, to look or not to look, is the whole ancient struggle with the material world in embryo,
and it is too freighted with pride for me to remember it accurately.
I’d like to say I didn’t look, my refusal a harbinger of the staunch atheism that would eventually develop out of my catholic upbringing,
but that’s just wishful thinking.\n

\n\nIf my mother and I had bothered to read the literature that came with my dad’s prescription,
we would have known that hallucinations are a common accessory in Zolpidem’s package deal of side effects,
especially upon its first dose.
This harmless hiccup in my father’s nervous system nonetheless had a chilling effect on us,
and we quickly gathered him up from his chair and into bed, where he curled up and left us to stew in our thoughts.
Here is where I must speculate entirely, because, after my dad fell asleep,
there is a patch of nothing in my head that looks to be about the length of an hour.
Guided by my current habits, I can safely assume that, in my distress,
I listened to an episode of Mystery Science Theater 3000 on my iPhone while I milled around the kitchen,
munching on a hastily stacked turkey sandwich, the kind where the lunch meat is constantly sliding out from between the bread on a
slick of mustard. There was a threat in the air that I had to escape.
Birds come down onto branches and stay put before a thunderstorm, and cows lay down to sleep.
I should have just stayed in the kitchen.\n

\n\nMy memory picks up again as I cross from the kitchen into the dining room,
feeling in the corner of my eye the tall window that looks out onto the lawn.
A warm flood light brightens the first few feet of our concrete driveway and the right edge of our boxwood hedge.
Beyond that is total darkness after nine P.M, and nothing can be seen for twenty yards except the neighbors’ porchlights across the street.
Although small and narrow, it is a picture window in the most wonderful sense.
At any time of night, you can see raccoons, opossums, squirrels, cats, dogs,
and all manner of mammalian life slinking by to sniff and enjoy the food and water we leave out for the neighborhood strays.
Sometimes, an enormous moth of exquisite pattern will flutter over and land with a thump on the glass,
allowing anyone who happens to be in the dining room to admire it for hours. It’s like our own private zoo.
But that night, there wasn’t a creature stirring anywhere. No crickets, no thumping moths,
no hideously sleek roaches trying to get inside – a bad stillness that made me want to look away from the window as
I sat down at the table to finish my sandwich.\n

\n\nBut it still beckoned my gaze, pulling my eyes towards it like a private letter left open on someone’s desk, and, as I looked up from my sandwich,
the little girl my father had seen passed by the window.
I remember snapping my head back towards the kitchen,
thinking my mother had come into the dining room and that I was seeing her reflection, but I was alone.
When I looked back, the little girl was gone, but I was sure I had seen a tan, diaphanous dress, fluttering in the humid summer air,
and young skin on a solid face, free of any adolescent blemish,
shining in the porch light as thick and alive as my own.
I can still see the turn-of-the-century brocade of her outfit,
and the unsettling way she quickly floated by the window, as if on roller skates.\n

\n\nA trick of the light no doubt, primed for a ghostly vision by my father’s hallucination,
could easily explain away what I saw that night. But, in my memory, I can feel the weight of that girl’s body.
Her reality is indisputable for me, but reality has shrunk for me as I write this.
All of us are pining for physical connection like we’ve never done before.
The world we miss, the one we think will finally satisfy us,
is the unmasked closeness of parties and movie theaters and sex that we once knew without limit.
Perhaps, for the first time in history, we wish that this really was all that there is.
Hamlet’s terrifying assertion that there are more things in heaven and earth than are dreamt of in our philosophy has only been
sharpened in the meantime, and our reunion with material life will find us totally unequipped, or, worse, totally unwilling, to confront it.\n

\n\nI still don’t believe in ghosts, or gods, or prayers, or blessings and mystical vibrations,
or any of the lies people tell themselves and their children so that life doesn’t seem like a succession of random cruelties.
This is a function of privilege. I’ve never really known the dire,
physical desperation that is a rule for most of the proletariat world – desperation for food, for shelter,
for a face that doesn’t regard you as an obstacle, for a day spent without the wounding anxiety of poverty and parenthood.
My worries have been wholly neurotic.
There’s no inherent honor or intelligence in being worried about death and the process of dying.
It’s a cheap anxiety that everyone buys the moment they are born, and it’s most sharp for me whenever I’m falling asleep.
It’s how I react to this fear, when I’m clamped inside the space between consciousness and sleep,
between life and death, that seems most important to me now. My generation likes to sneer at the ones that came before it.
They were all asleep at the wheel of history and willing to take whatever heinous orders they were given to preserve their sense of security,
but us millennials are still utterly unable to be alone with our thoughts.
Sensing the responsibility we carry as stewards of a rapidly crumbling world,
we search for disciplines that will show us the way forward,
and healthier ways of beating back the impish mental chatter that comes for us when all the lights are off and there’s
no one to talk to – meditation, exercise, natural supplements like melatonin and valerian root, soothing whispers and roleplays – but,
come morning, we still find ourselves upright and emptyhanded, like every generation before us.\n

\n\nI still do believe that my father’s drug, by bringing him closer to real sleep, brought him closer to death,
and that this closeness allowed death to bleed into my waking life. It doesn’t matter if what I saw was real in the supernatural sense,
and I don’t claim to have a better grasp on my own life because of it.
Cigarettes, Benadryl, booze, and my phone are still the only ways I can get to sleep,
and I remain as slavishly dependent upon artificial tranquilizers for comfort as any child with his favorite blanket.
What matters is the telling of this sleep story.
What matters is that I don’t keep what I saw to myself and pridefully let the strain of keeping it a secret rot my insides and
emaciate my conscience until I start denying that it ever happened.
What matters is that we take pride in our collective heritage of insomnia,
and recognize our resistance to sleep as an impulse against death and towards life,
as if the history of every society’s struggle against its own demise were being recapitulated every time we close our eyes.
This is what distinguishes us from the birds and the cows that land and lay down in the face of extinction.\n

\n\nAs I finish typing this story, there is a pleasant drowsiness tugging at my eyes.
I hope that as I fall asleep tonight, no matter how drugged or drunk or distracted I am,
I will try and feel myself sink into it, fighting all the time while knowing I am, like everyone, destined to lose.
I hope my sleep is long and restoring, and that I lift myself up in the morning like a wiser,
stronger generation, knowing the enemy better and ready to face it in the light of the new day.
</item>

        <item>
It\’s a tricky section of the garden- shaded and north-facing- but the foliage thrives under my watchful eye.
I ensure it grows lush and verdant, and only I can coax it from sulking in this hot, dry weather.
I\’m pleased to see the blue-green tones of sieboldiana flourishing beside the golden variegated undulates leaves.

\n\nI\‘m outraged by the pock-marked damage I\’ve discovered, and search for the culprit amongst the ovate leaves.
There! A snail clings to the underside of a leaf, sucked close in a non-consensual and greedy kiss.
I prise it off and the shell implodes in my pincer grip, crushed mush oozing between my fingertips.
I discard the muck onto the soil with disdain, satisfied that feeder has now become food.

\n\nA gardener must be brutal, constantly battling soft bodied grubs, mandible-fanged pests,
plagues of aphids and creeping insidious blight, all in order to protect the precious shoots and trembling new leaves.
She must also have a hard, calculating heart to destroy what was previously nurtured, cutting back and curbing life when the time comes,
sacrificing what was once so carefully created. I, the gardener, am like God; through me nature flows,
giving vigour to the strong and enabling the weak and damaged to pass.

\n\nInside the house the landline telephone clamours,
taking seven rings for Mrs Nolan to stir from her armchair doze and mobilise her arthritic joints to answer it.
Crouched here beneath the open kitchen window I am perfectly placed to eavesdrop what she says.

\n\n\“Hello, this is Miriam…

\n\n\“Oh, I\’m as well as can be expected. And you?

\n\n\“Yes, a very hot spell. The garden\’s very thirsty…

\n\n\“Oh…really? You\’re too kind! Honestly, it\’s too much…

\n\n“It\’s an absolute honour. I can\’t quite take it all in. Trevor would have been so pleased. So very, very pleased…

\n\n\“Thank you ever so much. It\’s all such a surprise!

\n\n\“I certainly will, and you too. Cheerio.\”

\n\nThe telephone pings as it\’s replaced in its cradle, and I sense Mrs Nolan shuffling along to the back door to find me.
I muse over the emotional wobble I overheard in her voice.
She\’s been prone to tears since Mr Nolan\’s unfortunate accident and numerous well meaning villagers have phoned to offer comfort,
but this call was a curious one and I\’m keen to be enlightened.

\n\n\“Mercy, are you there?\”

\n\n\“Right over here, Mrs Nolan.\” I sound as sweet as maple syrup.

\n\nMrs Nolan emerges from the side of the house, blinking in the bright sunshine, taking a moment to locate me by the shadowy border.

\n\n\“I\’ve had the most remarkable news, Mercy. The Village Committee have nominated me for the Best Blooming Garden award.
How kind of them! I\’m sure it\’s Trevor\’s dahlias that persuaded the judges; he took such meticulous care of them.
Trevor deserved the nomination, not me- he\’d have been so proud- but it\’s too late…\”

\n\nBoth Mrs Nolan and I glance involuntarily to the place on the lawn where Mr Nolan was found.
I am pleasantly surprised to notice how prolifically the daisies are growing. They\’re clearly thriving from minerals in Mr Nolan\’s blood.

\n\nHere we go. Mrs Nolan\’s eyes are welling up and her chin is wobbling.
I stand, knit my eyebrows together with a show of concern and gently usher her back indoors to put the kettle on.

\n\nThat\’s when I know there is no hope left for Mrs Nolan.
A well-meaning nomination- probably from sympathy votes- has exacerbated her misery and reduced her to convulsive weeping,
proving any pleasure in life is now well beyond her grasp.
What particularly irks me is that the dahlias were mostly attended to by myself, at least ever since Mr Nolan\’s stroke last year,
and I\’ve exclusively cared for them since his recent demise. The dahlias, the roses,
those blousy, vulgar petunias that Mrs Nolan chose and I obediently bedded in- the nomination is all thanks to me.

\n\nThe world has no place for the old and feeble. In this very garden,
right under our noses, nature uses all manner of macabre means to ensure order is kept; pincers, stingers, poisons,
parasites that eat their host slowly from within. Although violent, these acts are essentially a great kindness.
A kindness Mrs Nolan now deserves.



\n\nI ponder my options.

\nWhilst some impulsivity was involved with Mr Nolan, this time I\'ll carefully consider my plan.

\nNot to say last time wasn\’t efficient and effective.

\n\nI\’d taken great care that afternoon to prune the privet hedge to perfection.
I was clearing away the cuttings- gloved, as the sap can sting- whilst Mr Nolan limped up and down,
pedantically questioning some cross branch irregularities he perceived in the shrubs.
I pitied him, unable as he was to appreciate my work and no longer able to manage the shears himself with one useless arm.
It was the least I could do to relieve him of his agitation once and for all.

\n\nStepping close, I plunged the points of the shears into his fleshy, cotton-shirted paunch,
which gave little more resistance than a fish belly, and slid the blades upwards under his ribs.
It was remarkably easy. This single moment of pain was all it took to free him from his frustrated, failing body.
A poppy-crimson stain blossomed under his spread fingers as he clutched his gut in a futile attempt to hold back the seeping blood.
Before my eyes his pallid face became slack-jawed with disbelief.
He gurgled and spluttered, eyes bulging pleadingly, but there was nothing left to be said.
As he staggered, I gently grasped him by the shoulders and guided him down to the ground face first,
so the blade tips emerged through his back like fresh new shoots.

\n\nIt looked every bit the tragic accident; the clumsy fall of a foolish man carrying tools he couldn\’t handle,
when he should have left the work for the gardener. I removed the remaining cuttings under the pretence I\’d left much earlier,
and left him for Mrs Nolan to find after she returned from the Parish cake sale.

\n\nPerhaps a similarly violent end for Mrs Nolan would be fitting.
I\’m briefly excited by the thought of her pale wrists cut to scarlet ribbons by secateurs- driven to suicide by grief, of course.
I suspect the bleeding out could take some time and given the neighbours\' windows will be wide open in the summer heat,
enabling them to hear her screams, maybe this is an unwise option.

\n\nA fall on the patio? I think of Mrs Nolan\’s head as the snail shell crushed between my fingers and wonder if one blow would be enough.
Multiple blows would be inconsistent with a fall,
raising suspicions that could compromise the innocent image I\’m associated with throughout the village. I\’m reluctant to take such risk.

\nMy eyes narrow thoughtfully as I scan the tapestry of summer petalled foliage in the garden borders.



\nMrs Nolan\’s made a Victoria Sponge. She tells me it\’s to celebrate the Best Blooming Garden nomination,
but I can see her tired old heart\’s not in it. Nevertheless we\’re both playing along with her pointless charade, while it lasts.

\n\“Do have a slice before you go\,” she urges me. \“I\’ll wrap up an extra slice for you to take home.\”

\n\nWe\’re sat at her little kitchen table. I\’ve taken Mr Nolan’s chair as I\’m curious to see her reaction, but she doesn\’t comment.
She\’s adored my company since he\’s been gone- evidence of her lonely, pitiful existence.
My heart swells to think that soon I\’ll have released her from her misery.

\n\n\“Won’t you have any tea, Mercy?\” She looks quizzically over the top of her cup at my untouched one.

\n\n\“I\’m enjoying the delicious cake, Mrs Nolan.
\” I\’m certainly glowing with anticipation; not at the sickly slice on my plate, but to see beads of sweat break out on her forehead.

\n\nMrs Nolan raises a hand her heart, probably feeling some palpitations. “Mercy, you’ve been a rock over these last few weeks.
I don\’t know how I would have coped without you,\” she tells me earnestly.

\n\nA curious sensation passes through me; a brief flicker of guilt, possibly even doubt.
After all, it\’s not too late, is it? I push the inconvenient emotions away, remembering my role as gardener requires ruthless management of the weak and sickly, and I wait.

\n\nIt\’s all happening fast now. Panic creeps into Mrs Nolan\’s face as her heart begins to gallop like wild horses.
She gasps, reaches out a hand towards me but knocks my plate of cake onto the floor. Both smash into pieces on the tiles.

\n\nDigitalis Perurea, a cottage garden favourite commonly known as the foxglove,
is an excellent pollinator adding height and structure to summer borders. It\’s also highly toxic.
The foxgloves I propagated have been glorious this year, in my opinion outshining the dahlias by far.
From the unripe green seeds I\’ve ground a paste and steeped it in the tea that Mrs Nolan\’s poured from the pot.
Her cup stands empty on the table, white and fluted like the trumpet of a foxglove flower.

\n\nI watch closely and am certain Mrs Nolan experiences minimal pain as her racing heart outruns itself,
my face disappearing from her view as her vision blurs and darkens. At her age, no one will suspect a thing.



\n\nThe village shop door tinkles as I enter, and I wait patiently while Janet serves a child buying sweets from one of the large jars on the shelf.
I smile indulgently at the youngster who glances uneasily at me and takes a wary,
wide sidestep around me as he leaves- so strange that children often sense their vulnerability better than their adult counterparts.

\n\n\“Mercy! How are you bearing up?\” Janet is the picture of kind concern. \“Such a blow to hear about Miriam.
I heard you were there when she took poorly?”

\n\n\“It was terrible\” I murmur, eyes downcast. \“She’d never truly recovered from finding Mr Nolan in such a state.\”

\n\n\“It was the shock, wasn\’t it? And a broken heart. Maybe it\’s all for the best.\” Janet shudders before her bright demeanour returns.
\“What can I help you with?\”
\n\n\“Could I pop a note in the window, please? To let people know I\’m available for work.\”

\n\With Janet’s permission I take out from my bag the card I\’ve carefully written my number on and slide it into one of the plastic
sleeves hanging in the shop window. It\’s placed alongside local business cards and adverts for piano tuition and babysitting.

\n\nIn my neat, orderly cursive I\’ve written my number and a friendly message.
I’m confident there will be a good response, especially as the Best Blooming Garden award is still up for grabs.

\n\nDoes your garden need some love and care?

\n\nCall now for experienced help.

Just ask for Mercy.
</item>
        <item>

I gots a demon in me; that\'s what Mama used to say. Mama would always be telling me that demons are all over this world,
that they sneak up on little boys and girls and plant evil seeds in their heads that sprout and grow,
spreading around their souls like an infection. It kinda be like when you don\'t wash a part of open, scabby skin;
the spot around it starts to turn an ugly shade of yellow, then it gets sticky, and then you gots to clean it with a smelly,
\n\nburning liquid that leaves the gash looking dark brown for a moment.

\n\nMama swore that for demons the only medicine needed was prayer.
\"Keep your hands tight and close to your chest. Imagine they\'re chained, bound by your faith in the Lord.
Pray to him, my son, so that he may take your demon away.\"

\n\nBut my demon don\'t go away.
I see him in the shadows that bend all crooked like close to doorways.
And I\'m sure he hides in the bathroom mirror, tucking his slender body into the corners of the glass,
just waiting for me to look elsewhere so he can snatch me and pull me into his reverse world,
where the bad is very good, and the good is very bad.

\n\nI told Mama this; that he saw me brushing my teeth and spitting in the sink,
so she grabbed me by the ear, dragged me into the bathroom, turned on the lights, and pointed straight into the mirror.
\"Where\'s the demon?\" she asked. \"If he\'s here, then I want to see him.\"

\n\nBut the demon didn\'t show himself. \"You won\'t be able to see him, Mama,\" I said.

\n\n\"For heaven\'s sake,\" she yelled, letting her spit fly over to my cheeks.
She placed her hands on her hip and looked at me with her hair-raising eyes, the kind she always used before giving me a beating.
\"Why on Earth not?\"

\n\n\"Because Mama, he\'s invisible.\"

\n\nAnd so she burned my face with her hand, told me to go to my room and sleep.
\"Pray,\" she said, before having me leave the bathroom, \kneel by your bed and plea to the Lord so that he can take that demon,
only you seem to be able to see, away.\"

\n\nI put my knees on the ground, rested my elbows on my bed, kept my hands raised and my chin down.
I begged, \"Dear Lord,\" I sang, \"can you guide my demon, take him and forever keep me safe?\" Tears trickled down my face.
\"Please, I don\'t want him growing, taking over me like a weed, feeding on my fears, and making me think these awful things.\"

\n\nI said a Lord\'s Prayer: \"Our Father, who art in heaven, hallowed be thy name;
thy kingdom come; thy will be done on earth as it is in heaven.\"

\n\nI remembered Mama\'s words, her hand clutching the Rosary.
She often recited ten Hail Marys whenever she felt the need to clear her mind, so I did the same.
I didn\'t have any strings or beads, but I kept the number of the prayers alive in my head.
I started with ten, then added another prayer for the Lord, followed by another ten Hail Marys,
and repeated myself until my knees hurt and it was too hard to stand.


\n\nTen, that\'s how many times I blink as soon as I wake up.
I place my right foot on the cold ground first, followed by then my right.
Ten, that\'s how many times I pace from one end of my bedroom to the other before making my bed.
Ten, that\'s how many Hail Marys I pray before even thinking about leaving my room for breakfast.
Ten, that\'s how many steps I\'m supposed to take from the doorway down to the stairwell.
Ten, always ten; any more or any less, someone I love dies.



\n\n\"Good morning, Jude,\" Father Vincent says with his head turned to the stove, cooking up a pan of scrambled eggs.

\n\n\"Mornin\' Father Vincent\" I return.
I grab the kitchen chair by the top headrail, slide it out, back in,
then out again until its wooden legs are aligned perfectly with the floor\'s tiles.
I sit down and keep my arms off to the side because Father Vincent thinks it\'s impolite to place one\'s elbows on the table.

\n\n\"Sleep well?\"

\n\n\"Not really,\" I answer. \"I think I got about four hours of shut-eye.\"

\n\n\"How many?\"

\n\n\"How many what?\"

\n\n\"Hail Marys,\" he says, walking towards me with a smoking pan of eggs.

\n\nI see it. The disappointment riddled across Father Vincent\'s face.

\n\nThe eggs fly in the air.
The scorching pan strikes me square in the head. My body\'s now on the floor, my lips nearly kissing his feet,
his fist breaking my teeth. He laughs maniacally like a demon.

\n\n\"A hundred and ten,\" I answer.

\n\n\"A good night\'s sleep is super important, Jude. You can\'t go on living like this.
What\'s wrong with a hundred-nine, or even just ten.\"

\n\n\"Ten Hail Marys aren\'t enough.\"

\n\n\"And how do you know when it\'s enough.\"

\n\n\"I just know.\"


\n\nMama used to tell me that I was cursed. That a demon had latched onto my soul.
She\'d hear me talking to myself while pacing in my childhood bedroom.

\n\n\"Shut up,\" she\'d always yell. \"Go to sleep. What on Earth is wrong with you?\"

\n\n\"Nightmares,\" I\'d tell myself.
Nightmares that bloom and paint the black canvas of my eyes, pictures that break through the darkness of my headspace. He, my demon,
never ceases to trace vivid images of things I know are not true; he uses a set of ornate, fabricated lies as a front.
It\'s his way of keeping me terrified.


\n\nThe other boys are rounding up their plates and leaving the kitchen table.
They stand and grab their dirty dishes, forks, and napkins.
The chairs screech as some of them drag the legs back against the tiled floors.

\n\nOne boy plants himself in front of the sink while another rolls up the plastic placemats.
Another tall fellow scrapes everyones\' leftover food into the garbage.

\n\nThe kitchen is flooded with the sounds of scurrying footsteps, dishes clanking, water running out of the faucet.

\n\nThe boy rolling up the placemats beside me has a knife tucked under his sleeve.
He walks behind me, and the metallic tip shines from below his wrist.
He reveals his weapon seconds before the boy in front of the sink has any chance to escape.
He plunges the knife into the boy\'s gut. Blood seeps from the wound and trickles down his legs like piss. Everyone runs.
He looks to me, knife in hand and serrated teeth, grinning. I\'m next.

\n\n\"Hey Jude,\" the boy beside me asks, \"you gonna take much longer, or can I take your mat?\"

\n\n\"Huh? I don\'t know, just leave it with me. I\'ll put it away once I\'m done.\"


\n\nHe stares at the food on my plate, the pile of scrambled eggs looking like curdled cheese and the sausage patty symmetrically cut
into ten pieces.

\n\n\"Well, just make sure you finish eating before lunch,\" he answers, chuckling.
\"I swear, why the fuck do you take so long to eat?\"

\n\n\"WHAT DID I HEAR?\" Father Vincent fires, entering the kitchen.

\n\n\"Nothing,\" all the boys reply in unison as if Father Vincent had asked each and every one of them.

\n\n\"Jude here is just taking an eternity to eat again,\" the boy by the sink responds, with a water stain over the front of his shirt,
looking like an ink blotch. \"He\'s going to skimp out on helping us clean up again, Father V.\"

\n\n\"Tell you what,\" Father Vincent says.
\"How about you guys leave Jude and me to talk, and we\'ll clean up the kitchen by ourselves before lunch? Does that sound good?\"

\n\n\"Really?\" some of the boys gush in disbelief.

\n\n\"Yeah, yeah, just scram before I change my mind,\" and in a flash, the sound of excited running invades the space,
dissipating as each of the boys go upstairs or out through the front door to play in the yard.

\n\n\"Don\'t forget to dry them dishes,\" one of the boys mocks before leaving the kitchen behind.



\n\nSometimes I\'ll see Father Vincent on top of me, his robe draping down from his chest and swaying over my thighs.
The seamed edges of his gown will rub against my waist, expand and recede like the white scars that creep onto a sandy beach.

\n\nHe\'ll release a beastly sound, almost a tribal roar that\'ll echo and get absorbed into the sheets.
His breath hot over my face, his eyes fixate on the bulge of my neck right before killing me.



\n\n\"Jude, I\'m starting to get worried about you,\" Father Vincent says.
\"I know things haven\'t been easy for you since your arrival, but —\"

\n\n\"But what?\"

\n\n\"Your behavior,\" he says, \"it\'s not exactly something that I understand.\"

\"Don\'t worry, Father Vincent,\" I assure him. \"I\'m fine,\" I say, shining him a smile. \"It\'s no big deal.
I\'m great, see?\"

\n\n\"Come on, Jude, open up. You\'ve been here for eight months, and you still haven\'t told us much of anything.\"

\n\nFather Vincent pulls out a chair and sits across from me. He crosses his arms and places them over the table.

\n\n\"I thought you didn\'t like it when we did that?\"


\n\n\"Well, we\'re not eating now, are we?\" He returns. \"You want to know something?\"

\n\n\"What?\"

\n\n\"I have terrible table manners,\" he answers, laughing.
\"But the boys here need to know how to mind their manners if they ever intend to leave here. Honestly,
I\'m not much of a stickler for the rules.\"

\n\nI scan Father Vincent from head to hands,
notice his slouching, his head slightly arched forward as if at any moment he could jump over the table and grab me.

\n\nSo, he continues. I told you something about me, now how about you tell me something about yourself, Jude?

\n\nDo you really want to know?

\n\nLay it on me.

\n\nI have a demon.



\n\nI have a demon, one that can\'t be seen. He isn\'t noticeable like a shadow or a voice, he\'s silent like the air I breathe.
He speaks through thoughts and rituals, tasks that he can somehow force onto me.

\n\nI see him in the corridors, pushing me down the stairs or stretching his body from across the foot of my bed,
trying to make a grab for my legs.

\n\nI\'ll see him in what looks like dreams, strokes of light and color that occasionally bleed into reality. He\'ll take over a room,
the objects, the people around me, and sometimes even toy with my body.

\n\nThe rituals, I need to follow them, even if they seem like nonsense to me.
Tens, tens are sacred. Ten blinks, ten steps, ten prayers. I chew my food ten times on each side of my mouth.
I must wash my hands ten times on each side every time I go to the bathroom,
and I\'m not allowed to leave the space before looking at the mirror. I need to make sure he sees me;
he needs to be aware of each and every one of my performances.

\n\nHe knows everything about me. I need to make sure he\'s pleased. If he\'s ever unhappy, he\'ll do something terrible.

\n\nI pray every night for him to leave me.
Prayers in sets of tens. Ten Hail Marys between each Our Father, followed by cramping legs and burning knees.
This is probably the most valuable task among all the others.

\n\nOnce my eyes were heavy from such a tiring evening and a brutal beating that I fell asleep before completing my nightly ceremony.
That night, I woke up, and my demon had taken Mama away from me.



\n\nThere\'s a golden cross on the pulpit, glimmering from the chandelier basking the church in a warm, yellow glow.
Father Vincent told me to meet him here, \"We\'ll talk more after lunch,\" he said.

\n\nWe talked the entire time we cleaned the kitchen. Father Vincent asked me about everything that my demon had ever made me do.
I told him about the thoughts, the prayer, how Mama hit me each time I mentioned the demon.

\n\n\"And how do you know it\'s a demon?\" he asked.

\n\n\"Mama told me. She said my father had a demon too.
A kind that made him do crazy things. It forced him to go into drinking and make long cuts down his arms.
Mama said that my father had this thing with being clean and keeping everything in pristine condition.
He wouldn\'t touch certain things, and his demon only ever let him be when he was in church under the protection of the Lord.\"

\n\n\"I see. And what about you? Do you think your demon fears the Lord?\"
"I think so. I don\'t know. Maybe?\"
The doors from the entrance bang and echo through down the sea of benches.
Father Vincent walks down the aisle with a woman in a pencil skirt, a brown blazer, and turtle shell glasses.\"

\n\"Jude,\" Father Vincent begins, \"this is Dr. Wong.\"

\n\"Nice to meet you, Jude,\" she says, stretching out her arm. \"You can call me Lucy.\"

\nI stare at her wrinkled knuckles and the contouring lines of her palm and fingers.
\nI don\'t raise a finger to greet her, and so she retracts her hand.

\n\"A doctor?\"

\n\"Yes, Jude. Lucy here is a doctor and a dear old friend. I asked her to come down here to speak to you.\"

\n\"About what?\" I fire, looking to Father Vincent and then diverting my gaze to Lucy.

\n\"Well, let\'s say I think I can help you out, Jude. That is if you\'re willing to speak to me.\"

\n\"What do you mean?\" I return.

\"Vincent told me you have a demon. Is that correct?\"

\nI nod.

\n\"Tell me, how do you live with this demon?\"

\n\"I do what he wants. I try to keep things in order just the way he likes it. I also pray.\"

\n\"Does it always work?\"

\n\"Most of the time,\" I answer.

\n\"And how do you feel about that? About having to do all of these things?\"

\n\"Honestly? I feel pretty tired.\"

\n\"Anything else?\"

\n\"Shameful.\"

\nDr. Wong squats down beside the bench where I\'m sitting. Father Vincent takes a seat directly behind me.

\nWe want to see if we can offer you some relief, Jude.
A way to help you out that doesn\'t involve keeping you awake most of the night in prayer.

\nNO! I blurt out. \"I need to pray. Prayer is what keeps him at bay.\"

\nNo, Jude, it doesn\'t, Dr. Wong interjects. The truth is your demon isn\'t exactly the type that will simply go away like that.

\nWhat? But Mama said

\nWe know Jude,Father Vincent replies. But how about you talk to Dr. Wong for a bit. Tell her anything you want,
tell her everything you told me.

\nI look to Dr. Wong, her thin eyes bouncing back at me.

\nYou\'re a doctor, right? Am I sick?

\nLet\'s just say your demon isn\'t exactly what you think it is, she answers. Dr. Wong stands, rests her hand
on the arm of the church bench. \"Do you mind if I sit?\" she asks, pointing to the space beside me.

\nSure, I answer. One question, though?

\nAnd what\'s that?

\nDo you really think you can help me?
</item>

        <item>
  The night I got shot in the head: that\'s when I changed my mind.

\n\nThe Waypoint Diner was more like a hallway than a room. It was a place for coming and going, not for staying.
If you sat under the flickering fluorescent lamp and smelt the burning grease for too long, if you were too patient,
you would start to feel it: a hollowness, an unsteadiness, a sense that the diner itself was teetering on a pinhead.
Nobody made any sudden moves.

\n\nI tucked myself in on a red pleather stool at the end of the chromium counter, pinching an overstuffed laminate menu beneath my thumbs.
My order was always the same—cherry pie and a cup of black coffee—but I read the menu from start to finish anyway, dutifully,
as though it were scripture. You know, ye shall not order the milkshake. In a way it did have that kind of power;
I came to the Waypoint a hell of a lot more often than I came to church.
It had my kind of people, people that were content with silence when the world demanded that you be loud,
content with secrets when the world demanded that you come clean.

\n\nThe ceiling light above me shut off for a few seconds, and my stomach sank.
When it came back on, it flickered faster than before, almost strobe-like.
I looked up at the dead horse flies on the other side of the beveled plastic pane,
and silently condemned them for dying in such an inconvenient spot. How did they even get in there? I wondered.
You would think they could tell the difference between the sun and not-the-sun.
They\'d worshiped a false idol, God forgive them.

\n\nI was beginning to get frustrated with the lack of service when, after no warning whatsoever, my left arm felt wooden.
I thought of lots of words surrounding, but never touching, \'heart attack.\'
I assured myself over and over that this was just like the last dozen times, that it was all in my head. There was a dilemma.
On one hand, I didn\'t want to take a stupid risk by toughing it out. On the other, I couldn\'t foot another ambulance bill.
I just had to wait and see, shivering, breathing shallow breaths.
I thought back to a teensy spliff I had smoked earlier in the evening, and decided to push the blame in that direction.

\n\nIn. Out. In. Out. In. In. In. Wait, shit. Out.

\n\nAt the Waypoint, there was an unspoken rule about leaving things unspoken.
I didn\'t want to make a spectacle of myself, but I couldn\'t trust my own thoughts anymore.
I needed noise. I needed to hear someone else\'s voice.

\n\nA disheveled gentleman sat a few stools down. I hopped down from mine and slid into the one neighboring his.
\"Hello,\" I think I said. It didn\'t feel like I said it. It spilled out of me, like water from an overfull pitcher.

\n\nThe man\'s eyes were a little far apart for my liking, but he seemed sane enough.
He wore bluish coveralls and a small white name tag which read J-A-K-E. \"Can I help you?\" he asked, a little curtly.
I could understand why.

\n\n\"The thing is,\" I explained, \"As sad as it is to say, I haven\'t spoken a word to anyone in months. And the longer it\'s gone on,
the more I\'ve had this feeling, like... like I\'m losing my grip on reality?\"

\n\nJake licked the front of his top row of teeth and nodded.

\n\n\"Things will get better,\" he said, the night I got shot in the head.



\n\nThe waitress, Kelly, finally arrived with two cups of coffee. Jake stirred in an ungodly amount of Splenda,
and we sat side by side, taking sips and watching the clock. Time seemed to be passing by more quickly than usual. I was distracted.

\n\nDistracted by that stench...

\n\nThe hairs on the back of my neck stood on end. I turned around to follow the feeling.
There adorning the corner booth was a small, sallow-cheeked girl. She was ever so still,
with blue lips and dark half-moons beneath unflitting eyes. Horse flies buzzed about her person. Another dying light.

\n\n\"Don\'t look at that,\" Jake said.

\n\n\"Okay,\" I replied. For the moment, he was my anchor. I would honor his words.

\n\nHe drummed his fingers on the counter. \"They could at least bring the toast out. Is the wait always this bad?\"

\n\n\"No, not always. Maybe we caught the cook on a smoke break or something.\"

\n\n\"Any longer, I might could gnaw the meat off your arm.\"

\n\n\"I know, right?\"

\n\n\"Tell you what,\" Jake said, standing. \"While we wait, how\'s about some music?\"
He walked over to the jukebox, pushed in a couple of quarters, and pressed a button.
The machine whirred to life, and Louis Armstrong croaked.

\n\nGive your heart and soul to me / and life will always be / la vie en rose

\n\nI wanted to tell him to turn it off, that we should keep it down. I bit my tongue, but I think the effort showed.

\n\n\"What\'s wrong?\" he asked me.

\n\n\"Nothing,\" I said. \"I love this song.\"

\n\n\"Me too.\"

\n\nJake took a sip of coffee and winced. He swallowed carefully, then pulled a long brown hair through his lips.
That\'s when I noticed that his tongue was forked.

\n\n\"Your,\" I mumbled. \"Your tongue.\"

\n\n\"I served some time,\" he said. \"Lot of fellas in the clink who don\'t mind rapin\' ya but draw the line at deviltry.
God\'s all they got left, you know, even if they don\'t think they deserve him.
I decided I\'d rather have my ass kicked than... whatever else they were planning on doing to it. Got tatted up, too.\"

\n\nJake pulled down his collar to reveal a pair of faded horns on his collarbones, then lifted one sleeve to show off a crooked swastika.

\n\nOh dear, I thought. I am definitely too high for this.

\n\n\"Say what you want about them skinheads,\" he said. \"Their prison protection package is c-c-c-comprehensive.\"

\n\n\"I bet,\" I replied. I wasn\'t sure what else to say.

\n\nA pair of men wearing tan jackets walked into the Waypoint and sat down at a booth. La Vie En Rose started to play again.
It seemed louder this time.

\n\n\"Don\'t worry,\" Jake continued.
\"I ain\'t a racist or nothing. As a matter of fact, I used to make license plates with a fella named Javier.\"

\n\nI was hardly listening. The words registered, but not their meaning.
I wanted to hear what the two newcomers were talking about, but the brassy lilts of Louis\' trumpet put a rift between us.
Meanwhile Jake droned on, and on....

\n\n\"Wait, what?\" I said. \"Can you repeat that last part?\"

\n\n\"Really? Alright. So, ever since I got out, I\'ve had a hard time getting work. For all the obvious reasons.
I\'ve been working at an auto shop, but it ain\'t paying the bills the way I thought. So I came here to rob the place.
But the minute I stepped inside, I lost my nerve. Just like that,\" he said, snapping.
\"Something a little off about this here diner, don\'t you think?\"

\n\n\"Yes. I do think.\"

\n\nFinally, Kelly burst through the swinging kitchen door and dropped off two plates.
Jake\'s held some slightly burnt eggs, bacon, and buttered toast. Salivating, I looked down at my plate.
It held a wet yellow sponge and a little silver dip cup full of what looked—and smelled—like dish soap.

\n\nI felt disoriented.
Was I supposed to clean something? I turned around and looked at the dead girl in the corner.
The number of flies had increased tenfold, and they buzzed, such that I could hardly think.

\n\n\"Don\'t look at that,\" said one of the tan-jacketed men, projecting his voice to cut through the commotion.

\n\n\"Right,\" I said, returning my gaze to the sponge. \"What am I supposed to do with this?\"

\n\n\"Clean your plate,\" Jake replied matter-of-factly, his mouth stuffed with egg. \"It\'s considered polite.\"

\n\n\"Something is terribly wrong,\" I said, the night I got shot in the head.



\n\nSome time later, the jukebox started skipping.

\nGive your heart and soul to me /

\nGive your heart and soul to me /

\nGive your heart and soul to me /

\nAnd I might have complied, if I thought there was something to give.

\n\nOne of the men in tan jackets stood up and reached into his waistband.
He drew a pistol, aimed it at the jukebox, and opened fire.

\n\nThe first shots were not what I thought they would be.
They were loud, certainly, but something about them was phony, as if they had come from a child\'s cap gun.
This could not really be happening, not to me. The music stopped, but the man kept firing, and the shots rang louder, louder, LOUDER.
When he finished, I could hear nothing at all.

\n\nThe Waypoint Diner was meant for coming and going, not for staying. I had to get out.

\n\nI shook my head violently and dug into my ears, trying to remove whatever blockage there was, but my hearing would not return to me properly.
I had no sense of what Jake was shouting at the men, nor what they were shouting back. I could not hear the scratchy sound of my sponge against the plate, no matter how closely I leaned in to listen.

\n\nI could only hear horse flies buzzing.

\n\nI turned around to look at the dead girl. Very little was left of her.
I called out, but could not hear my own voice. I could not even feel it vibrating in my throat.

\n\nHorse flies rose from the booth in a blurring black cloud.
As I opened my mouth to shout, they shot towards me in a horrible beam. Some crashed against the back of my throat, choking me.
Some wedged themselves under my eyelids and crawled into my skull.
Even after everything went black, I could feel them there, sawing their little forelimbs, greedily feasting on the last light I had left to give.

\n\nI begged for mercy.

\n\nThick fingers hooked into my lower jaw and yanked it down, making way for cold metal.
I felt a jolt as the pistol went off, and then I felt nothing.

\n\nMy last thoughts were of cherry pie. I remember that much.

\n\nI awoke in a seated position, propped up in an adjustable hospital bed.
There was a hell of a lot of bandaging and plastic apparatuses situated around my face.
I tried not to move too fast. It felt like my ears were stuffed with cotton, but I could hear a quiet beeping in the corner.
My head ached something serious, and it got worse when I tried to move.
I gagged on a tube that must have run all the way through me from top to bottom.

\n\nA little while later the nurses extubated me, stuck me with a new IV, and carried away a sloshing bedpan.
As soon as they finished, a doctor named Feeney appeared at my side. She was a stern-looking woman. Not mean, but distant.

\n\n\"What\'s up, doc?\" I asked. A whisper seemed to be the most I could manage.

\"What\'s up\," she said, \"is that you\'re very lucky to be alive.\"

\"How do you mean? I had the craziest dream....\"

\"Do you remember going to the Waypoint Diner?\"

\"I go there all the time, so.\"

\"Good. Do you remember what happened there?\"

\"The... the lights were especially horrible... and then
there was this poor little girl... and a man out of prison... and... the flies... these huge horse flies... they\'re inside me,\" I said,
clawing at my face and chest, drawing blood. \"They\'re inside me,\" I said, as loud as I could this time.
The act sent a searing pain through my neck and jaw.

The nurses returned, this time restraining my wrists and ankles to the bed.
I tried to shake loose, but the pain was too much to bear.

\"Try to relax,\" the doctor said calmly. \"Really think about it. What did you do?\"

\"I... I don\'t remember doing anything. I ordered pie... and coffee... and I said hello to a man. Jake.\"

\"No, you didn\'t. You bit him.\"

\"What? No, no. Why would I bite him?\"

\"You were as high as a kite. THC, alcohol, maybe more. We\'re still waiting on the results, but I\'d put my money on methamphetamine at least.
Now, a mixture like that, you're bound to hallucinate.
It\'s not impossible that you didn\'t even realize what you were doing; that\'s something I suspect you\'ll want to bring up with your lawyer.
But here's the fact: you bit a chunk clean out of a man's shoulder.\"

\"Then what happened to me?\" I asked.

\"The man you attacked, \'Jake\': he put a gun in your mouth and fired. The bullet tore clean through your soft palette.
All I can say is, you\'re lucky you didn\'t attack someone with better aim. He missed everything vital.\"

\"Sorry, I don\'t understand.\"

\"For your sake, I hope that\'s true.
There were a couple of off-duty officers on the scene who saw everything and tried to break it up.
Of course, ex-cons aren\'t too keen on hearing what cops have to say, so things escalated.
I shouldn\'t tell you this but... ah, well. You ought to know. One of the officers got shot in the neck, like you.
It\'s looking like he won\'t make it.
The other one, winged. And \'Jake,\' he took a bullet through each of his lungs. Drowned in the back of an ambulance.\"

The heart monitor beside me was hypnotizing, a digital metronome. The regularity of it was disconcerting; it meant I wasn't dreaming.

\"So... what happens now? What am I supposed to do?\"

\"You\'ll have plenty of time to think about it,\" said Feeney. \"My suggestion? Count your damn blessings. And get sober.\"

The doctor turned heel and walked out of the room, disappearing into a hallway lit by flickering fluorescent lights.

Get sober, I thought. Just like that?

I tried to remember what the twelve steps were. A lot of them had to do with God; that I remembered.
I used to wonder, what\'s the point of pushing all your shit onto someone you don\'t really believe exists? I found it absurd.

The night I got shot in the head: that's when I changed my mind.

Next to God, I am no more or less important than a fly, than any creature.
It could all be a delusion—probably is, actually—but His forgiveness is the only one I have, and it gives me something worth living up to.
He cares more about me than I do, so I figure, why not let Him?

It\'s as simple as this: I would rather die on the other side of the beveled plastic than under my own boot.


</item>

        <item>

Kensington Park was the kind of place that was photographed for newsletters, where every pearly
white shuttered home had grass of no more than a height of one inch.
The small, close knit town rallied around their local high school, and everyone knew everyone.
In a town full of bake sales, coffee shops, and football games,
no one could have suspected the darkness that would soon consume this perfect little town.
Rainden high school housed every walk of life you could imagine, the jocks, the school nerds, the band geeks,
the goths, the cheerleaders, and the gamers.

\n\nThe interactions between them were as you would expect and as you would see in any teenage drama movie.
\“Are you going to Jameson\’s party on Friday?\” Francesca asked her best friend as she put on lipstick in the girls 3rd floor bathroom.
Odessa, a skinny cheerleader with blonde curls flowing in all sorts of directions blew out smoke from a Newport 100 and replied,
\“I guess so Frankie, as long as Dean is going to be there.\”

\n\n\“He will be Dessi, you slut!\” Odessa put out her cigarette, sprayed her perfume,
and the girls laughed as they left and walked towards their least favorite class, math.\n
As they took a seat, another group was discussing the same party towards the back of the room.\n
\“Another Jameson party, where the pity invite comes our way,
just so we can sit in the corner and pretend to like these people, let\'s just stay home and play minecraft.
I\’m working on a brand new farm\” Nico said.\n
\“I still want to go anyway, maybe we can actually make a new friend,\” Marnie said hopefully.\n
Three p.m came around and the school doors burst open as if the students were running for their lives.
Little did they know, the curse that would land upon this town would have these \“innocent\” children running for their lives.
It was mid October, and a chill rolled through the town as the weekend approached.

\n\nAt nighttime, the streets of Kensington Park were usually quiet, almost to an eerie decibel.
The noise occurred behind closed doors. To the world, these families were just as perfect as the town.
To each other, the problems were swept under the rug and would soon runneth over.\n
It was Friday night, and everyone was getting ready for Jameson\’s party in their own way.\n
Frankie was tearing apart her closet trying to find the perfect dress long enough to hide the scars on her upper thighs.
Francesca Mione was one of the \“populars\”, a beautiful cheerleader captain.

\n\nEveryone wanted to be her friend, or at least everyone felt like they needed to be her friend for a chance at an upgrade in social status.
You could easily get lost in her tremendous brick home, which often made her feel lonely, although you would never know it.
Francesca\’s mom and dad usually kept to themselves and their work and came out to show their love for their daughter when it was necessary.
In other words, when they were on display in the town.

\n\nThe only one Frankie really loved was her best friend Odessa.\n
Dessi understood Frankie, but even Dessi didn\’t know about the scars that ravished the perfect canvas that was Francesca Mione.
She discovered the blade in 9th grade, the time she started to notice just how alone she felt in the world.
How nothing she could do seemed perfect enough to fill that void of a family.\n
She often wished that she didn\’t have the parents that she did.\n
She needed to feel something, and so she did.\n
Frankie rolled her eyes, threw on some tights, a low cut dress, and some silver high heels.
\“Go ahead Dess, your turn to raid my closet,\” Frankie said as she headed towards the mirror to check her hair one more time.
\“Oh come on, Frankie, like you even need to check your hair.\n
It\’s always perfect,\” Odessa said as she looked hopelessly through her best friend\’s closet.\n
Odessa Trakos was also known to be popular, but usually in the shadow of her best friend Frankie.\n
As mentioned earlier, Odessa smoked any chance she could get.\n
While she thought this tamed her anxiety, it only fueled it to great magnitudes.\n
She always had a fire under her feet and was never satisfied where she was, she longed to escape her reality whenever she could.\n
Dessi loved Frankie too, but even best friends withhold truths.\n
The girls hopped on their bikes and headed towards the Jameson residence,
with a six pack each in tow.

\n\nDean, a defensive end for the Rainden Rattlesnakes, arrived at Jameson\'s with his bottle of Bacardi,
donning his letterman jacket and perfectly gelled hair.\n
Jameson, another blonde haired spectacle, turned on the music and motioned to
Dean to set the alcohol amongst the copious amounts that were already there.\n
\“So whatcha thinking man, you gonna get with Odessa tonight?\” Jameson inquired.\n
\“Psh I mean I can get that anytime I want, that girl is practically begging for it.\n
If I do that, then you have to try with Frankie,\” Dean said with chauvinistic confidence.\n
The doorbell rang, Jameson yelled, \“IT\’S OPEN,\” and then whispered to Dean, \“Let the games begin\”.
Meanwhile, two blocks over on Carol Court, Marnie was yelling at Nico to hurry up and put the finishing touches on his minecraft farm,
so they could head to the party. Marnie Teller, wasn\’t exactly part of the popular crowd,
however everyone always got invited to Jameson\’s parties.\n
It was almost as if the town was begging for drama or anything remotely interesting to happen.\n
Marnie Teller was a hopeful 11th grader, trying to expand her friend group beyond Nico who didn\’t see anything wrong with just having one friend.\n
Marnie grew up next door to Nico, so they were practically built as best friends.\n
Although, some have speculated that Nico felt more.\n
However, Marnie never picked up on those feelings.

\n\nShe always had her eyes set on some football player, but always ended up night after night sleeping next to Nico, platonically of course.\n
Marnie and Nico knew they would always have each other no matter what.\n
Would this curse upon this perfect little town be the final straw to tear them apart?
Marnie and Nico swiftly took two liquor bottles out of Nico\’s parents\' cabinet and headed to the party.\n
All the familiar party festivities were happening, drinks being spilled, tongues and spit being exchanged,
body parts rubbing against each other on the dance floor, all inhibitions gone.\n
Drew the drug dealer made his appearance late as usual.\n
Drew Wells always came to the parties although he never really got close to anyone, only for \“business\”.
Drew was making his way through the dark, smoky hall, when he was grabbed by Odessa, with mascara running down her face.
His usual response was to keep stone faced and not play into any emotion of a possible customer.\n \“What can I do for ya,\” he said to a panicked Dessi.
\“I don\’t know, I just don\’t know, I need anything, fucking strong!\” Odessa said in between gasps for breath and tears.\n
Drew and Desi stepped into one of the many rooms in Jameson’s house and he handed her a bag with a little blue pill.\n
\“What do I owe you?\” Desi said, rummaging through her purse.\n
\“Ya know, it\’s on me,\” Drew said, almost shocking himself as he said it. Then Drew did something even more out of character.
\“What\’s the matter?\” he said.\n
Desi popped the pill and laid down on the floor, \“Dean is what\’s the matter,
why am I just not good enough?\” \“Oh Ms. Trakos, please don\’t tell me you are wasting your tears over someone with the IQ of a rock.\”
At this comment, Desi laughed and looked at Drew, almost as if it were the first time.\n
Why was she throwing herself at Dean, practically taking her clothes off for him, just to be rejected.\n
He joined her on the floor, and they started to smoke countless cigarettes, and talk about their favorite bands, aliens, and what inspired them.
Downstairs, Nico was wallflowering himself while he watched Marnie desperately try to capture the attention of Jameson.\n
Frankie was in her usual spot by the shots table, doing what she could to become the popular drunk girl they all expected her to be.
Then it happened, an ear splitting sound that could only be described as something you hear in death,
spread throughout the party and the lights departed from the lamps, and soon from this perfect little town.\n
The panic set in slowly, just as everyone was pushing each other to find the nearest exit, the lights came back on.\n
Only everyone knew that something was different, the party that was happening before the lights went out,
was not the same party that was occurring now.\n
Although they all had this same sinking feeling in their stomachs, they partied till they couldn\’t anymore.\n
Everyone went home or passed out in their usual holes.\n



\n\nThe sun rose on the quiet town that was Kensington Park, but was covered by a cluster of gray, ominous clouds.
Marnie opened her eyes, and looked to her left expecting to find Nico drooling. Only Nico wasn\’t there. She got up, looked around.
Everything was different, her room was different, almost empty. She felt different, like half of her was gone.
Unable to shake this feeling, she ran downstairs, and out of her ripped screen door.\n
\“Where is Nico\’s house?\” she screamed, holding her hands to her head. \“NICOOOOOO,\” she started to panic.
Nico\’s house was gone, almost as if it never existed. Only, she knew it had, once upon a time.\n
She looked around Carol Court, and the uneasy feeling started to grow.\n
The once perfectly manicured block was now something she did not recognize.\n
Mrs. Laken, who always was dolled up with the perfect makeup, was now sitting on her porch,
her eye a deep purple and green, her face drawn and pale.\n
Marnie always heard Mr. and Mrs. Laken fighting, but the way she was always so chipper and so put together,
Marnie didn\’t recognize the woman. Marnie started running, sweating down the block until she reached what looked like a cemetery.
This had never existed here before, what was happening.\n
She was running when she tripped over a cement marble headstone. \“Here lies Nico Torren, 1960-1976\” Marnie fell over at the sight of this.\n
It felt like her soul was taken from her body.\n
The sky got darker, and a unrecognizable, demonic voice came into existence, \“Marnie, welcome to your personal hell,
you wanted to run away from the love Nico gave you, now feel his loss forever.\”

\n\nThree blocks over on Henderson Street, Frankie woke up to liquid dripping down her arms.
Once she fully opened her eyes, she let out a blood curdling scream.\n
She was covered in blood.\n
The scars that once hid underneath a pair of tights had now covered her entire body.\n
\“SOMEBODY HELP ME!!\” She screamed as she ran through the empty, almost haunted house that she had once called home.
Blood splattered an artistic masterpiece upon the cream colored walls.\n
She started to come to the realization that this blood was not hers.\n
She ran outside, begging for anyone in what seemed like a lifeless town, to help her.\n
She stumbled upon a cemetery, where broken pieces of cement lay in a pile.\n
She frantically started to pull them apart,
\“Here lies Nancy Mione and Fred Mione\” Red spray paint across their names tagged with \“Worst parents ever\” She screamed,
knowing in her heart that it was her who had committed this unspeakable act.\n
The sky got darker, and a unrecognizable,
demonic voice came into existence, \“Francesca, your deep desire for a family drove you to murder the only family you had.\n
You are incapable of having one, welcome to your personal hell!\”

\n\nDessi woke up out of her blue pill fantasy haze, and seemed to feel better than she had in a long time.\n
That was, until she walked out of her room.\n
Panic started to set in, her breaths got shorter, she started to feel faint, and dropped to her knees.\n
All over her skin, were the words she had drilled into her mind over the years. Accept me, look at me, love me, fuck me, pay attention to me.\n
She frantically tried to wash them off her skin, only to find how permanently written they were.\n
She ran outside, and the sky got darker, and an unrecognizable, demonic voice came into existence, \“Odessa,
all you ever wanted was to be loved in the wrong way, now you must show the world how you so desperately feel,
welcome to your personal hell!\”

\n\nYou see, Kensington Park was the perfect little town.
All of these problems were hidden under dresses, inside anxious minds, behind closed doors and closed eyes.\n
This demonic presence that had descended upon Kensington forced all of these fears and realness out into the open.\n
The real Kensington Park came out to play.\n
The hold that this darkness had on this quaint little town would not be given up without a fight.\n
The question is, how will a town full of bake sales, coffee shops and football games ever recover?
</item>

        <item>

Two kids sitting in a brick wall, smoking, laughing, and listening to music. Coffee nights and slumber parties. Movies and drinks after an awful week. That’s what Joe meant to me. I still remember how terribly sad I was when we first met and how terribly alone he felt.

\n\nI’m not sure I can ever forget him, even though the face of my once best friend is blurry in my mind. I remember the black hair, the pale skin that reddened with too much sun or without on the cold days. I remember how tall he was and how we could talk about nothing and everything.

\n\nJoe died three weeks ago, but for me, he had been dead for years.

\n\nWe had been mad at each other for a few months, almost a year. I thought it would eventually go away and we would go back to the happy best friends we had always been. That we’d find some common ground. He didn’t like that I belittled my efforts to get out of the city, and I didn’t like that he always chose to stay in it, even when he could go away. Our city was a horrible place, but it was all Joe knew.

\n\nFor a couple of years, I guess we both could see the end coming, but we looked the other way.

\n\nRight after I moved countries and left our two-bedroom apartment, that’s when it started. Whenever I came to visit, I stayed in my old room, now re-baptized as the “guest room”. On a specially warm December when I came to visit my parents, I also paid a visit to my old friend.

\n\n‘Look at it’ Joe said revealing a tiny orb of onyx with words inscribed in it ‘isn’t it beautiful?’

\n\nI looked at the sphere but didn’t touch it. It looked beautiful indeed, but there was something else, something evil about it, or rather untrustworthy.

\n\n‘Where did you find it?’

\n\n‘Oh, we have been excavating this site for a while and they said I could have it’

\n\n‘I’m not sure the museum would be okay with that’ I suggested ‘you want another beer?’ I said on my way to the fridge. The apartment was weird now. Joe had made a couple of changes to the room, there was a new couch, my old room was now the TV room and outside the window a big blue and white screen shone upon us, advertising toothpaste and junk food.

\n\n‘Okay, they don’t know it exists, but hey, I deserve nice stuff too’ he said ‘no thanks’ he answered as I took a beer.

\n\n‘How are things with Ali?’ I asked to change the conversation. He sighed ‘Not good then?’

\n\n‘She’s fine…’ his voice trembled ‘she won’t do it again, she promised this time would be…’

\n\n‘What?!’ I snapped ‘come man you can’t keep…’

\n\n‘I don’t care really, we all make mistakes, right?’ he said trying to sound happy, but his face was far from it.

\n\n‘Not for the third time’ I whispered.

\n\n‘What’s that supposed to mean?!!’ Joe snapped.

\n\nI stopped listening for a second, drawn in concern.

\n\n‘Don’t give me that look’ he said.

\n\n‘What look?’

\n\n‘Like I’m crazy’

\n\n‘Hey, what do you think about this beer I bought? It’s good isn’t it?’ I tried to change the conversation.

\n\n‘I love her,’ Joe admitted ‘she’s not that bad’

\n\n‘Fine’ I said. ‘I just want you to be happy’

\n\nIt would take a while before we met again, he knew how much I disliked Ali and her occasional cheating. She was not a bad person, but I couldn’t say they were good for each other. He would become depressed or angry when this happened and she said she would never do it again, then after everything was fine, Joe would avoid her and ignore her for weeks. He always hated listening to my opinion, so I tried not to give it.

\n\nA year passed by and I returned for another warm December at my parents’ house. On my last night, we had a big fight, one of those you can only have with someone who you have known for a very long time. It’s funny, the worst fights are the ones that never seem to make sense, I swear I don’t remember why we fought, only fragments of it, all I knew is that he had started it and that he was going to finish it!

\n\nBut he never contacted me, so we never talked again. I never heard from him, he was, as good as dead.

\n\nI must have received a thousand calls from my boss on the day he died for real. So when I was just returning home to my puppy, a Labrador retriever, and I was finally free of all the madness on the telephone, I decided not to answer it anymore. My cellphone must have rung about a dozen times before someone decided to leave a voicemail. It struck me as something important then, so I listened to it.

\n\nIt was Laura, Joe’s mother. She couldn’t speak properly, her voice trembled and broke at uneven times, and you even could hear the tears coming out of her words.

\n\n‘It’s Joseph,’ she finally managed, ‘he’s dead’

\n\nMy heart sank. Dead? No, of course not, he couldn’t be, dead. I fell to the floor and started crying, the baby Labrador, Leo, came running to my side. He, he couldn’t be dead. That was the worst night I’d ever had.

\n\nI didn’t fully believe it until I saw him in the casket. He wore his usual combed black hair, a long beard, and his brown leather jacket. It was him without a doubt, he was dead and there was nothing I could do.

\n\nWhen they heard about Joe’s demise, the museum he used to work on send their condolences, alongside a request to his mother about a missing artifact. Laura wouldn’t dare to visit his old apartment again. Not since she found him lying dead on his bed, with blood all over the carpet. She asked me to go instead, I could take anything I wanted and if I was lucky, look for the damn sphere.

\n\nI walked down the dim-lit corridors of the city streets the next afternoon until I reached the huge apartment complex where he used to live. The automatic door was locked so I had to press a button to call for the guard to come to open up.

\n\nHe took a few minutes to arrive, and every damn second he did my discomfort grew bigger and louder, like an express hot pot. What was I doing there? Joseph… we hadn’t talked in years… and now his mother wanted me to collect his stuff? To look for that damn piece of onyx? This didn’t feel okay, but there was I, diving into the mud one last time for Joe. Just like I used to when we were teens.

\n\nThe outside facade of the building unnerved me. It was a wreck, the paint was old and stained, peeling down. The automatic glass doors wore scratches, like scars, and the lights were out. It used to be a yellow building, with lots of light and nice glass doors. I wondered where all that had gone.

\n\nThe guard opened up and guided me to the tiny apartment. He opened the door and left, running like a mouse being hunted by a cat. As soon as I stepped in I understood why the guard had left in such a hurry, the place smelled like rotting food and decay, like a stagnant feeling of the putrid coming for you. There was no light but I tiny ray of dying sunshine that filtered through the curtains. I went into the dark, blindfolded, naked.

\n\nI tried to reach for the lights but the power was out. So I opened the curtains, and the window and let the fresh air rush in along with the sound of traffic.

\n\nThe place was no better on the inside, if anything, it looked messier. There was food on the walls and broken, dirty dishes on the ground. Clothes were left behind all over the place and a briefcase was vomiting books and socks. I knelt over the things, it seemed to me, like someone was in a rush to leave.

\n\nA loud noise made me jump, and my heart beat fast. The door closed at the same time cold air filtered through the window. ‘A ghost’ I thought for a second, but of course, it was a stupid thing to think.

\n\nI looked around the living room. A rush of laughter came to my memory. Old pop songs and indie music, the smell of beer and smokes. I looked at the table where Joe and I used to sit down, drinking and smoking the night away. Talking about nothing, yet talking about everything.

\n\nIt had been a long time since I left that tiny apartment, but somehow I felt like looking at a broken home, a place that used to feel safe and soothing, now torn apart by time and lost love. I used to know the exact time of the evening when the bus stopped outside the building complex and people would get out and cars would start shouting that they couldn’t get out in that part of the street, I used to know how to do the coffee in Joe’s old french press so that it wouldn’t stick or get bitter. I even got used to the blue light of that screen outside! But now everything looked different, strange… unfamiliar. The cars made no noise and the giant screen now projected a flashy annoying red light.

\n\nMy favorite part was the guest room, aka the TV room aka my old room. That’s where I used to stay whenever I didn’t want or couldn’t return to my parents’ house, way before I even moved in. ‘Stay, that way I can pay you all of what you’ve done for me’ Joe would say ‘you don’t have to pay me back. You’re my brother,’ I’d say. I still wonder, where did all the kindness we had of each other go to?’

\n\nI carefully reviewed the living room, the kitchen and the guest room. I made a list of everything in every room. I even took photos with my phone and all. I felt like an intruder, checking on the drawers, the book stands, and shelves. I was looking for stolen property, looking for memories, photographs, or something that reminded me of my lost friend, but all I ever found were the thousands of books I had gifted him. Most of them remained unopened and that made me sad, for he had lost the opportunity to live through other eyes, through visiting other worlds.

\n\nI saved his bedroom for the last. I didn’t want in, every time I looked at the door I felt a chill running down my spine. His mother found him half dead unable to do anything to save him, blood spilling out of his left arm that had stained the white carpet as if it were a canvas. I was sure the red oils would still be there and that I would be able to make up his silhouette. I’d have to get inside eventually, but I avoided it for as long as I could.

\n\nIt was a long night, after all, everything I was at the moment was a robber trying to find something valuable, but not wanting inside the obvious place it would be in. I half slept on the couch in the TV room. Voices kept coming to me, happy ones, reproaching ones, songs, and white noise.

\n\nAt two am I heard a noise, coming in from the main room. At first, it startled me and gave me goosebumps, it even filled my heart with unnatural pain. I wanted to run, but it was time. I approached the door and opened it wide.

\n\nAn empty bedroom greeted me.

\n\nThere was a closet, an old tiny TV and books spilled all over. The bed had its white sheets spread around the room, still stained with blood.

\n\n‘Shit, Joe!’ I shouted ‘why would you…’

\n\nIt took me a while to make up my mind, I wanted to leave, never to return. I couldn’t though, not if this was to be the last thing I did for Joe, or his mother anyway. I looked in the closet and the drawers of the TV room.

\n\nNothing, not even in the toilet’s water tank.

\n\nThe sun was coming up when something hit my left foot. It was the onyx sphere sliding itself through the room.

\n\n‘What are you?’ I asked closing in on it. I reached my hand to take it and leave. But the tiny ball was more untrustworthy than ever. I reached for a napkin and a cloth and I grabbed them. The thing violently moved and tried to escape my hands, it tossed me to the sides until I realized it.

\n\n‘Fine’ I said ‘I don’t know what the hell you are, but you leave me alone’

\n\nI felt as if a bucket of ice pierced me. The sphere or that thing, whatever it was, started shaking from the other side of the room. It stopped looking at me and looked at something behind me. I swear I could see a lonely gruesome eye on it. I turned around to see what grabbed its attention.

\n\nA white, translucent figure appeared before me. Combed hair and a long beard. Dressing in old clothes but wearing a distinctive leather jacket above them. He looked sadly at me and to the floor.

\n\n‘I’m sorry’ we both spoke at the same time.

\n\nI laughed and shed some tears ‘I should have called’ I said

\n\n‘And I should have been less on an asshole’ Joe answered.

\n\n‘You alright? Wherever you are?’ I wanted to know.

\n\n‘I’ve been better and I’ve been worse’ he raised a white spectral finger and touched my forehead.

\n\nAnd I saw it. I saw the forests and the deserts. I saw my grandmother and the times when she was a kid. I heard the noise of the downstairs avenue and then I saw two lost kids in the middle of a strange city, two brothers, but one was gone.

\n\n‘That thing, it did this to you?’

\n\nJoe nodded.

\n\n‘I’m gonna miss you too’ his ghost answered.

\n\n‘Don’t worry, we won’t let it take you too’ his voice changed, it turned cold and lifeless. At the sound of these spectral words, a thousand ghosts filled the room, all wearing clothes from other time periods, some talking, some looking as if they just woke up. They all had cuts on their wrists, just like Joe’s.

\n\n‘So you didn’t?’ I asked.

\n\n‘I don’t think I did’ Joe answered ‘you must go’

\n\nI walked to the door

\n\n‘Take this,’ Joe said, handing me his journal, some old photographs and his favorite pen.

\n\n‘This might help,’ I said and gave him the ankh around my neck. I never took it off.

\n\n‘Goodbye, Joe’ I said as I opened the door.

\n\n‘Goodbye, Em,’ he said with a smile.

\n\nThe door closed behind me and I left the building.

\n\nA long time passed before I dared talk about that night or before I understood what happened, what it all meant. At least I got to see my friend for the last time.
</item>

        <item>

I needed this apartment, not for me, but for my mind.
I didn\’t push her, she fell.
The demolishing was said to start at 1030 on the dot so I decided to miss work to witness its demise.
Actually, I haven\’t been to work in over five years.
At 4 am I arose from a restless night.
Unable to sleep I decided to start my day, washes of memory flood my mind and drench me with mortification. She wanted to die.

\n\nWhen I was growing up, I always wanted to live across the street in the beautiful \“Casa del Mar\”, but more so after the incident.
She deserved what she got.
My friends and I would marvel over the residents of Casa del Mar—they were high class in our book.
Their clothes glimmered in the light every time they stepped out of their cars.
Giving their car keys to a valet under a covered entrance and then being swept
away into the revolving doors and swallowed up by glitz and glamour was mesmerizing.
Her life was miserable anyway.

\n\nBut, as a child, I lived in an apartment building with my parents that was run down.
The plumbing was always making strange noises and stains littered the walls and ceiling making it look more like a crime scene than a
place for families to live.
In that apartment, the first thing you saw when you walked in the door was the living room.
That\’s where it happened, it was so quick.
After the living room was the kitchen, that\’s where we dragged her,
and then the dining room followed by a hallway that led to bedrooms and one bathroom.

\n\nMy apartment is different in \“Casa del Mar\”, once you walk in you are greeted by the kitchen.
It feels so welcoming to see such a clean sterilized room. After the kitchen is the dining room, the living room, two bedrooms, and a bathroom.
Today I decided to sit comfortably on my living room sofa and watch the retched building tumble to the ground.
I made sure that my living space was opposite to what I grew up in.

\n\nNow I get swallowed up by glitz and glamour.
Although the building isn\’t as beautiful as I remember it, it\’s where I have always wanted to live —-even more so now.
Everything in my apartment is high-end.
My sofa converts into a sleeper bed and my sofa chair is a rocker with built-in speakers.
My dad was sleeping in the sofa chair when it all happened—-he didn\’t even awake to the screams.
My friends tell me that I\’m just obsessed with the past, but I\’m not. We all managed to stay friends for so long even after the incident.
Perhaps in fear that one of us will talk.

\n\nThe tile floor feels cold under my feet as I walk to the bathroom.
The floor was cold that day when I had to kneel on it to clean up the blood.
Up until recently, I found the bathroom a place filled with memories, but the new decor makes one forget the past.
Its walls have a decal that\’s ocean-themed bringing to life the walls in an underwater maze of coral and school fish.
She never even entered school. I don\’t have to worry about the plumbing making strange noises.

\n\nIn the shower, I make sure to scrub my hands thoroughly.
After so many years I still see some bloodstains on my hands.
I decided to wash my hair because I could still faintly smell something on it… Clorox? Regardless,
I exit the bathroom fully dressed in house clothes, but with a towel over my wet hair.
I don\’t want my hair to drip, like the drops of blood that led the way to her final resting place. Bobby took care of that.

\n\nAs I reentered my living room to settle on my sofa by the window, I am faced with everyone that participated that day.

\n\n\“Hey, Bobby how are you?\” his blood-splattered face turns to look at me.
He can\’t necessarily talk, not after he shot himself in the mouth a couple of years back. Perhaps the memory of the events killed him.

\n\n\“Catherine, I didn\'t think that you\’d make it.\” Catherine is my best friend.
From the age of two, we were inseparable. But that day changed that as well.
Her husband called me shortly after he found the suicide note.
She didn\’t mention the incident, but I know it was her that killed them.

\n\nJames, Christopher, and Maddy, all settled by the window. \“Come sit by me, or pull up chairs from the dining room.
\” No one seemed to listen so I went over and brought chairs for them all to sit.

\n\n\“Now James, isn\'t it time that you stop treading water in the apartment? Hasn\’t it been six years since you drowned…\”
James looks over at me his face bloated just like I saw him at the morgue where I went to identify the body.

\n\nChristopher and Maddy married after we all graduated from high school. They were her first victims.
Maddy\’s mother called me screaming and crying as she retold the story of when she found them both in their garage with the car on.
They both succumbed to carbon monoxide. Now here they were still wearing their marriage rings.
It was Christopher\’s and Maddy\'s idea to place her in the walls of the empty apartment.

\n\nAs I drink my ginger tea, I look around my apartment and notice the empty dining room chairs in my living room.
She had carved her initials on one of the chairs. Papa got mad and hit her. Mama had said that she wasn\’t his child to hit.
Papa just went to drinking and fell asleep while Mama headed to her night shift.
I never understood how Mama always said she worked the night shift, but it was early afternoon when she left.

\n\nThe ginger tea went down spicy as I take another look out the window.
It started to rain and the small drops hit the window and then slid down.
I follow one drop as it joins another drop all becoming one big drop that slides faster down the window.
Behind it, the crew is still getting ready. The old building casts a menacing plume of dust from the arriving equipment.
The air carries the dust in a whirlwind then dies at the feet of a massive truck carrying the bulldozer.
The rain slowly kills any remaining dust into small puddles.

\n\nI look again at the window and notice my reflection.
I\’m older now, a bit fatter.
The white hair slightly shapes my face giving me a look of wisdom that I don\’t have.
My skin is white, so very white, and my eyes are darkened by my failures, my tribulations.
I try to look away, but I\’m mesmerized by the appearance of the red marks around my neck.
The purple and bloody red marks on my neck haunt me. It wasn\’t my fault. I pushed her but she fell on her own.
Oh papa, mama, I miss you.

\n\nIt\’s now 6 am and a wrecking ball has arrived.
\“Perhaps the demolishing will start early,\” I say to everyone in the room.
I look around and everyone is back and waiting for the big event.
Finally, we can all leave this behind us and move on.

\n\nI decided to make some breakfast for myself.
I\’m not necessarily hungry, I just want to busy myself with something while the crew continues to get ready.
\“Anyone hungry,\” I say as I get up from my sofa, but no one answers.

\n\nEvery time I cook, I have to disinfect first.
\“Cleanliness is next to Godliness,\” my mom would say.
But I suppose there isn\’t anything godly about me. Nonetheless, I have to sterilize. Like that day.
I sterilized the kitchen before papa could see what had happened.
I never thought that he\’d get life.
I hope he didn\’t suffer when they found him hanging from his cell.

\n\nThe kitchen is so beautiful. Once I moved in, I opted for an all-white kitchen.
I needed to see any stains to quickly clean it up.
I did push her, but it wasn\’t my fault that she hit her head against the edge of the table.
Oh, the blood, so much blood. Eggs and bacon will have to do.
I can\’t see myself cooking an extravagant meal when I need to be on the sofa watching, waiting.
Eggs and bacon suddenly seem so boring, so I add biscuits and a side salad.
Three eggs don\’t seem enough so I add five more to make it an even eight eggs.
She wasn\’t eight yet, she was only three. A surprise birth, given that my mama and papa didn\’t share a room.
Five biscuits seem to make it better. Everything washes down with a liter of soda.

\n\nI noticed a spot on the floor and quickly went and wiped it down.
Christopher learned how to patch up drywall by working with his father after school every day.
Her head wouldn\’t stay put so Bobby used the nail gun to nail her head down.
The floor is clean now and all the dishes are in their places and I finished my meal.
I headed to the bathroom to shower again.
Disinfectant got on my legs and I need to remove it, plus the stains on my hands need to be removed.
The stains on my hands glow red, I scrub till I see my own blood mingle with the stain.

\n\nOnce again, I am seated on my sofa with a towel covering my hair, a bandage on my hand, and dressed in my house clothes.
The rain has led up, but the windows still have some water sliding down.
I settled in with my blanket and the cup of hot chocolate I prepared on the Keurig.
Drinking the hot chocolate brings warmth into my chest. I bring my left hand to my chest,
since my right is still holding the cup, and a little moan escapes my throat.
A lower moan than the one she gave when Bobby nailed her head. James used the hammer to quiet her down.
Once he was done, her face was unrecognizable. We stood in silence.

\n\nFinally, the clock alerts us that it\’s 10 o clock.
It was Catherine\’s idea to put some plaster on my papa\’s fingernails as he slept.
It was my idea to put some blood on the bottom of his shoe. The crew, all wearing yellow hard hats, prepare for the wrecking ball.
It swings eastwards so far that I had to come up, nose to the window, in order to see.
As it moved westwards, towards the building, I quickly looked back at the building as a final farewell.
That\’s when I saw her staring right at me, then suddenly the wrecking ball hits…
</item>

        <item>

The sky rips over us as we drive out of our old familiar,
our parents\’ neighborhood and their stuffy old ways and the beat-up old buildings that used to be
something special and now lie as monuments to our society\’s collective sense of neglect and waste.

\n\nWe make for the ocean, not to live there, but to make a day out of the experience like many others from more blue-collar zip codes.
We packed few things;
stood on the beach until we couldn\’t take it anymore,
as if we wanted to \‘get our monies worth\’ out of the sun and sand; and then I chose to drive Francis around the hills to do some sightseeing.


\n\nIt wasn\’t before long that my dear fiancé Francis looked up rent prices for some of the rooms and home that we can afford nearby,
we she stumbled on a real Doozy.

\n\nYou may think I\’m a cynical guy, and you\’re right, in my life, there has never been anything that was \‘too good to be true\’,
if it looks too good to be true, than it probably is,
and yet here we are a mere few hours later and Francis finds this awesome one bedroom studio apartment for rent cheap in a valley nearby,
the place ever has its own lake.

\nOf course, when it comes to a place like this you start off by asking yourself, I wonder why nobody rents this place?

\n\nMy line of inquiry is vague enough for the landlord\’s imagination to get piqued about my perception of his sale,
he quickly and desperately shows me pictures of the ad and compares them to what we see, after all what you see is what you get, right?

\n\nAs we tour the apartment, I get a funny vibe from the Landlord who rents this place, he\’s a real try hard,
going all out with his fake smiles and phony laughs to \‘be our friend\’, this is worse than being patronized,
its high energy sales mixed with a pungent amount of desperation.

\n\nFrancis is the daring one who like to bicycle down back alleys by herself,
of course she gets to the point quick and tells the man she is concerned about the seclusion of
the apartment may make it difficult to get the help we need when we need it.

\n\nWe look at the lake, and for a moment there is a lull of silence in the conversation,
Me and Francis are left speechless at the sight of the pristine calm waters surrounded by the torn down ruins of other apartments,
I think in this moment we both truly coveted the apartment by the lake, owning the pleasure of being here for ourselves for a moment.

\n\n\“You want to hear a story about this lake?\”, He asks the open air since every other human is preoccupied with the lake.

\n\nI\’ll tell you something that happened to me at this lake, then he continues without skipping a beat, \‘what if I said no\’,
I thought, then he goes on, I had a heart attack right here, and I thought I was going to die,
with my last breath I looked at the lake and a human looking shape came out of the water and touched me on the heart.

\n\n\‘Wow\’, I thought, \‘that sounds made up, but why make that up\’, so I ask him, hoping to draw a circle around the truth with more questions,
\“why did you tear down the other apartments?\”

\n\nFrancis adds her two cents, \“it seems like you\’d make a killing renting out multiple units?\”

\n\n\“The lake doesn\’t want it\”, he says while staring at the lake, \“with all that beauty and tranquility why would I destroy the lake? Instead,
I took out the dock and the boats, and the floating platform, and I expanded the lake, people come and go, but this lake should be forever.\”

\n\nI see Francis look at him with admiration and I know he sold her,
which means he sold me too, in the end we decide to be good stewards to the lake and a three-month lease, just to check the place out.

\n\nLike most good relationships start out, we tend to move around a lot,
anything to avoid living with my parents, or hers, God bless them all,
but we work hard to have our liberty, and here, we have our privacy and a nice view of the woods.

\n\nDay 1: We\’re moving everything important to us, for me;
my computer that I edit videos on so I can keep paying for this place, for her;
all our bathroom stuff and her computers and cameras, she must be thinking the same thing as me, gotta keep up.

\n\nDay 2: Francis and I are moving everything we can live without, but yet still need, extra clothes,
boxes of things we still want from our last move, and cleaning supplies,
by now we\’re making pacts amongst ourselves to buy what we need with our moving fund,
at this point I realize our mutual access to the moving fund inadvertently is a test of our relationship,
the test of trusting someone with your money.

\n\nDay 3: We\’re committed to calling this our last day, if it doesn\’t fit in my car, or her hybrid, then we officially don\’t need it,
the artwork she created will get picked up by her sister later.
While moving our stuff I can see what the things that are important to us also define us, without our things,
it would be hard to believe we even exist.

\n\nIt\’s late afternoon and the reflection of the sunset reminds me of why I\’m renting this place,
I still wonder what happened to the last people that lived here when Francis emerges from the apartment wiping sweat from her glowing brow.

\n\nShe intently marches towards the water with a smirk on her face while barely acknowledging me as she walks past,
\“The burgers are almost done!\”, I futilely say as she throws off item after item of her clothes,
stripping herself to her birthday suit before enjoying the lake more than I was by looking at it.

\n\nFrancis swims free and fast as the lake water shimmers and shines while she swims around in the crystal-clear lake,
while on a dive underwater with her limited vision Francis can clearly make out sharp edges and hard surfaces, a perplexing.

\n\nFrancis\’ bare cheeks glow in the afternoon light while in focus in the viewfinder of a camera.
From a high vantage point in the woods nearby,
the camera rolls and the eye of the lens wonders from Francis to David at his bar-b-que and back again.

\n\nThe landlord, satisfied with his camera angle, tightens his camera rig,
and walks away while the red-light flashes record and Francis is in frame.

\n\nAfter walking away from his \‘observation area\’ the landlord tours his gallery lost possessions in a makeshift cellar
filled with his own filth and clothes and top off with a makeshift bathroom and shower.

\n\nFrancis\’ makeup is well done, as expected of her,
and her cheeks glow in the light of her home -studio set up while I finish up an outtake cut for her next video,
I wish I could have recorded her swimming, but she would never do that.

I don\’t edit video because I don\’t have a face and body like Francis\’, I edit because Francis hates editing and I love her,
so I need to love editing too. I\’m going hours into this studying my dear Francy, frame by frame,
sometimes gauging weather her smiles and laughs are real shot by shot.

\n\nAfter a while you get to the point where you Know-know,
what things like the background look like and what does and doesn\’t belong, by the end of my editing,
a shadow figure outside of the window is consuming all my attention. Is it just a play of shadows or something in the background?

\n\nQuestions bounce through my mind like rubber balls in a hallway,
like a child, I follow my curiosity without a single thought of harm.

\n\nI get to the space outside the window and find footprints leading from the window to the lake,
now I\’m officially freaked out, my first thought is, nobody else knows we’re here, except one person.

\n\nThe drone flies high with it\’s million killer bee buzzes, this was one of the things I had to have here,
my professional grade drone camera, I want to see how far a person would have to swim if they crossed the lake.

\n\nI didn\’t tell her about the footprints, since there\’s nothing I can do about it,
yet I told her I\’m just shooting b-roll footage in case she wants it later.

\n\nIt\’s not long before I\’m left in shock, I can clearly see a structure under the lake,
and I can see that it continues under the ruins of the old apartments.

\n\nBy now I\’m curious as to what lies in the woody hills around us,
and as I take my drone to the far edge of the lake I get a phone call from the landlord.

\n\nI start off the phone call by telling him about the structures that I was seeing under the lake and how it
looked like it went under the old apartments,
when he cuts me off and tells me about some special tool in the garage used to get into the attic,
then he piques my interest when he tells me I can have whatever is left up there.

\n\nI forget all about the drone during the call, but when started talking about the footprints,
he cut me off again and told me I shouldn\’t swim at night, because \“you don\’t know where the bottom is.\”

\n\nWhile up in the attic, I find left over items from the previous tenants under a hazy blanket of dust and cobwebs,
there\’s not much, but the gem of this collection is a VHS tape I find in a cardboard box.

\n\nI watch the video of a happy family, no more than one year ago enjoying the lake,
it reminds me of when I was young and carefree, I also think of how Francis makes me feel like that,
until something I see startles all comfortable thoughts from my mind.

\n\nWith the software I got, and my editing skills,
I expertly enhance the video and I am reminded of the horror that brought me here,
that same shadowy figure in the background looking right at the camera, I don\’t know how I\’m going to sleep tonight.

\n\nI\’m shaking and sweating as I\’m looking up ancient relics while under the guise of editing,
this is my final act before having to worry Francis over the thing.

\n\nJust when I think I’m in the clear,
Francis surprises me and asks me about my research after seeing images of pre-Christian religious symbols,
this is where I tell a selective truth, and tell her that Vikings were said to have once lived in the Americas,
nobody knows where they vanished to.

\n\n\“But some of the glyphs from the structure on the lake are of an ancient temple dedicated to the god of the underworld\”,
I say hoping we won’t have to start packing tonight.

\n\nTo my surprise, Francis laughs off my observations as paranoia,
she even reasons that there is still no evidence that Vikings have made to California, in which she\’s right,
being wrong for once has brought me comfort, and seeing her this defiant to the dread that I feared for days is inspiring,
I feel like I can tell her anything.

\n\nShe always has to beat me to the breakfast table and have something ready,
I know she doesn\’t like to get up early, so I know she only does this for me,
because she loves me, she finds a way to get up and go.

\n\nIn the kitchen where we share an unspoken truce to never hold back at our diner table,
and example we want to set for our children, if we have any, here I tell Francis about a re-occurring dream I have periodically,
which I have kept from her.

\n\n\“What I can remember is that you always sleepwalk into the lake, and I ends up following her into a dark realm of strange living creatures,
that\’s why I\’ve been taking the sleeping pills, so I don\’t remember my dreams and just sleep.\”,
I feel like I\’m trying to sell her on my new dependency.

\n\nI see my words washed over her by her eyes and somewhat pale expression and I know my words made an impression,
it is now, that I lie my darkness at the feet of my dear Francis and strip myself bare of my fear and anxiety,
she destroys my world with a silent gesture.

\n\nFrancis turns around and shows me a drawing of a dark figure that I am all too familiar with already,
the same dark stranger from my editing bay and the back of my mind, then she tells me she’s been having dreams too.

\n\nFrancis suddenly awakens from a nightmare in a cold sweat,
and after trying to subtly wake up David, who is sleeping like a stone while on the sleeping pills he has developed a habit for,
Francis decides to go for a walk.

\n\nThe refrigerator closes and Francis looks to the bedroom for a second,
hoping David will be awakened as she gets some milk and cookies then walks back towards the bedroom,
when she sees the tool to get into the attic and which piques her interest.

\n\nFrancis slowly creeps into the attic, and notices David\’s equipment and Drone when she turns on the lights,
the knowledge that David has occupied the space and said nothing negative about it empowers her to explore the dusty and cramped space.

\n\nFrancis feels her inner child\’s curiosity in her as he feels compelled to look out of the vent folds of the attic and see
how far she is from the ground, as she gives in to herself to look out the window and she remembers all the time she was a little girl,
and she was never allowed in the attic.

\n\nThrough the slats of the ventilation Francis is shocked to see a little girl looking at the lake that looks just like she did when she was young,
then she sees the girl look at her, almost reading Francis\’ thoughts and then the girl walks into the lake.

\n\nFrancis is shocked by what she sees, and in a moment of panic, she dashes out of the attic and swiftly runs out to the lake,
in her heart, she had to disprove herself crazy,
she had to prove that she was just too tied as she makes her way out of the apartment to the lake.

\n\nA hand is seen by Francis rising out of the water and slowly descends back into the water almost as if saying goodbye to her.

\n\nFrancis is almost driven mad by fear and anxiety as she is caught in a dilemma,
to hurry and save the girls life, or wake up David and see if he can help.

\n\nIn this moment of panic, her mind goes to a dark place of a time when her mother threw her into the water to \‘teach\’ her how to swim,
and where she almost drowned for the first time in her life, and she learned to never trust anyone until she met David.

\n\nIt is her thought of \‘doing what David would do\’ that she remembers her courage and throws herself
in the lake with all the confidence of her own swimming that she gave herself in high school, sure that she can save anyone, including David.

\n\nI wake up and realize Francis is gone, not unusual,
but normally the apartment is fill with the liveliness of her morning sounds, my need to use the bathroom forces me out of bed,
and on my way I build up the assumption that she has gotten up early to unpack more of her things in the attic, since the attic is still open.

\n\nAfter finding her keys in the kitchen and seeing no sign of her making herself or me breakfast,
I remember seeing the attic still open and briskly make my way up with a sudden chill crawling down my spine realizing how
quiet and empty it is without Francis until I hear a woman\’s voice echoing over the water.

\n\nI rush to the shore of the lake after hearing an echo of Francis\’ voice,
then I swim into the crystal-clear lake where I can see Francis\’ phone at the bottom at the edge of the structure under the water.

\n\nForgetting all fear, I desperately swim to the bottom, where I reach for the phone,
then a hand reaches back and a Francis with her skin covered in scars and black veins screams grabs hold of my arm with
a deathly cold grip and screams through the water,
\“come and see!\” then she pulls him through a dark hole from where she came which seals behind them.

\n\nThe landlord watches the lake next to his camera, then he starts to have heart pains,
and the camera begins to malfunction, almost with anticipation of his impending demise.

\n\nAn illuminated figure from the lake appears and approaches the landlord then touches his heart and
the landlord recovers from his heart pains then he tells him in a ghastly voice, \“the deal is still the same,
for every one year of life they had left, I will give you one hour, I have granted you forty-five more hours\”,
then the sprit dissipates into glowing orbs and swarms into the lake.

\n\nIn the wake of the lake spirit disappearing and the calming of the water, the landlord is left alone with his thoughts,
and he thinks to himself, \‘forty-five more hours, I must rent again\’.
</item>

        <item>

From the basement, I take the stairs to the ground floor. When I enter, there\’s a creature in the corner.
It\’s putrid breath reaches me; I tremor in horrifying terror as it exhales death and rot into my face.
It pierces me with large red eyes, then scuttles off along the ceiling – gone as if it never existed.
It\'s freezing cold, and there is no power to the building, after a small fire on the third floor damaged the wiring.
So far tonight, I\’ve checked through the basement where all the staff lockers,
changing rooms and showers are located, plus the staff cafeteria and a temporary office for security,
since the control room is out of order. There is an indoor swimming pool, sauna and a gym for tenants only.
It\’s rather fancy, considering it\’s one of the oldest apartment buildings in town.
Some cosmetic work has been done to bring it into the 21st century. Basement completed; I write on my check list.

\n\nSomething touches my hand and I yelp in fright, but try to ignore it – it was probably a spider? The ground floor hosts a lavish restaurant,
a cocktail bar and a gift shop, though it has no apartments. I check these are secure, and tick them off my list.
Something is following me; I can hear it – the noises it makes sends needle sharp prickles upon my body.
I point the flashlight behind me, but there is nothing there, though I hear loud footsteps pounding the floor.
It rushes me, then backs off.

\n\nI reach the stairwell to ascend to the first floor, I push through the door as something grabs at my arm, making me drop the flashlight.
What I catch in the light is something God awful terrifying. It\’s a swirling black mass of distorted faces.
My mind cannot fully comprehend what I am seeing.
Scooping my flashlight up, then pushing through the door to the staircase, the door slamming behind me gives me a scare.
I stand against the door, trying to catch my breath, because I feel a panic attack coming on.

\n\nI entered this building at sunset. For a minute I\’m lost in the memory of the golds and magentas, spreading their fingers across the sky.
It was breath-taking.
Now I have no idea what time it is, I\’ve accidentally left my cellphone at home.
Somehow, all the clocks I\’ve come across have been showing different times. Weird. Funnily enough, my watch has stopped at 6 pm,
when I entered this hell hole of a building. It seems to be eating up time.
But it must be well after midnight, judging by the darkness which smothers the windows; a cold empty chill has set in.

\n\nI\’m here because of the murders that occurred three nights ago.
Eight tenants were murdered in cold blood. The police have cordoned off the areas where the shootings took place.
The security firm I work for got the contract to secure the premises, and to ensure explorers and thrill seekers stay off the property.
Over the past three nights, I\’ve had to run off a couple of paranormal investigation teams,
who begged me and offered me money to let them in for a tour. The boss would have my head on a stick if I let them in.

\n\nThe apartments have been left abandoned, and the tenants are not permitted back until the investigation is through.
The police emptied the place when they got the emergency call,
about a gunman walking through the building shooting people with a rifle.
My brother Colten is a cop and when he found out I was coming here to do security detail, he called me immediately.

\n\“Hey Gabe, how\’s it going?\”

\n\“Good thanks. What\’s up?\” I asked.

\n\“I\’m wondering if you want to catch up in the weekend, have a game of basketball? I\’ll book us in if you want?\”

\n\“Sounds good bro. How\’s work?\”

\n\“The murders at the Waterfront Apartments are keeping me up at night, I tell you,\” he exhales and I can tell he is shaking his head,
I know my twin brother very well.

\n\“Are you any closer to catching the bastard who did it?\”

\n\n\“No, we\’ve not caught him yet, but we know who he is. It\’s been a difficult investigation,
with all the camera footage destroyed, you know, after he shot the security guards.\”

\n\nColten goes quiet.

\n\n\“Yes, poor old Bobby Ray, he didn\’t deserve that. And Luke McGee has a baby on the way,\” I said.

\n\n\“Please don\’t do it bro. I heard you were replacing them. I know you probably feel obligated,
you and Bob were good friends. But it is dangerous there,
I have heard all sorts of things about the place from other cops…really scary stuff, even some of the squad refuse to enter it now.\”

\n\n\“Colten, you know I don\’t believe in that crap, ghosts and demons, goblins and ghouls, it\’s utter rubbish.\”

\n\n\“Just be careful. Sometimes murderers go back to the location of the crime,
for the thrill and to marvel in the destruction they caused, he is a sick bastard whoever he is.
Look I\’ve got to go, but I\’ll give you a call tomorrow. I\’ll see you at the BB court at 10 am, on Saturday. Okay?\”

\n\n\“See you then bro, you don\’t need to call to check up on me. I can look after myself, always have,\” this makes us both laugh.

\n\nChills afflict me as I recall the conversation, and goose pimples give me the jitters.
I shake a vision away – me lying there dead in a pool of my own blood.
I am jolted out of my reverie, when I glance something big and black down the staircase.
I\’m in the stairwell, trying to make it to the first floor.
I run up the stairs, because I can feel something behind me, it\’s all in my imagination, I reassure myself.
Places like this give me the creeps, not from the dead, who I don\’t believe in, no, it\’s the living I fear.
I walk the corridor and check all the rooms on this floor are secure. I check this off my list.

\n\nThe murders began on the third floor, then it carried on to the fourth floor, and then the basement.
There are eight floors all up.
It\’s a huge place to secure, and I wish there was someone else with me – this is the first place I\’ve done security alone.
I think of Bob and how he was murdered when he went to investigate the commotion on the third floor.
He was shot dead, then the murderer used Bob\’s keys to enter the control room, where he found Luke and ended his life.
He destroyed the camera screens and the footage, obviously so he couldn\’t be recognised.

\n\nI get a jolt when I hear the door at the far end of the corridor slam shut.

\n\n\“Hello, is there someone here? This place is off limits, you aren\’t allowed in here,\” I say trembling.

\n\nNo one responds. The hallway is in complete darkness, except for my flashlight.
It\’s a standard police issued torch that can be used to hammer someone in the head, I suppose.
If it comes to that, I\’ll save my own life in whatever way possible.
I hear a female scream, it assaults my ears, making me drop the flashlight again.
I\’m all thumbs tonight. This place is freaking me out, and I seem to be chasing shadows.
In the corners the blackness is deep and whole, it seems to go on forever.
Like I already said to Colten, I don\’t believe in ghosts, never have, and tonight is no exception.

\n\nThe scream pierces the air again, but now it is closer, almost right next to me. A cold shiver feathers down my back.
There is no way anyone could get in here; I checked all the entry and exit points as soon as I\’d arrived.
Though now the camera screens have been destroyed, there is no way for me to confirm this.
I direct my light up and down the corridor as I make my way to the staircase to go up to the second floor.
Something touches my shoulder and I jump out of my skin in fear. Turning abruptly, I search with my light, there is no one there.
This place is playing tricks with my mind.

\n\nThe second floor has a heaviness that leaves me momentarily dizzy, and I feel eyes watching me, but I can\’t explain it.
I\’ve never been a nervous person, but tonight something inside me is telling me to run and hide.

\n\nAlthough the foreboding feeling is strong, I manage to check all the rooms are secured, I tick them off my list.
There are guest bathrooms, I check these off too.

\n\nI make it out onto the landing, and start climbing towards the third floor.
On the previous night\’s I\’ve been here, I couldn\’t get to that floor as the police forensic team were still investigating.
As I reach the door to the floor, a cold blast of freezing air hits me with full force in my face.
I\’m suddenly tired in my bones, finding it hard to lift my feet.
I feel a heavy pressure on my chest, but I keep going…hoping to get the fuck out of here.
I don\’t want to admit it to myself, I am terrified.

\n\nI scan the area with my flashlight.
There is evidence that the police and the forensics team have been here.
Crime scene tape has cordoned off some of the corridor, and a couple of apartments.
A sound somewhere behind me has me turning.
I hear screams. My teeth are chattering, not from the cold.
Something isn\’t right.
I hear gunshots coming from somewhere inside the building, but that doesn\’t make any sense, perhaps it came from outside? Regardless,
I pull my taser out of my utility belt, only to be used under special circumstances, and this is one of those moments.
It\’s the only thing I have to protect myself.
Unaware of where the noises, gunshots and screams are coming from, I walk deeper into the building.
I step over the yellow and black tape, as bursts of gunfire shatter the silence.
I know in my bones this isn\’t right, the shots blast all around me, though they hit nothing.
A huge black shadow darts past, setting my nerves on end. I carry on, I need to get this done.

\n\nI check all the apartment doors on this floor and they are locked up and secure.
I check the guest bathrooms, they are empty.
It is getting challenging to ignore all the noises coming from every direction.
I need normal noise, I start humming…That doesn\’t last long, I hear a loud crashing sound.
With my flashlight I search the hallway, only to find all the apartment doors are wide open...

\n\n\“What the fuck?\” I yell, confused.

\n\nThe murderer could still be here, like Colten warned me.
A vision of the madman bursts inside my head.
Him killing his girlfriend, and then his Mother – only an evil prick can do something like that.
Him shooting two kids and their parents on the fourth floor.
I hear giggling behind me, I\’m stopped dead in my tracks when I spot two small shadows dark past in my peripheral.
It chills me to the core.
I walk faster along the corridor, and come to the spot where Bobby was killed, there is still blood dried to the carpet.
Something shoves me hard, and I fall to my knees. Perhaps I just tripped on something?

\n\nThere shouldn\’t be anyone here but me. My adrenalin is spiking through the roof.
More gunshots has me off the ground, bolting up the stairs to the fourth floor.
It is dark and eerie, bitterly cold. As the door shuts me in, I feel hands all over my body, but there is no one there! I cry: petrified.
I move away from the door and make my way towards the second crime scene.
I\’m really not supposed to be on this floor, but I need to check I am actually alone.
The pressure is back on my chest. I feel hands around my throat, so I can\’t scream for help, though there is no one to yell for anyway.
I\’m trying to catch my breath, when it tightens its hold around my neck. My scream reverberates down the corridor when I am released.
I fall to the floor and I don\’t have the strength to get up.

\n\nPure fear grips me hard. I thought I could do this, but it is getting nearly impossible to maintain myself.
I get off the floor and pull myself together.
I\’m trying to remember what happened, but it seems my memory has stopped working.
Suddenly, I am in full throttle terror. I can\’t remember arriving here. Something inside my head feels broken.
I remember arriving in my Ute, I can visualise the last thing I saw before I entered:
the sunset. As I catch my breath I try to remember…but it\’s useless, I can\’t even remember what day it is.
I don\’t know what is going on, but I feel like a different person, like I\’m walking around in someone else\’s skin.

\n\nSomething scuttles towards me; I can hear its claws scratching on the walls.
Pointing my light towards the sound, I see it – it\’s horrid and ghastly.
It\’s clinging to the ceiling upside down, it\’s arms are so long, they nearly touch me.
As quick as humanly possible, I hoof it down the corridor to the other side of the floor.
There are doors I should check, but I am too terrified to continue. In a fear so total, I make my way to the staircase.
I want out. I quit: I\’m done. I have never been so scared in my life.
What I just saw confirms, I should not be here, especially alone.
Suddenly I am livered at Bobby for getting himself killed. Now I have to deal with this shit.

\n\nA memory implodes inside my mind, something Bobby had said the last time we spoke, that was a few weeks ago now.
I\’ve barely slept since I started working here.
I\’ve been carrying around this ominous feeling and it\’s been messing with my head.
I can\’t remember much of anything, and although my memory is unreliable at the moment, I do recall what Bobby had said about this building.
It was his two-year anniversary working here, and I said I was happy for him.
But then he said something bizarre, that it\’s not been too good recently.
He was seeing a counsellor about the things that had been happening in his life, and his job here.
His life has been falling apart.
I tried to remind him, he has a loving wife, Nelly, and three great children.
He said, the job is getting to him and that he is sure he is being haunted.
That he sees things in the corner of his eye. Shadows seem to be following him everywhere.
Not just at work, but they seem to have followed him home. I laughed at him, saying he obviously needs a holiday.

\n\nWhen I make it back to the office, I am shaking and sweating all over, cold chills attack me.
I stuff my gear into my backpack, getting ready to leave. Three knocks on the office door has me freaking out.
But it could be someone coming to replace me from the graveyard shift? Or the police could be here to resume their investigation?
When I open the office door, there is a man standing there with a rifle pointed at me.
I gasp in a frightened breath, waiting in quiet torment for him to pull the trigger.
When it happens I am not surprised. I look at him, deep into his eyes, they are soulless and black.
He smiles as the trigger releases and the pain hits me an instant later…

\n\nI come too and the man has vanished. I check myself over, to be sure – I appear to be okay.
I get up, heading for the front doors. I try to get out, but the key I used to get in, is no longer working.
What the hell is going on? I start running when I hear more gunshots from the floors above.
I run to the other exits, but I can\’t escape. I look back and see the hole in my stomach as I lay in a pool of blood.
I am distraught. After everything I\’ve been going through, one bullet ended my life. Now I will never see my brother Colten again.
I should have listened to him. He has always been the logical one out of the both of us.
Our parents will be gutted, I don\’t think they will be able to handle this.

\n\nI\’m lost and all alone. Dying is not what I had expected.
No cracking open of Heaven, the earth still spins. Lost in the memory of what happened, a vision nudges me as I am taken under.
I see what actually happened…In my mind it plays out like a horror movie, over and over repeating itself, until I grasp the reality.
I am dead. Finally I stop running.
There is a tunnel and I decide to follow the light…I see Bobby Ray, he tells me to go back,
I ask back where? And I wake in the hospital attached to monitors.
Relief floods me, Colten is holding my hand, crying, and our parents are sitting either side of me.
I am alive, I survived the graveyard shift from hell.
</item>

        <item>
That Mole!

It stared at me as I tried my hardest to concentrate on what she was saying.
Jenny Langstrom, our realtor had been droning on for what seemed like days.
Jenny was showing us this apartment for the second time because my wife liked it so much.
I kept looking at that huge mole that sat on her top lip like a bird perched on a fence.
I felt my wife\’s hand touch my arm. She knew I wasn\’t concentrating.
Emily knew I was basically a child in a man’s body.
I slowly turned my head towards her, and she flashed me an annoyed look.
I took a gulp and looked back at Jenny.\n
Jenny was a short woman with unkept brunette hair and the greenest eyes I had ever seen on a person.
She wore a grey blazer and black pencil skirt.\n
Hiding behind her almost oversized blazer was a white blouse.\n
Her black high heeled shoes propped her up and gave her a bit of authority.
There was something wrong with that woman. From the moment I met her I knew there was something off.\n
I had tried to tell Emily a few times, but she didn\’t take me seriously.\n
You see I had been dreading moving to a new apartment.\n
I had lived in my current apartment for years as a young bachelor.\n
I had been there even before I met Emily. From the moment we were married, and she moved in she hated it.
All of it. The exposed brick. The smell of car oil.\n
The shower that had to be turned on with a pair of pliers placed on the floor.\n
Emily also claimed that there was an old man from across the road who would watch her when she was alone in the apartment.\n
I didn\’t believe her too. I knew she would do anything to get out of that apartment.\n
It wasn\’t a big deal anyway. I loved her and she loved me so I could stomach the idea of moving.\n

\n\nJenny kept going on about the crown molding or something boring like that. Emily ate it up.
She was nodding her head and humming. She kept asking questions about the apartment and the area and homeowners associations.
What the hell was she talking about? I often believed Emily enjoyed acting like a grown up. I myself didn\’t care.
It felt like these people were just making up grown up words. Whatever.

\n\n\“I\’m going to check out the bathroom,\” I said while pointing at the hallway.

\n\nJenny smiled at me and nodded, and Emily gave me a murderous stare.

\n\n\“I\’ll be back,\” I said with a grin to reassure Emily.

\n\nShe was not happy. I didn\’t care, I liked pushing her buttons.
I feared if I didn\’t challenge her once in a while, she would get bored of me or something.
I walked to the hallway and Jenny words started to fade away and it sounded like a grown up from \“Peanuts\”.
I found myself at a sort of T junction where I saw 3 doors around me.
Right Infront of me was a door and on both sides were two more doors on each side.

\n\nKnock Knock

\n\nI heard a slight Knock on my right on the wall along the hallway.
I turned my head towards it. The faint knocking continued.\n
I looked back at Emily and Jenny, and they were still deep in conversation.\n
I touched the wall and the knocking stopped.\n
I was probably hearing things.\n
I brushed it off and walked towards the door on the right and opened it.\n
I found a large bedroom that curved around me.\n
I walked in and looked around.\n
After gazing at the walls I opened the closet.\n

\n\“Don\’t rent the apartment,\”

\n\nI heard a whisper around me. I looked around. I leaned closer into the closet.

\n\n\“Don\’t rent the apartment,\”

\n\nThe whisper got louder. I stepped back from the closet. I closed and rubbed my eyes.
I walked back to the closet and listened again. The whisper was gone.
I smiled to myself and sighed. I walked to the door, and I heard a knock coming from area I heard it from before in the hallway.
The knock then intensified. I walked closer to the wall.
I realized that the coat of white painting around that area was slightly different.
I was a dentist so I could tell the difference between shades of white. The knocking continued.
I pressed my ear onto the wall. The knocking stopped again.

\n\n\“DON\’T RENT THE APARTMENT!\”

\n\nA female voice shouted into my right ear. I grabbed my ear and fell to the ground. It felt like someone had stabbed my eardrum.

\n\n\“Emily!\” I shouted.

\n\nMy body felt limp. Suddenly my voice was gone. I crawled to the door, and I struggled to turn the door handle.
I walked out the door. Suddenly the apartment was dark. I struggled to my feet, and I limped to the living room.
The skies outside the window were now red and it gave the room a bloody tint. Emily and Jenny were now gone.
I tried to scream for Emily a few more times. Nothing came out of my mouth.
I looked back and Jenny stood in the hallway and her left hand was on the wall where the knock
had come from earlier and her right hand had an object in it. I walked towards her.

\n\n\“Where\’s Emily?\” I asked her.

\n\nShe ignored me.

\n\nI could now see that Jenny was rubbing the wall as if the wall was her womb and she was caressing her baby bump.
She had a big smile on her face. Now I could see the object in her hand. It was a blood-soaked knife.
Now I was really worried.

\n\n\“Where\’s Emily?!\” Shouted angrily.

\n\nShe giggled.

\n\n\“What do you mean? She\’s right behind you,\” she said with a sinister tone.

\n\nI slowly turned backwards while trying to keep an eye on Jenny. I got the shock of my life.
Emily was right behind me with her hair covering her face.
I tilted her head up slowly and her face had a pale blue hue.
Her neck had striation marks like she had been strangled with a rope or a garrot.
Her body was also riddled with stab wounds. I grabbed her almost lifeless body and shook her.

\n\n\“Emily!\” I shouted again.

\n\nI then felt a pair of hands rub my shoulders. I jumped up and looked back. It wasn\’t Jenny.
It was a young black woman who had pale brown skin. Her eyes were blueish white, and they looked dead.
She also had rope burn around her neck and stab wounds all over her body.
She then grabbed my neck and started choking me.
I tried to fight her off.

\n\n\“I thought I told you not to rent the apartment!\” She screamed angrily.

\n\nI woke up in my bed riddled with sweat.
I had also woken up Emily. She wrapped her arms around me and hugged me.

\n\n\“What\’s wrong?\” She asked with concern.

\n\nI insisted that we should change realtors.
I didn\’t have the guts to tell her about the dream.
After days of back and forth arguing she agreed. We got a new realtor and found an apartment that we both liked.

\n\nI\’m sure you think I was overreacting right? Why don\’t you ask Lucy Johnson if
I was overreacting? She was the previous tenant of the apartment and she had been missing for a year and half.\n
They believe she is dead, but they never found her body.\n
I\’m pretty sure we both know where she is.\n
If you don\’t think that\’s enough, why don\’t you ask the McGregor\’s if
I was overreacting? They were the couple that rented the apartment after we pulled out.\n
Come to think of it they wouldn\’t really be helpful because they were both
found stabbed multiple times and strangled to death in the apartment.\n
I watch the news time and again and I see them struggle to find any decent leads while I sit here with this unbearable burden.\n
I have no idea if I should call the cops.\n
Would they even believe me? What do you think I should do? Whatever happens there is one thing for sure: Jenny Langstrom is a monster.
</item>

        <item>

Three loud bangs on the door startle Leslie out of her reverie.
The noise reverberates through her empty apartment, bouncing off the parquet floor and past the unopened moving boxes.
Rattling her bones. The echoes fade but never quite disappear.
They sink into the mute white walls, drown in the shadow bog under the sofa.

\n\nShe sets her bottle of water on the kitchen counter.
Her muscles still ache, but the high of the jog is forgotten, and her sweat, pleasant a moment ago, runs cold.

\n\nIt\’s midday but the fierce bright only creeps in through her windows, scoring her living room floor. It never reaches the kitchen.
She swallows hard and flicks the light switch, and the dull yellow bulb buzzes above her at sixty Hertz.

\n\nThe air is heavy, suddenly still, and she rushes to the front door, throws it open.
Foolish. The door chain isn\’t engaged and she doesn\’t even check who’s there.
Dangerous behaviours for a single woman new to this part of town.

\n\nBut there\’s a change in pressure, almost a wind rippling past her, and she can breathe again.

\n\nA man stands on the other side of the door and he takes a step back. His surprise – his dimples – are adorable. Her heart flutters.

\n\n\“Oh–\” he says, forgetting what he was saying.
His eyes dart over her, almost too fast for her to notice. But not quite.

\n\nHeat colours Leslie\’s cheeks.
She\’s still in her jogging shorts, and the sweat soaked tee.
But she knows she looks good in it. And the way his eyes linger a little too long, he knows it too.

\n\n\“Yes?\” she says. Always best to dive into discomfort.
Only way to move forward in life.
She flutters her lashes just a bit. Serve!

\n\n\“Um.\” He clears his throat. Grins and looks away.
When she tucks a loose hair behind her ear, he runs his thumb along his chin.
Also dimpled.

\n\n\“Sorry to bother you,\” he says, that school-boy smile tugging at his lips.
\“Um… I\’m Mark.\” He holds out his hand.

\n\n\“Leslie,\” she says, shaking without thinking. His palm is clean, strong.
Hers is sticky with stale sweat.
But he shakes and doesn\’t flinch.
Maybe he didn\’t notice. Either way, he returns the serve and the ball is still in play.

\n\n\“I’m your downstairs neighbour,\” Mark says.
\“Uh, first off… I guess, welcome to the building!\”

\n\n\“Thanks! I like it here.\”

\n\n\“Yeah, it\’s a great place.\” His smile melts into a frown, and he hesitates.

\n\n\“What\’s up?\” She frowns too. The sun\’s in her eyes and she can\’t see the ball.

\n\n\“Look, I hate to be that guy, but I work from home, you know? It\’s just, it was pretty loud today,
right in the middle of a call with a client.\”

\n\nShe crosses her arms and leans against the door frame.

\n\n\“I get it,\” he says. \“Working out is important. Could you maybe hold off until after four PM?\”

\n\nShe shakes her head. \“I don’t know what you\’re talking about.\” She doesn\’t.

\n\n\“It\’s just, the stomping was pretty distracting.\” He holds his hands out, shrugs. The ball hits the court.

\n\n\“I think you have the wrong apartment, Mark.\”

\n\n\“Well,\” he drags out, \“I don\’t think I do.\”

\n\n\“I haven\’t been home all day.\”

\n\nHe frowns. She frowns. The ball rolls out of bounds, and they stand in silence for a while.

\n\n\“Okay,\” he says, rolling his eyes. She narrows hers.
He retreats, and entreats, \“Just please keep it down from now on.\”

\n\n\“It wasn\’t me,\” she says, but he\’s already on the stairs going down.
Why are people always accusing her of stuff like this? What\’s wrong with everyone? It\’s like this every time.

\n\nLeslie shuts her door, locks it. Mutters, \“Asshole.\”



\n\nThree loud bangs on the door two hours later. She puts her book down.
This time the chain is engaged and when she looks out the peephole she sees Mark again. She snarls and cracks the door.

\n\n\“What?\”

\n\nHis face bounces around worry, guilt, other things.
She wants to hate it but those dimples catch her eye and won\’t let go.

\n\n\“Look, I just wanted to apologize,\” he says. \“I think… wow. Well, I think we got off to a terrible start. I was a real jerk.\”

\n\nYou were, she thinks.

\n\n\“You\’re new here, and I made these, um, baseless allegations. Please, let me make it up to you. How about dinner tomorrow?\”

\n\nHer jaw almost drops. She undoes the chain and opens the door.

\n\n\“Are you seriously asking me out? After that?\”

\n\nHe\’s got his palms up, and his gaze down. \“No, no, this just an apology-dinner.
And a welcome-to-the-building dinner. Nothing more, I promise.
Unless, you know… unless you decide it\’s a date-dinner.\” He grins that stupid charming grin. \“I wouldn’t be opposed to that.\”

\n\n\“It\’s definitely not,\” she says, but she can\’t help smiling herself, and, she fears, blushing. \“Pick me up at six?\”

\n\n\“Will do.\”


\n\nThe next night, she returns to her apartment. New apartment. New job.
New… boyfriend? She grins as her keys jangle, finally getting her door open.

\n\nNo, too soon for that. But maybe, maybe. Mark\’s fun, and they have things to talk about.
And the kiss was nice. At his door. She refused his offer to escort her up another flight of steps.
Too dangerous to have those handsome dimples right at her porch. Not on the first date. Which, she concedes, it was.
And she giggles, because maybe.

\n\nShe flicks her light on and kicks her heels off.

\n\nThree loud bangs on the door.

\n\nHer light champagne buzz turns sour. The darkness of the night presses through her windows.
Her feet are cold on the parquet floor.

\n\nThrough the peephole she sees a man. Shorter than Mark, older.
Balding on top, but with wild curls elsewhere, and a roiling mustache.
She opens the door a crack and he snorts loudly.

\n\n\“Yeah, listen lady, you gotta keep the damn noise down, all right?\”

\n\n\“Excuse me?\”

\n\nHe runs his hands over his head and snarls.
\“All god damned night with the banging! The thumping! Right? Some of us have to work tomorrow,
so please just have a shred of decency and keep it down!\”

\n\n\“I don\’t know what you\’re talking about!\”

\n\n\“Look, lady, I know the super! I\’ll call the cops! Okay? I\’m not nuts.
This is your friendly warning. Just keep it the hell down, or I\’ll get your ass thrown out.\”

\n\nHe stomps down the hall in his flip-flops before she can answer. His feet groan heavy on the stairs going up.
Leslie shuts the door, lets out an impotent growl. Fear? Anger? Confusion? All of it.

\n\nShe wasn\’t home. It wasn\’t her. Is this some stupid game that Mark\’s playing? Why is every guy like that?

\n\nShe grabs a bottled water from the fridge and downs it.

\n\nMaybe there\’s a mistake. Maybe it’s one of her neighbours. After all, sound travels strangely through the walls.
Tomorrow she\’ll talk with them, get to the bottom of this.

\n\nThree hours later she’s still tossing in her bed, sheets soaked with sweat.
Her mind races her heart. She\’s hurt. Afraid.
What if this is a prank? What kind of sick game are they playing? And who\’s doing the playing?

\n\nAnd what can she do about it?

\n\nThe silence of her apartment offers no answers.

\n\nAnd then it does.

\n\nThere\’s a ka-dunk, a muffled pile-driver miles away on a misty morning. Dull metal strikes dead metal. Again. And again. And again.

\n\nAnd it comes from her living room.

\n\nLeslie screams. She\’s not thinking, just moving.
She tears out of bed, flies through the kitchen, and is out her door never once looking back.

\n\nThe next thing she knows, Mark is holding her tightly, her face buried in his chest. She\’s bawling.
There\’s words she wants, words she needs, but she can\’t find them. Did she run down the stairs? Is this his apartment?

\n\nHis arms are strong, they protect her. She\’s safe here.
He sways with her and she allows him to calm her down.
She takes a shuddering breath and the cup of water he offers.
Only now does she notice he\’s only wearing boxers.
There\’s sleep-blear in his eyes and a red welt all over his chest where she had pressed against him.
Pressed into him. And her eyes linger on that chest.

\n\nThere\’s a scratch, too. A fresh line bleeding red.
She notices she has her keys in her hand, in a death grip. She must have grabbed them as she ran.
Unthinking. She must have injured him. Also unthinking.

\n\nMark sits her down on his couch, sits opposite her, yawns. \“Leslie, what\’s going on?\”

\n\n\“I don’t know,\” she whispers, blinking away tears. \“I couldn\’t sleep.
I heard… I heard something.\” Another shaky breath to keep from crying.

\n\n\“You heard something?\” She nods. \“Could it be… like, something you ate? At the restaurant?\”

\n\nLeslie shakes her head. \“No. I heard something in my apartment.
\” She wipes her eyes. \“I think you were right,\” she barely whispers.
\“I think someone\’s in there.\” She places her hand over her mouth, afraid that by speaking it she makes it true.

\n\nThere\’s a moment of silence between them. Mark takes a deep breath, about to talk, but then they hear it.

\n\nKa-dunk, ka-dunk, ka-dunk. Above them. Distant and yet close enough to touch.
Dust falls from the ceiling, and they stare at each other.
        Her eyes are wide and his are intense. They get up at the same time.

\n\n\“Mark!\” she whispers.

\n\n\“Stay here,\” he says, his voice iron.

\n\n\“Where are you going?\”

\n\nA wooden Louisville Slugger rests against the wall. He picks it up, tests the familiar grip. Grim satisfaction on his face.

\n\n\“Stay here,\” he says again. \“I’m going to handle this.\”

\n\nMark leaves and Leslie sinks to the floor, covering her face. She couldn\’t move even if she wanted to.
She hears the noise in her apartment again, and then his distant footfalls on the stairs. A moment later, she hears him above her.
There\’s a muffled \“Who\’s there?\” as he rushes from the kitchen to the living room.
A fuzzy \“Show yourself!\” as he darts into the bedroom and bathroom.
His bare feet squeak against the parquet floor. He moves again, to the living room, and there\’s one more muffled, \“Is that you–\”

\n\nKa-dunk.

\n\nAnd then there is silence.

\n\nIt takes Leslie ten minutes to realize that there\’s nothing more upstairs.
Ten minutes without a single sound. Ten minutes of squirming, alone, on Mark\’s floor.
Where did the time go? She wants to crawl out of her own skin and hide somewhere, but she doesn\’t know where.

\n\nShe decides she needs to do something. Maybe Mark needs help. Maybe he\’s injured.
She thinks about calling the police, but how long would it take them to respond? Maybe Mark doesn\’t have the time.
She steels herself and picks up her keys. And she goes upstairs.

\n\nWhen she gets to the landing of her floor she sees the door to her apartment is open.
Shadows spill out of it into the dim hall. Her heart pounds and her throat is dry.
Each step she takes, the old floor creaks under her. She whispers \“Mark?\” but it\’s so quiet even she can\’t hear herself.

\n\nShe approaches her door from an angle, and when she finally stands before it, she sees into her apartment. Nothing.
Just her empty floor, her still-to-be-unpacked boxes, and nothing else. No intruder. No sign of Mark.
No pool of blood. Just the bat, right at the threshold, and nothing else.

\n\nShe takes the bat – you never know – and then flinches from the nothing in her apartment.

\n\nBecause nothing is still something too.
Standing at the door she finds each breath harder to take than the last, finds the sound of her own heartbeat growing dimmer and more distant.
Finds the light at the edge of her vision growing quiet. Finds herself drawn to step inside.

\n\nShe lunges for the doorknob, slams the door, and locks it. From the outside.
And then she runs back down to Mark\’s and slams the door there too.

\n\nLeslie places the shopping bag, heavy with groceries, beside the door, and she unlocks it.
She steps inside, her heart hammering.
Immediately she locks the door again, and her hand caresses the bat which has become her constant companion.

\n\nThis is the first time she\’s left Mark\’s apartment in a week but she\’s eaten everything he had.
She\’s wearing his oversized clothes, because hers are… elsewhere. She doesn\’t think where.
She doesn\’t like to think where, but she can\’t stop thinking about it either.

\n\nBut she needs to get moving, to stop cowering. A week is long enough.
She\’s used up her sick days, and Mark’s not coming back.
Mark is… again, she doesn\’t want to think about that. And again, she can\’t stop.

\n\nShe managed to go shopping though. That was a triumph.
Three or so hours outside. She can do this. Return to normal.

\n\nShe snorts. What is normal about this? She lives in someone else\’s apartment, because hers is… she doesn\’t know what.
But it\’s been quiet for a week, so maybe whatever it is, is behind her.
She knows her current arrangement can\’t last,
that eventually someone will notice something, but that\’s a problem for another day. One step at a time.

\n\nShe opens the fridge and grabs a carton of eggs from her grocery bag.

\n\nThree loud bangs on the door.

\n\nThe carton falls on the floor, emitting a wet, subdued crunch.
Leslie approaches the door, her hand trembling towards her bat.
She sees a little old lady outside, the kind of adorable granny that would canvas a neighbourhood for a church fundraiser.
Leslie exhales, feeling relief. She opens the door.

\n\n\“Hello, dear,\” the old woman says, with a beatific smile. \“I\’m Matilda, your downstairs neighbour.
I hate to be a bother, but would it be possible for you to keep that thudding noise down? It\’s been going on all afternoon.\”
</item>

        <item>

\“Should I get up? Should I say something?\”Eric whispered in my general direction from the seat to my left,

\n\n\“No, no, I\’m sure it\’s fine,\”Julia answered from my right, forever not wanting to make a fuss about anything,

\n\n\“The credits have been over for like…5 minutes now, the movie for like 20, so?\” Eric complained not bothering to whisper anymore.
The theater was pitch black all around, soundless without a movie playing,
and blind without the theater screen or any lights on inside of the giant room.

\n\n\“Just give it a minute I\’m sure somebody just fell asleep in the projection booth or something?\”Julia argued,
never wanting to be impolite. Eric scoffed,

\n\n\“Babe, come on. You don\’t gotta be nice to these people, they don\’t give a shit about you,
so you don\’t have to give a shit about them,\”Eric said quite brashly,

\n\n\“Eric!\”Julia hissed, \“Language!\” Julia covered my ears quickly.
It startles me for a second, but her hands are cool against my temples and comforting.
They smell of her Beach Nights hand lotion. I envy her whenever she gets to buy such pretty looking and smelling things for herself.

\n\n\“Oh cool it, Julia, Jupiter\’s cool.
Aren\’t you, Jupiter?\”he asks, though I can feel this is a little demeaning him asking like I\’m a dog, I giggle,
because he ruffles my hair. I like it when he ruffles my hair.
Though I can\’t see my sister or her boyfriend, I know he\’s smiling like a court-jester, and she\’s rolling her eyes.

\n\n\“My mother will kill me if I come back and my little sister\’s spouting cuss words like she\’s back from war.
\”My sister says, \“Don\’t repeat that word, Jupiter.\”she reminds me. I nod and say something to the effect of: mhmm.
It really is dark in here, I can\'t see anything, not even my own hand in front of me.
I\’ve never really been afraid of the dark, I think that\’s because I never had a reason to.
And there was no one to be afraid of.
There was no one else in the theater except for the three of us all the way up in the second to the top row.
In the center, \“best seats in the house\” Julia had rejoiced when we arrived there.

\n\n\“Ugh, this is taking fucking forever!\”Eric whined, it echoed loudly in the empty and silent room.

\n\n\“Eric, oh my goodness, you do not need to be so lou-\”Julia started to say

\n\nBut the lights flickered on for a moment, but we were plunged back into the dark just as fast.
I was relieved, I liked this moment, it felt nice. Being between my big sister and her friend in this theater, just us.
It makes me feel like I\’m a big kid, which is all I want to be.
Because being called \“too young\” all of the time at age ten sucks.
My sister got to do whatever she wanted, and drive cars, and hangout without supervision with her friends.

\n\n\“Okay, maybe it is some kind of power outage?\”said Eric aloud still to my left

\n\n\“Yeah, let\’s just wait for someone to come in, though, okay?\”

\n\n\“What? No, let\'s just leave. Get your candy, Jupiter.
\”Eric argued, I could hear him start to move, the crinkle of his jacket on the leather seat,

\n\n\“Eric, come on, let\’s just stay put, okay?\”she moved and I\’m pretty sure her arm swished in across me to attempt to grab Eric.
The bag of popcorn that had been in her lap, I heard it fall to the ground, \“If it is an emergency, someone will come and get us,\” she said

\n\n\“Julia, it\’s not a big deal, we\’ll just leave,\”
\n\n\“I mean, would it be a big deal to stay, though?\”she said

\n\n\“Oh my god, babe, get your bag. We\’re fucking leaving-\”

\n\nAnd then, I guess, he stood up, I felt the familiar swish of air as he did.
Then I expected him to grab my hand or crossover and take Julia\’s hand and we\’d try to descend the stairs in this expansion of darkness.
But, but, something felt different in the air after that.

\n\n\“Eric?\”Julia whispered in confusion. Did she feel the same thing as I did?

\n\nThere was no response.

\n\nA knot tied itself in my stomach.

\n\nI reached my arm out to where I believed he could have been standing…but there was nothing there but air and layered shadows.

\n\n\“Eric, this isn\’t funny!\”my sister cried out to the empty theater


\n\nThere was still no response.

\n\nIt was cold, chilly in the theater. I was getting tired of not looking at anything.
It was unnerving, I felt along the armrest until I found my sisters hand, I slid my hand into hers and said,

\n\n\“I love you, Julie,\”

\n\n\“You don\’t need to say that, Jupiter, Eric is just trying to scare us. He thinks it\’s funny,\”she tried to explain to me.
But honestly wasn\’t quite convinced herself,

\n\n\“You hear that! Huh? You fucking jerk!\”she screamed into the void in front of us, again her voice shook. She let go of my hand,
something grazed the backs of my ankles,


\n\n\“Ahhh!\”I squealed

\n\n\“What? What?!\”

\n\n\“Something touched my ankle!\” I said, swinging my legs up onto the seat and hugging them to my chest.

\n\n\“Oh my god! Eric, I swear-\”and I heard her stand up on my right side.
Before I could protest, she was already gone. The only thing I had left of her was the scent of her lotion and the popcorn on the floor.

\n\n\“Julie?\”my voice cracked, why was I even talking? I knew she wasn\’t there.

\n\n\“Eric?\” I knew he wasn\’t there either, I just thought I\’d try.

\n\nI sank back farther into my movie theater seat, tried to meld myself into the chair,
so that if there was something watching me it wouldn\’t take me.
I covered my mouth to hide my crying. Even though I wanted to scream.
There was nothing but darkness around me, nothing but shadows, and a void.
Was I even in a movie theater anymore? I don\’t know, I can\’t see, I can\’t see. What\’s worse is that now I\’m alone, all alone.

\n\nThe lights came back on. They stayed on.

\n\nI was still in the movie theater.
My eyes adjusted to the sudden brightness, spots everywhere.
I could see, I could finally see what was around me.
But there was no joy, as the theater was still empty. I was still alone. All alone.
</item>

    </string-array>

    <string name="Horror_Title">
        Berenice, Harrington’s Hearse (Lake Lopez), Darkness in the Rear View Mirror, Instant Messaging, KIDS IN THE DARK, The Oneirophage, I Sat On The Bus, The man in the bunny costume, The ghost babysitter, Stranger in the house, When the dead walk the halls, Sleep Story, just ask for mercy, The Intrusive Demon, la vie en rose, The Perfect Curse, a ghost story, Casa Del Mal, Why Doesn\'t Anyone Rent This Place?, THE GRAVEYARD SHIFT, If the Walls Could Talk, Three Loud Bangs on the Door, The Best Seats In The House
    </string>

    <string name="Horror_Title_A">
        Horror Title List
    </string>

</resources>