<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Smart Book</string>


    <string-array name="story_genre">
        <item>love story</item>
        <item>African Fables</item>
        <item>Horror stories</item>
        <item>poem</item>
        <item>Novel</item>
        <item>Adult</item>
        <item>Fiction </item>
        <item>Writer\'s Blog</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="story_names">
        <item>The man who moved a mountain</item>
        <item>The bicycle ride</item>
        <item>A well-deserved prom night</item>
        <item>The second </item>
        <item>No arms, no legs but love</item>
        <item>Accident with a happy ending</item>
        <item>A heartwarming farewell gift</item>
        <item>Surgery</item>
        <item>Runaway</item>
        <item>The “make-up guy”</item>
        <item>A disastrous accident</item>
        <item>A transformed man</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="Author_Name">
        <item>The man who moved a mountain</item>
        <item>IshNemi</item>
        <item>The Unknown tales</item>
        <item>The second</item>
        <item>No arms, no legs but love</item>
        <item>Accident with a happy ending</item>
        <item>A heartwarming farewell gift</item>
        <item>Surgery</item>
        <item>Runaway</item>
        <item>The “make-up guy”</item>
        <item>A disastrous accident</item>
        <item>A transformed man</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="stories">
        <item>
There are people who say love can move mountains.\n
This might not be physically possible, but Dashrath Manjhi,
also known as the ‘Mountain Man’, came quite close.\n
In one day of his life, his wife fell while crossing a nearby
hill and hurt herself seriously.\n\n
She needed quick medical assistance,but that wasn’t possible due to the hill that isolated their small village
from the next town.\n
Tragically enough, his wife died from the serious injuries
before Dashrath could do anything about it.\n
It was the night when Dashrath Manjhi
decided to carve a small path through the mountain in order to give
his village easier access to medical assistance.\n
It was an ambitious plan and he was heavily ridiculed for it.\n
But after working for 22 years with the greatest determination and willpower,
a path was carved into the hill.\n
Even though he was initially mocked
and ridiculed for his mission to give his hometown easier access to the nearby town,
he finally succeeded.\n\n
His life’s work helped to reduce the distance between the two
towns from 55 km to only 15 km, so that never again such a thing would happen.
</item>
        <item>
It is the year 1975, when Charlotte Von Sledvin, a 19-year-old student of a Swedish royal family,
travels to India to get a portrait made by a gifted artist. The artist was born into a poor
Indian family of the lowest caste, also known as the “untouchables.” Despite the incredibly
difficult circumstances, the artist named Pradyumna Kumar Mahanandia had gained an outstanding
reputation for being a gifted painter. His reputation led Charlotte Von Sledvin to travel all
the way to India to get her portrait done.

\n\nBy the time the portrait was finished, the two had fallen in love. Pradyumna was fascinated with Charlotte’s beauty.
Never before had he seen a more beautiful woman from the Western world.
He gave his best to capture all her beauty in the portrait, yet never fully succeeded.
Nonetheless, the portrait was magnificent and Charlotte fell for his simplicity and his beautiful character.
Because of him, she spontaneously decided to stay longer in India. Out of a couple of days became weeks and then even months.
The two had fallen so deeply in love that they decided to get married according to traditional Indian rituals.

\n\nUnfortunately, the time came when Charlotte had to leave again in order to complete her studies in London.
Thousands of miles separated the two but their feelings for each other never changed.
They stayed in contact through letters, which they exchanged almost weekly with each other.
Naturally, the newlyweds terribly struggled with the great distance between each other.
Charlotte offered her husband to buy him air tickets, which he refused. He had not only decided to
complete his studies first, but he had also set his mind on reuniting with the love of his life on his own terms.
He even made her the promise that he would do anything he can to see her again.

\n\nAfter Pradyumna had finished his studies, he took all his possessions and sold them.
Unfortunately, the money he earned didn’t even come close to a flight ticket.
All he could afford was a cheap and used bicycle. Many would have been greatly
disappointed, some would have even given up. But not Pradyumna. Instead of allowing the difficult
circumstances to stop him from seeing his beloved wife again, he met the decision to
use what he had in order to see her again. Nothing could stop him from reuniting with his wife,
even if that meant an exhausting bicycle ride half around the world.

\n\nHis decision was the beginning of a bicycle journey from India to the Western world. Pradyumna took all his
paintings and brushes along with him in order to financially support his endeavor. His voyage led
him through eight countries and took more than four months. But eventually, he arrived at Charlotte’s hometown
in Sweden and finally saw her again. From then on, the two did never leave each other’s side for too long.
</item>
        <item>
Alex and his grandmother always had a unique bond with each other. He would spend hours
with her, listening to his grandmother’s stories of a lifetime. She once told him that she
had met his grandfather a long time after graduating from high school. This was also the reason
why she was never asked out to go to prom. When the day of Alex’s prom had arrived, his
grandmother was so excited for him. She had watched him save money for months so that he
could afford a tuxedo and even a limousine. His grandmother eagerly waited to find out who
Alex would be taking to the prom. But to her great surprise, he told her that he would
be taking her to prom. He told her that every woman deserves to go to prom, no matter if
they are 18 or 80.
</item>
        <item>
The story of the building of the second Taj Mahal begins when Faizul Hasan Quadri and
his wife Tajammuli Begum begin to realize that their marriage will remain childless.
It is a difficult situation, especially for Tajammuli who begins to question if anyone
will ever remember her after her death. Moved by his saddened wife, Faizul decided to
erect her a monument so that his beautiful wife could be remembered for centuries.
His decision marks the beginning of the construction of a scaled-down replica of the
famous Indian monument.
It has now become a location that attracts many tourists each year.
</item>
        <item>
In 2012, bomb disposal expert Taylor Morris was severely injured after the explosion
of an improvised bomb in Afghanistan. The explosion took all his limbs and changed the
life of the 23-year-old US military soldier forever. While recovering from the injuries in
hospital, Taylor was confronted with the painful realization that his limbs had gone.
He also had to face the fact that he would be dependent on assistance for the rest of his life.
It was an incredibly difficult situation not only for him but also his family and
especially his long-term girlfriend Danielle. But instead of ever giving him up,
Danielle became Taylor’s pillar in life. She helped him recover and took care of him during
this incredibly challenging time.

Danielle played an important role in Taylor’s quick recovery.
She never went away from his side and assisted him greatly when he learned to walk again
with his new prosthetic limbs. After Taylor had recovered, he proposed to his beloved
girlfriend and they got married. It’s a beautiful ending of an incredibly inspiring love
story that shows that nothing can ever stand in-between to people who really love each other.
</item>
        <item>
When Frank’s wife had a car accident, she was so injured that she fell into a coma.
Years passed but Frank did not stop visiting his wife at the hospital. Even though
almost everyone – including the doctors – had given up hope, he remained faithful that she
would one day recover. Every time he visited her, he began talking to her,
recounting all those beautiful moments they spend with each other. One day,
when he showed her the video of their wedding day, she slowly began to move her hand.
She whispered his name and began gaining consciousness. Several weeks after she had woken up,
she had fully recovered and was finally allowed to leave the hospital for good.
When the couple left, she told Frank that she heard his voice while she was in a coma and
that it was his voice that was the greatest aid in helping her to return to consciousness.
</item>
        <item>

When Gene was diagnosed with melanoma, he had only been given six weeks left to live.
It was a shocking diagnosis but Gene decided to use the time he had left to make all the
necessary arrangements for his wife Carol, with whom he had been married for 30 years.
He cashed out his pension and used the money to pay off the house they were living in.
The second step was to arrange a trip for his wife Carol and the rest of the family to Italy.
When they visited a specific church in Venice, a priest was already waiting for the couple.
It was in this church that Gene’s parents had married more than 50 years ago. At that day,
Gene and Carol renewed their wedding vows and had the most beautiful day.

After Gene had died, his wife Carol discovered that he hid hundreds of Post-it notes around
the entire house,
shortly before he died. Throughout the course of many months, she found one note after another.
The notes are beautiful and very personal statements meant to encourage
Carol in this difficult time.
But Gene also reminded his wife in these statements to fully enjoy every aspect of life,
to sell his car and to move on with her life.
It was the most heartwarming farewell gift one could ever imagine.
</item>
        <item>
When a surgeon operated a little girl, complications started to arise. She lost a lot of blood
and was in need of blood transfusion. However, she had blood type O, which wasn’t
available in the hospital.
The surgeon, therefore, asked the girl’s little brother, who was an O-type as well,
if they could draw blood from him. He explained that it was incredibly important,
or has he said, a matter of life and death. The young boy, seemingly afraid,
sat a couple of moments in silence until he finally agreed. He got up and hugged his parents,
wishing them goodbye. After the nurses had taken the blood from him, he whispered anxiously if
they knew how many minutes he had left to live. He was absolutely convinced that he was going to
die so that his sister could live. And he was willing to do so. When the nurses realized
that the young boy thought he was going to die, they cheered him up and explain to
him that he had many wonderful and joyful decades left to live.
</item>
        <item>
When a young student of a Catholic Church asked her teacher about the reasons why she decided
to become a religious sister, her teacher told her a heartwarming love story.
Many years ago, when she was at a similar age, the teacher (let’s call her Ms.
Patterson) fell in love with a young man stemming from a wealthy family.
The two began seeing each other and quickly developed a deep connection with each other.
Unfortunately, the young man’s family was not at all in agreement with the relationship.
They even threatened to enroll their son at a university overseas and far away. As Ms. Patterson
came from a poor background, she couldn’t possibly have afforded to go with him at that time.
This meant that if they wanted to continue the relationship,
they would be separated from each other if they wanted or not.

But they both had fallen so in love with each other that ending the
relationship – no matter in what way – was not an option.
For this reason, they decided to run away. In great secrecy, they planned their escape
and set these plans into action when the young man’s family finally found out about it.
But instead of quickly returning back home after running away, the two never went back.
They joined the church, took holy orders and began traveling the world for various humanitarian missions.
The two spent 40 years traveling and even got married, shortly before the man’s life came to an end.
</item>
        <item>
Dave is a make-up artist who regularly holds makeup artistry classes at the local community college.
Usually, the majority of his students are middle-aged housewives who want to fine-tune their makeup skills.
But this one time, he held a class that was attended by man as well.
The new student was a gentleman in his best years with a seemingly boundless interest in makeup artistry.
He was keen to learn as much as he possibly could and wouldn’t stop until he was satisfied with the result of his work.

Understandably, the man was the number one subject of conversation when the other women were alone.
Speculations quickly started to spread. Was he perhaps a transvestite?
Why else would he attend such a class? The community college was placed in a conservative rural area,
which is why the other participants were quite doubtful of the man’s intentions.

Throughout the lessons, the man carefully listened and wrote everything down he learned.
When the day and class were slowly coming to an end, the outer attendees simply
could not hide their curiosity any longer. When they finally asked him why he was so
interested in makeup artistry, he gave the most inspiring beautiful reply:

He said, “You know, my beloved wife partially lost her eyesight because of diabetes.
She’s no longer able to apply her makeup. I think she’s absolutely beautiful,
even more so without makeup. She knows this and I tell her every day.
But the thing is this,… she simply feels not comfortable leaving the home without make-up.
She never went outside without wearing any makeup-up.
Seeing the love of my life like this makes me really sad.
So I decided to take this course to surprise her! I do not only want to learn how to apply her makeup;
I want her to wear the most beautiful make-up so her inner beauty also shines on the outside.”
</item>
        <item>
When Tonya was driving her daughter to school, she was a witness to a shocking car crash.
The accident was pretty serious, so she got out of her car in order to see if she could help.
There were two cars involved in the accident. One of the cars, an SUV, quickly started to catch fire.
She immediately checked if there were passengers left in the car and saw an unconscious 14-year-old boy.
Without hesitating, she pulled the car door open and brought the boy to safety.
He was brought to a hospital where Tonya and her daughter visited him several times in order to help him recover.
As time started to pass by, Tonya began to notice that her daughter started to go to the hospital on her own account.
As it turns out, the two teens fell in love with each other and married each other when they had grown up.
</item>
        <item>

One day Natalie found a worn down diary in the toolbox of her dad. It was his diary that he wrote roundabout the
time he was 18 years old. Natalie absolutely loves her dad, who is not only the best dad but also a loving
and kind husband to her mother. So wasn’t easy for her to open the diary, but eventually, she became so curious
about his life that she decided to read it. The last entry in the diary was a short paragraph,
hectically scribbled down. It said that at the time of writing the entry, he was 18 years old,
an alcoholic who dropped out from college with a criminal record. Her dad also noted in the entry that one
month later he would become a teen father. But he also made the promised to himself that he would set his life straight.
That he would become the father for his little daughter that he never had.
</item>


    </string-array>



    <string name="Love_Title">
The man who moved a mountain, The bicycle ride, A well-deserved prom night, The second Taj Mahal, No arms, no legs but love, Accident with a happy ending, A heartwarming farewell gift, Surgery, Runaway, The \“make-up guy\”, A disastrous accident, A transformed man
    </string>
    <string name="Love_Title_A">
        Love Title List
    </string>

    <string name="Moto_Notes">
        PICK A STORY,READ A STORY, \"ESTORADEY\" YOU\'LL BE ALRIGHT
    </string>
    <string name="Moto_Notice">
        Maxim
    </string>


    <string name="love">

    </string>
    <string name="About_The_App">
        In this App i have tried to provide collection of short stories
        \nfrom famous authors to up-coming young authors and their names,
        \nsome of these short stories are been written by unknown authors
        \nyet are still good short stories.
        \nIf you find any mistakes in this App as whole,you can send me an
        email to smartAppdevelopment1234@gmail.com
        \ni will get back to you or rectify the mistakes as soon as possible
    </string>

    <string name="attribution"><b>Special Thanks to Freepik website for providing the following icons</b>\n\n

<a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-vector/african-savannah-landscape-wild-nature-africa_21376678.htm#page=3&amp;query=africa&amp;position=17&amp;from_view=search">Image by upklyak</a> on Freepik\n
Image by <a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/blue-mist-smog-black-background_4251267.htm#query=blue%20smoke%20background&amp;position=48&amp;from_view=keyword&amp;track=ais">Freepik</a>\n
<a href="http://www.freepik.com">Designed by Freepik</a>\n
Image by <a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/usa-independence-day-concept-with-old-declaration_2290333.htm#query=old%20paper%20burnt%20written&amp;position=38&amp;from_view=search&amp;track=ais">Freepik</a>\n
Image by <a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-vector/background-galaxy-particles_5940671.htm#query=blue%20sstars%20background&amp;position=17&amp;from_view=search&amp;track=ais">Freepik</a>\n
Image by <a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-vector/collection-young-people-reading_5172217.htm#page=4&amp;query=girl%20reading%20silhouette&amp;position=43&amp;from_view=keyword&amp;track=ais">Freepik</a>\n
Image by <a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-vector/set-young-people-reading_5147237.htm?query=girl%20reading%20silhouette#from_view=detail_alsolike">Freepik</a>\n
Image by <a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/love-inscription-with-small-heart_3537551.htm#from_view=detail_serie">Freepik</a>\n
Image by <a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-vector/flat-hand-drawn-hygge-lifestyle-illustration_12301251.htm#page=2F&amp;query=book%20reading%20illustrastion&amp;position=31&amp;from_view=search&amp;track=ais">Freepik</a>\n
<a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-vector/ethnic-people-african-tribes-wild-animal_9721341.htm#page=2&amp;query=african%20map%20lion%20human&amp;position=21&amp;from_view=search&amp;track=ais">Image by brgfx</a> on Freepik\n
<a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/blank-catalog-magazines-book-mock-up-blue-background_1255169.htm#page=5&amp;query=book%20background&amp;position=4&amp;from_view=search">Image by jannoon028</a> on Freepik\n
<a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/3d-halloween-background-with-zombie-hand-bursting-out-ground_17308320.htm#query=horror%20background&amp;position=2&amp;from_view=search">Image by kjpargeter</a> on Freepik\n
<a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-vector/isometric-icon-with-colorful-books-white-background-vector-illustration_23580825.htm#query=isometric%20icon%20with%20colorful%20book&amp;position=14&amp;from_view=search&amp;track=country_rows_v1">Image by macrovector</a> on Freepik\n
<a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-vector/study-online-during-coronavirus_24382772.htm#query=book%20and%20sunsat%20reading%20illustrationand&amp;position=23&amp;from_view=search&amp;track=ais">Image by rawpixel.com</a> on Freepik\n
<a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-vector/autumn-watercolor-background-with-leaves_9221810.htm?query=dry%20leaves&amp;collectionId=1698&amp;page=2&amp;position=29&amp;from_view=collections">Image by pikisuperstar</a> on Freepik\n
<a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-vector/offline-concept-illustration_18352146.htm#query=lost%20internet%20connection&amp;position=4&amp;from_view=search&amp;track=sph">Image by storyset</a> on Freepik\n
<a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-vector/elephant-office-with-working-businesspeople_32069087.htm#query=idiom&amp;position=15&amp;from_view=search&amp;track=sph">Image by upklyak</a> on Freepik\n
<a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/stack-books-black-wooden-table_21708612.htm#query=school%20books%20library%20bookshelf&amp;position=44&amp;from_view=search&amp;track=sph">Image by fabrikasimf</a> on Freepik\n
Image by <a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/halloween-wallpaper-with-cemetery-night_19055598.htm#page=2&amp;query=horror%20background&amp;position=10&amp;from_view=search&amp;track=sph">Freepik</a>\n
<a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-vector/isometric-icon-with-colorful-books-white-background-vector-illustration_23580825.htm#query=blue%20book%20background&amp;position=33&amp;from_view=search&amp;track=sph">Image by macrovector</a> on Freepik\n
<a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-vector/sunset-ocean-red-sky-with-sun-going-down-sea-surrounded-with-mountains-beautiful-nature-scenic-landscape-background-evening-heaven-view-gulls-flying-water-cartoon-vector-illustration_17995521.htm#query=orange%20sky%20sunset%20ocean%20wave&amp;position=41&amp;from_view=search&amp;track=sph">Image by upklyak</a> on Freepik

    </string>

    <string name="About_Homepage">
        All the categories and genre of short stories are listed here on the Homepage
    </string>
    <string name="About_View">
       you can view title-list contained  in a particular category
    </string>
    <string name="About_editmode">
       Edit your text-font short story and set your screen to dark-mode,light-mode and back to default
    </string>
    <string name="Home_Message">
      Never Date Or Trust Anyone Who Never Read Or Bought A Book In Their Entire Life
    </string>
    <string name="Home_Short_Stories">
      Read more about Love stories, Fables, Horrors, Poems, Novels, Fiction that contains funny stories,and  Erotic short-stories
    </string>
    <string name="Home_Long_Stories">
     It wouldn\'t be so fun without long texts to stimulate your adrenaline,so enjoy every possible good book from classic to modern best selling authors
    </string>
    <string name="app_overview">app overview</string>


</resources>